<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.0/excerpt/"	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.0/"><channel>	<title>Tuttle goes to SXSWi 2010</title>	<link></link>	<description></description>	<pubDate>Sun Jan 17 04:05:29 -0800 2010</pubDate>	<generator>http://posterous.com</generator>	<language>en</language>	<wp:wxr_version>1.0</wp:wxr_version>	<wp:base_site_url>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com</wp:base_site_url>	<wp:base_blog_url>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com</wp:base_blog_url>		<image>		<url>http://files.posterous.com/user_profile_pics/437642/icon1.jpg</url>		<title>Tuttle goes to SXSWi 2010</title>		<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com</link>	</image>	<item>	<title>Dana goes for a spin (Boston to NYC)</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/dana-goes-for-a-spin-boston-to-nyc</link>	<pubDate>Wed Mar 10 13:21:12 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/dana-goes-for-a-spin-boston-to-nyc</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='164' poster='http://posterous.com/images/media_thumbnail/default_poster_frame.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/Y4A7vcON4l9cWecyoRcJMNi3wJin5Es4idZJQFBDczmsREMxbSOk89NTzK64/wg_has_a_turn.mp4'></source></video></div><p>silly</p><p /><div>shot on the Nokia N900</div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[sillyshot on the Nokia N900]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Mar 10 13:21:12 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Day 4: Our adventures in three boroughs</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/day-4-our-adventures-in-three-boroughs</link>	<pubDate>Sun Mar 07 05:37:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/day-4-our-adventures-in-three-boroughs</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>Yesterday was a blur. We started with Bagels and coffee for Michelle (yes &ndash; I am still caffeine free for the NSPCC Kick bullying campaign) &ndash; Nick went out on his scooter to go and pick them up for us.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>I had an all-dressed one with all the toppings including onion.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>The thing about these bagels that make them stand out is the salt. It&rsquo;s just a thin sprinkling of it, but it makes all the difference. And you don&rsquo;t even need to put anything on it, in fact I&rsquo;d argue it&rsquo;d sully the taste if you did.</span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>First interview of the day was in Redhook with Jen and Brian Gubicza of <a href="http://www.zooguu.com" title="Zooguu">Zooguu </a>(thanks to John DeYoung who set it all up!).<span style="">&nbsp; </span>They work out of a warehouse space with around 12 other artists making stuffed toys to be sold on Etsy, their own online shop and in craft fairs.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>The warehouse is in an area that only a few years ago was known for crime &ndash; On the Waterfront was based on that area and bodies have been known to wash up on shore. More recently, gritty crime chases are filmed there &ndash; Matt Damon was filming down the road the week before so I&rsquo;m going to keep my eye out next time I&rsquo;m watching a chase scene down by the docks. A large amount of the area was bought up by a retired cop who wanted to regenerate Redhook. So anyone wanting to rent his properties has to put in a proposal to show what they will be using it for. Which is why Jen and Brian found themselves in a warehouse over looking the water (and the statue of Liberty). </span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>They are starting to get some interest from wholesalers, which can be trickier as Brian traces and cuts all the patterns for Jen to sew by hand.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Yes, that&rsquo;s right.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>All Zooguu toys are hand-made.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Lately they have been doing more collaborations with illustrators (Brian being one of them), to make stuffed toys out of their 2D work. The results have their own Zooguu-esque quality that still keeps the aesthetic that the original illustrations have.</span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>All of the toys have a quirky appeal that makes them loved by adults and children alike. And because they are homemade, you can pick what colours you want each part to be.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Jen always knows when a kid put the order in as the colours are not ones most people would ever put together.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>But that&rsquo;s what makes these toys so personal and something you could grow up with. Though Brian teases her about it, Jen always makes sure she packs the toy so when you open it; it looks up at you like it&rsquo;s greeting you like an old friend. If you want one of your own, you can order them online and you can get one sent to you anywhere in the world. Go. Do it. I&rsquo;m going to. <a href="http://www.zooguu.com" title="Zooguu">www.zooguu.com</a></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>After lunch in midtown with my old friend Reisha, we met with Jill of <a href="http://www.jillwrites.com" title="Jill writes">www.jillwrites.com</a>, who is born and raised in Brooklyn and lives on Staten Island. We took the ferry over to Staten Island with her and looked back across the water at Manhattan. To me this ferry is the starting point of my favourite movie: Working Girl.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Well, one of my favourite movies. The film opens up with Carly Simon singing her heart out as Melanie Griffith makes the journey into Manhattan to work her way to the top.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>She has brains and beauty but no one takes her seriously because of where she&rsquo;s from. Honestly, the Carly Simon song went through my head the whole way there AND back.</span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>On the way to the Tweet-Up at BBH in the AT&amp;T building (<a href="http://www.32sixthave.com/location.html">32 Avenue of the Americas</a>), Michelle and I made a special stop inspired by Zooguu&rsquo;s Brian &ndash; <a href="http://www.bigwaste.com/photos/ny/ghostbusters/firehouse.shtml" title="The Ghostbusters firestation">the Ghostbusters fire station</a>! Yes, photos and video were taken.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>It was much narrower than I expected but what a beautiful little firehouse it was.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>And just around the corner from where the meet up was.<p /></span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman,serif; font-size: 12pt;">Thanks go out to Dan, who helped make the tweet-up in New York happen.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>We did a live feed as the night progressed so anyone, anywhere in the world could be a part of it. I found that by capturing it and interviewing, the two hours go by too quickly and I actually met very few people there.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>And everyone I spoke was so interesting that I wish we had more time to meet and talk with everyone there.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>But I guess that&rsquo;s how it all goes and the people you meet are the right people to meet at the time.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>And in less than 2 days, I&rsquo;ve met so many wonderful people that I would have never met under other circumstances.</span></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Yesterday was a blur. We started with Bagels and coffee for Michelle (yes ??? I am still caffeine free for the NSPCC Kick bullying campaign) ??? Nick went out on his scooter to go and pick them up for us. I had an all-dressed one with all the toppings...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Mar 07 05:37:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Patrick]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Sun Mar 07 06:24:16 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Sun Mar 07 06:24:16 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I've been processing my photos from my trip to the States last year - I still have several hundred to go... But I have some great pictures taken from the Staten Island ferry of a storm over Manhattan: shiny skyscrapers set against black clouds.They may even get posted to flickr by the time you return! ]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Almost the end</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/almost-the-end-3</link>	<pubDate>Sun Mar 21 11:27:03 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/almost-the-end-3</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4447160573/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4004/4447160573_4922e803eb_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a></div><p />I&#39;m sitting in Borders in Downtown Long Beach sipping Seattle&#39;s Best Coffee and using the (still meagre, but better than on the Queen Mary) wifi. ??Hopefully I&#39;ll get a good bunch of pictures up to flickr before I have to go to lunch. ??Then I&#39;ll probably get back to some writing or strumming my ukulele on the beach before I meet up with @msjen who&#39;s taking me to the airport.<p /><div>I still have probably a dozen blog posts to write about this at least. ??In addition I have hundreds of photographs to tag and describe properly - many of them with stories to tell along side. ??And I have video that&#39;s been too hefty to mess around with on this Nokia Booklet. ??That&#39;s ignoring what probably amounted to nearly 30 hours of video shot by Michelle &amp; Heather and everything that Brian created too. ??I&#39;m pleased with the amount of content we&#39;ve created and published on the way, but it&#39;s nothing compared to what we have jointly sitting on our hard drives. ??I&#39;m pretty sure there&#39;s a book in this as well as a couple of movies, a newspaper or two, workshops and consulting to pass on what we&#39;ve learned about ourselves, the USA, our respective cultures and the internet.</div> <p /><div>I&#39;ve travelled through 20 states to get from Boston to Los Angeles - didn&#39;t see all of them in daylight but I can say that I&#39;ve been through more places than many visitors manage in a 3-week trip and probably visited more of the country than many of the people I&#39;ve met along the way, let alone their less-well travelled friends and neighbours.</div> <p /><div>I&#39;m tired, but inspired.</div><p /><div>There are too many people to thank to do them justice here - I hope that I&#39;ve expressed my gratitude sufficiently face to face, but I won&#39;t stop saying thank you - this trip wasn&#39;t about us, it was about you.</div> <p /><div><div>I haven&#39;t fallen in love with the USA but I have a pretty solid crush on it. ??America has surprised me. ??Americans have surprised me.</div><p /><div>I&#39;ve surprised myself.</div><p /><p /></div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I'm sitting in Borders in Downtown Long Beach sipping Seattle's Best Coffee and using the (still meagre, but better than on the Queen Mary) wifi. Hopefully I'll get a good bunch of pictures up to flickr before I have to go to lunch. Then I'll prob...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Mar 21 11:27:03 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Englishmen at Breakfast</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/englishmen-at-breakfast</link>	<pubDate>Thu Apr 29 14:32:55 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/englishmen-at-breakfast</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='217' poster='http://getfile4.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/4PqVFwuapnLZiDjjnvxZebp7NZg7ruVrVxzDERayojmRr8wexY3MRFhiQiei/brianemotionnola.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile3.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/4PqVFwuapnLZiDjjnvxZebp7NZg7ruVrVxzDERayojmRr8wexY3MRFhiQiei/brianemotionnola.mp4'></source></video></div><p>This clip is from my last breakfast with Brian in New Orleans, just before Taylor drove me over to Austin.?? This was just after I&#39;d been <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/lloyd-plays-in-nola">playing and singing on the front step of Laura&#39;s house</a> and we&#39;d done some final filming with Heather on the steps too, just summing up what we thought.?? It was an important milestone in the trip and it was a very good breakfast - the <a href="http://www.nolacakes.com/">Cake Cafe on Chartres St</a><p /> We talk, as Englishmen so often do over breakfast, about the unexpected emotions that our encounters were bringing up.?? And we recognised for the first time here, I think, the pivotal importance of our visit to Riderwood.<p /> I&#39;ve since been thinking about the roles that we each played throughout the trip.?? I guess here we&#39;re both partly being analysts and recorders and Brian throws in a bit of good parenting at the end.<p />It&#39;s going to continue to be slow going I think with processing the video.?? The bulk of what I have left needs to be stitched together as it was shot during the Austin to LA train ride. <p /> </p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[This clip is from my last breakfast with Brian in New Orleans, just before Taylor drove me over to Austin. This was just after I'd been playing and singing on the front step of Laura's house and we'd done some final filming with Heather on the ste...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Apr 29 14:32:55 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name>englishmen-at-breakfast</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>We're doing Tuttle Boston on March 3rd</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/were-doing-tuttle-boston-on-march-3rd</link>	<pubDate>Thu Feb 18 00:56:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="boston"><![CDATA[boston]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="conversations"><![CDATA[conversations]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="support"><![CDATA[support]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="techsuperpowers"><![CDATA[techsuperpowers]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/were-doing-tuttle-boston-on-march-3rd</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/needfire/1219873714/">http://www.flickr.com/photos/needfire/1219873714/</a> <br />photo by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/needfire/" target="_blank">needfire</a></p><p>Big thanks to Mike Oh at Tech Superpowers in Boston for &nbsp;saying "mi case es su casa" and helping arrange an evening Tuttle tweetup at the start of our trip.</p><p>Mike came to Tuttle in London soon after we moved to the ICA I think and he's a regular visitor when he's in London. &nbsp;He and I talked excitedly about his concept of a Digital Lounge in his <a href="http://www.techsuperpowers.com">Mac Support Shop</a> and the idea of doing Tuttle in Boston. &nbsp;I'm really glad that he both managed to open <a href="http://www.techsuperpowers.com/digilounge">Digilounge</a> and to do several tuttle-esque events there. &nbsp;I'm looking forward to coming over and giving it a bit of London flavour.&nbsp;</p><p>Mike has said we can use Digilounge as Tuttle HQ for the day. &nbsp;We're also talking to a certain prestigious business school on the other side of the Charles River about running some conversation spaces so we're going to be busy.</p><p>And on Wednesday evening we'll be holding Tuttle Boston there for local folk to come together, get some beer (or coffee!) &amp; nibbles (also generously provided by Mr Oh and his team) and join in some great tuttle-ish conversations.</p><p>At the moment Heather, Michelle &amp; I are arriving in Boston at around 1.30 on Tuesday March 2nd and Brian is going to get there a little earlier, we think. &nbsp;We'll take it easy on the Tuesday night while we acclimatise to the different gravity conditions of the USA, 18th Century spelling conventions, escaping the metric system etc. &nbsp;But as we're getting the train to New York City on the Thursday morning Wednesday is the big opportunity to meet up with us, so give us a shout and help us get the trip off to a bostin' start (sorry, couldn't help it...)</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[http://www.flickr.com/photos/needfire/1219873714/ photo by needfire Big thanks to Mike Oh at Tech Superpowers in Boston for saying "mi case es su casa" and helping arrange an evening Tuttle tweetup at the start of our trip. Mike came to Tuttle in ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Feb 18 00:56:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>High-level itinerary choices</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/high-level-itinerary-choices</link>	<pubDate>Sun Jan 17 05:07:25 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/high-level-itinerary-choices</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[I spent some time this morning on the Amtrak timetable site.?? I will never complain about <a href="http://nationalrail.co.uk">nationalrail.co.uk</a> again.?? Well I probably will, but when I do so I will likely bear in mind the fact that things could be worse.<p /> Everyone has said to me &quot;You know they really don&#39;t have a train system like Europe&quot; and I&#39;m like &quot;Well duh!&quot; but it wasn&#39;t until I actually started putting real dates and times in that I realised what a constraint travelling by train will be.?? Yipeee!?? Nonetheless, I am completely committed to making this work by rail.?? Loads of people do road trips across the States.?? Only a bunch of nutcases from London would attempt to do it on the railroad.<p /> So there&#39;s a decision that needs to be made first of all, which is the overall shape of the trip. What is &quot;firm&quot; is that we take our time to get there, having conversations on the way, we hang out at the festival and then pull together our movie based on whatever happened in the previous week or so. At the moment I have a few alternative ways of doing this in mind:<p /> 1.?? The original idea was to return the way we came and use the time we have on the train to reflect a little on our experience and turn it into an interesting narrative.<p />2.?? Another suggestion was that instead of heading back east, we carry on across the desert (by train again) through Tucson and up into California, finishing our trip either in San Francisco (where we&#39;re likely to meetup with people from SXSW who flew straight back) or that place further south where we have friends in Long Beach.<p /> 3.?? We stick around and finish the movie making in Austin, taking in some of the music festival which starts after interactive, and then fly straight back home from there.<p />Hmmm.... pros and cons, pros and cons]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I spent some time this morning on the Amtrak timetable site. I will never complain about nationalrail.co.uk again. Well I probably will, but when I do so I will likely bear in mind the fact that things could be worse. Everyone has said to me "You ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Jan 17 05:07:25 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[pollyrt]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Tue Jan 19 05:25:00 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Jan 19 05:25:00 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to following your travels.You've probably seen this but www.seat61.com/UnitedStates.htm has useful summary info on routes and timings.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Tue Jan 19 05:31:19 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Jan 19 05:31:19 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Yes, thank you that's where I started out and am getting most of my information from now :)]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Nailing down the itinerary Part 1</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/nailing-down-the-itinerary-part-1</link>	<pubDate>Thu Jan 28 15:38:08 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="amtrak"><![CDATA[amtrak]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="itinerary"><![CDATA[itinerary]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/nailing-down-the-itinerary-part-1</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Right.&nbsp; Let's come at it from the other end.</p><p>We want to be in Austin late on 11th or early on 12th March for the opening.</p><p>This means leaving New Orleans on the 11th - it's an 8 or 9 hour drive (Taylor has offered a lift &amp; there may be a bus going) so leaving early on the 11th feels do-able.&nbsp; I had a lingering idea that I'd love to actually roll in to Austin station - I saw it last year and parked it as part of the idea that turned into this year's trip.&nbsp; However, New Orleans has become a solid part of the trip too and insanely enough the timetable suggests that the only way from NOLA to Austin is via (wait for it...) Chicago and if we left NOLA on Thursday 11th, we'd get to Austin on the Saturday.&nbsp; So it's all working out beautifully.&nbsp; I really want to have a full day in New Orleans so that would be the 10th and so we need to arrive on 9th.</p><p>So the 9th is a travel day from Atlanta to NOLA leaving Atlanta at 08:38 and arriving in the Big Easy at 19:38 yup a cool 12-hour trip.</p><p>Now the trip from Washington to Atlanta is a biggie too - 14 hours overnight.&nbsp; So to be able to leave on the 9th we'll have to arrive on the morning of 8th which means leaving Washington on Sunday night (7th) Train leaves Union Station at 18:30</p><p>Our time in Washington then would seem to be Saturday night and Sunday.&nbsp; We could leave New York on Saturday morning and get to Washington after lunch in time for an evening do and then maybe a brunch date on Sunday.</p><p>This means our main event will need to be on Friday evening in New York and to make the most of our time there we should arrive on the afternoon of 4th.&nbsp; Boston to NYC is 4 hours - so leaving first thing (there's an 09:40 gets in at 13:50) should get us there OK.</p><p>This means an evening event on 3rd in Boston and probably arriving the night before in order to give time for last minute glitches.</p><p>Oh, so that means leaving UK on 2nd - earlier than I expected.&nbsp; Which has implications for costs - I just added 3 nights accomodation to the budget... ah well, better to know now.&nbsp; In my head, I now have every project manager I've ever worked with looking at me over the top of their glasses, nodding and saying "I told you so"</p><p>so to summarize in reverse order, which is actually the right order:</p><p>2nd March Fly London to Boston</p><p>3rd March day in Boston for conversations (any Berkman Centre folk up for that?) and a Boston Tuttle in the evening.</p><p>4th March 09:40 to NYC arrives 13:50 evening tweetup</p><p>5th March day in NYC for conversations and exploration (New Work City and other coworkers?) unconfirmed sponsor event in the evening</p><p>6th March 10:05 to Washington, DC arrives 13:25 evening conversation space and tweetup</p><p>7th March Brunch conversation spaces, afternoon exploration 18:30 to Atlanta arrives 08:12 the next day</p><p>8th March day in Atlanta, conversations, exploration, evening tweetup<p />  9th March 08:38 to New Orleans arrive 19:38<p />  10th March day in NOLA - exploration &amp; conversations in the hands of Mr Taylor Davidson<p />  11th March drive with Taylor to Austin<p /> 12th SXSWi begins - sighs of relief all round</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Right. Let's come at it from the other end. We want to be in Austin late on 11th or early on 12th March for the opening. This means leaving New Orleans on the 11th - it's an 8 or 9 hour drive (Taylor has offered a lift & there may be a bus going) ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Jan 28 15:38:08 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 15:41:11 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 15:41:11 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Very jealous, sounds like a great trip. Looking forward to Tuttling with you in Texas.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 15:43:23 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 15:43:23 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I think that works - though am starting to think that SXXSW should be the destination.  That it's the climax to the journey though coast to coast is nice it could be a nice north to south journey and then a little fun, more discussion, more bits of having fun, talking, cowboys, then...home.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>mail@taylordavidson.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 16:13:53 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 16:13:53 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Right.  I'll work on a couple things for you in NOLA. Great to hear you're coming.  Remember my car probably only has space for 2, but we'll hack that out :)]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 23:17:24 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 23:17:24 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Sam, I'm trying to see how we can tie things together with other Brits during the trip.  Nonetheless, big thanks for making Tuttle in Texas happen again on the Sunday!]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 23:25:26 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 23:25:26 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Heather, I know.  I'm very drawn though to getting over to the West Coast in order to make the overall shape of the trip be Boston to LA because those are the places where we have strong Tuttle support.  I also accept that this is a pretty big trip already... and carrying on would bump up the costs because the rail passes are for 15 days or 30 days.  It all comes down for me to how much support we can raise.  But also remembering that we don't all have to do the same thing all the way.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 23:29:40 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 23:29:40 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Taylor, capacity noted.  I'm not surprised that the NOLA -&gt; Austin leg is going to be the wildest and most unpredictable.  However, I'm also confident that we can build enough momentum in the next 6 weeks to get us from Louisian-i-a to Texas, no matter how many of us there are]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Fiona Cullinan]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>fionacullinan@hotmail.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Sun Feb 07 05:09:53 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Sun Feb 07 05:09:53 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Oh ello! I'm flying to Miami and routing either through Atlanta/Birmingham to New Orleans (or direct bus to New Orleans). Might be able to join up with TuttletoTexas for the last leg anyway! PS There's a train from New Orleans to San Antonio then Austin (if that helps).]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Lloyd's &quot;surprise&quot; outing - he gets to play the Uke!</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/lloyds-surprise-outing-he-gets-to-play-the-uk</link>	<pubDate>Mon Mar 08 14:54:25 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Condon]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/lloyds-surprise-outing-he-gets-to-play-the-uk</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-size: medium;">Lloyd Davis&rsquo;s &ldquo;surprise&rdquo; on Saturday last was to go to a massive gated complex for &lsquo;seniors&rsquo;, meet their Ukelele Group and play with them and for them.&nbsp; But we didn&rsquo;t know that before we got there; just that Lloyd had to bring his uke and I was asked to bring my guitar.&nbsp; Put like that it sounds a bit stark and unfriendly.&nbsp; It was anything but.</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">We were well over an hour late.&nbsp; Our train from New York to Washington was delayed; we got stuck in an awful traffic jam.&nbsp; We were crammed into a small car with instruments, cameras, a big tripod bag and rucksacks.&nbsp; I hate being late nearly as much as a Japanese person hates being late.&nbsp; We were unpardonably late.&nbsp; So we turned off the freeway, up the hill and saw the buildings; large apartment blocks with high-level enclosed walkways between them, surrounded by car parks and linked by access roads.&nbsp; &ldquo;Go up the hill, straight through the four-way stop, right at the T; you&rsquo;ll see a pond and a gazebo on the right.&nbsp; The Village Center is right in front&rdquo; said the laconic guard before looking into the car and making remarks along the lines of &ldquo;I never knew you could get a whole family in one o&rsquo; them things&rdquo;.</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">At first, I was shocked at the place - the scale of it and the closed-off nature of a gated community on the outskirts of Washington DC - not something I&rsquo;m familiar with from the UK.&nbsp; It made me think of being on a cruise; but on a vast brick and concrete liner firmly rooted to the Maryland earth.&nbsp; We followed the instructions, watching the little blue blob of the GPS on the iPhone ping away.&nbsp; In the distance we saw a small red-clad figure, waving.&nbsp; The red was a Hawaiian shirt.&nbsp; &ldquo;Ahh . . .&rdquo; said Lloyd like the noise of a penny dropping into treacle.&nbsp; I started to feel nervous.</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">We groaningly extracted ourselves from the car; not easily or quickly.&nbsp; The lady in the red Hawaiian shirt was one of our hosts.&nbsp; &ldquo;I hope they&rsquo;re all still there; we eat early round here.&rdquo; she said, ushering us through the reception area and up a wide staircase.&nbsp; I didn&rsquo;t know how Lloyd was coping with his &lsquo;surprise&rsquo; - Michelle was filming him and I was a bit ahead of that and trying to deal with my own reactions to the place.&nbsp; That&rsquo;ll be a piece of video worth watching!</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">We went into the Music Room and found about 15 people with ukes and a lady sitting behind a piano at the front of the room.&nbsp; All of them were wearing bright Hawaiian shirts; cheerful friendly faces.&nbsp; We apologised for being so late.&nbsp; They&rsquo;d obviously been waiting, apparently with the patience of the wise; and though I felt bad and awkward about being late; they kindly made it clear that that said more about me than about them.</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">Lloyd was an instant hit, as you&rsquo;d expect.&nbsp; He got out his uke, stood at the front of the room, chatted and tuned, a bit of banter - he didn&rsquo;t look nervous.&nbsp; I found a space at the back of the room, next to a guy with a lovely-looking baritone uke (which was even better when he played it).&nbsp; Just along from me were two other blokes.&nbsp; I thought &ldquo;That&rsquo;s ok, I can hide at the back!&rdquo;.&nbsp; I unpacked and tuned my travel guitar - a normal sized guitar fretboard with acoustic strings and action, but a reduced-size soundbox; pretty and soft-voiced, delicate.&nbsp; It should fit ok with the ukes.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">They suggested that Lloyd play for them but he said &ldquo;Why don&rsquo;t we find something we can all play; what do you suggest?&rdquo;.&nbsp; So they handed round song sheets and we had a go at &ldquo;Alexander&rsquo;s Ragtime Band&rdquo;.</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">Away we went; I could hear the baritone uke playing under the rest of the ukes, could hear the guys to my right singing the harmonies - one of them with a pure tenor.&nbsp; I found a space to sing and, maybe, play a bit; finding chords and bass notes and singing the harmonies with Lloyd and my friends at the back.&nbsp; The lady at the piano kept us to time with a basic approach, adding in supportive runs and little flourishes that spoke of a talent reined back.&nbsp; I remember thinking &ldquo;Wow, I&rsquo;d like to hear her play what she usually plays . . .&rdquo;.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">This somewhat bald and factual account leaves out the feeling in the room.&nbsp; Which was extraordinary.&nbsp; A mix of players and abilities; some of whom have only recently started playing and others who have played for a long time.&nbsp; It turns out that the lady at the piano is an accomplished former professional who had her own girl band decades ago.&nbsp; Her husband was a band-leader and saxophonist.&nbsp; It didn&rsquo;t matter that some of us weren&rsquo;t particularly good (and I include myself in this statement).&nbsp; It&rsquo;s not the kind of music know how to play, and I don&rsquo;t think I&rsquo;ve ever sat in with 15 ukes before!&nbsp; Stick me in a pub session with the fiddles and the Irish tunes and I&rsquo;m yer man.&nbsp; But 30s songs and ragtime, well, that&rsquo;s a different matter.&nbsp; And, d&rsquo;you know it didn&rsquo;t matter a bit.&nbsp; Because we were all there having a go; for the music and for the hell of it.</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">I can&rsquo;t, sitting here writing this later the same evening, remember the other tunes we played - seems odd I know but I was listening and concentrating so hard - trying to find the space to play and not mess up.&nbsp; I leant on the baritone guy - and tried to follow him.&nbsp; He played with a delicate and beautiful tone - chording the harmonies under the melody.&nbsp; Later, I talked to him and found out that he&rsquo;s played the guitar and the uke since he was a teenager.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">Lloyd did his stuff next - and he played and sang with an openness and joy that captivated the room.&nbsp; His first song &ldquo;Who&rsquo;s sorry now?&rdquo; brought a gasp from a lady at the back of the room - she was still; listening and remembering; an important song for her and she cried a little bit, I think.&nbsp; He sang the old songs that they knew.&nbsp; He played in a way that helped to understand how to play better and how to live in the music.&nbsp; I can quite understand, as you read this, that you might think I&rsquo;m exaggerating or that it sounds a bit corny.&nbsp; But the emotion in the room was palpable and deep and the communication was at a level difficult to describe; it was touching.&nbsp; Happy and sad at the same time, the music bridging the present and the past simultaneously, and the songs linking us together irrespective of age or ability.&nbsp; I&rsquo;ll never forget it.</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">We had to stop for a bit after that.&nbsp; There was a bit of chat.&nbsp; Heather asked some questions and Michelle filmed.&nbsp; We found out a bit about the group; why they&rsquo;d formed, how often they meet.&nbsp; They perform. They&rsquo;re on Youtube.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">I was asked to sing.&nbsp; Now, being brought up in an Irish family, everyone has a song or two, a party piece.&nbsp; These circumstances, I find difficult - with my family I sing; with people I don&rsquo;t know it&rsquo;s harder.&nbsp; I thought of 3 or 4 songs I could do and then settled on the Night Visiting Song.&nbsp; And to those of you who know me; no, I didn&rsquo;t forget any of the words nor did I get the verses in the wrong order (a fluke, obviously).&nbsp; I was pretty nervous but it seemed to go ok.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">Lloyd finished off with a number and then, as is a tradition with this group, they all joined in with &ldquo;Happy Trails&rdquo;.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">Afterwards, we had an early dinner with three of the ladies in an enormous dining room filled with circular tables.&nbsp; They talked about their lives, both past and present - one of them worked for NASA and she said she didn&rsquo;t want the video on a DVD - she&rsquo;d prefer a flash drive.&nbsp; They talked to us about the place and the community in and around it.&nbsp; About their own independence and the levels of care they can design for themselves (from largely independent living through to fulltime nursing care).&nbsp; And yes, the seniors are well-to-do people; I don&rsquo;t see how they could afford to live in this place otherwise.&nbsp; The people I spoke to seemed mostly to be former professional people, now retired and in control of their lives.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">The young people serving and clearing tables go to local high schools; they get paid for the work and once they&rsquo;ve worked there for a while, they can qualify for college scholarships funded by the seniors.&nbsp; I watched the movement of people around the dining room, young and old, and the way they smiled and talked to each other.&nbsp; Between the people serving and their elders there appeared to be a feeling of mutual respect.&nbsp; It felt authentic.</span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">As we left the dining table, I offered my arm to the lady whose idea it was to start the Ukelele Group.&nbsp; She has a buggy to get around in she had parked nearby.&nbsp; I&rsquo;d talked to her&nbsp; across the table over dinner.&nbsp; A determined and intelligent person.&nbsp; Funnily enough, I don&rsquo;t think any of us asked her what she used to do.&nbsp; I think because she is so much in the present - it didn&rsquo;t occur to us.&nbsp; As she took my arm, I sensed the strength in her - not physical strength; but strength of will and clarity and determination.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">At the top of the stairs, we passed a large banner, red and cheerful with &ldquo;Blizzard 2010&rdquo; and &ldquo;Thank You&rdquo; on it.&nbsp; All over the banner were little messages written by the residents to the staff.&nbsp; The Washington area recently had about 5 ft of snow.&nbsp; Overnight.&nbsp; The staff came in, through snowdrifts and ice.&nbsp; One of the servers walked several miles to get there because he wanted to make sure the elderly people he cared for were ok.&nbsp; Many staff stayed overnight.&nbsp; Everybody mucked in.&nbsp; The messages on the banner were about that.&nbsp; </span><p /><span style="font-size: medium;">Oh, and the early dinner.&nbsp; It turns out that there are rules that apply to High School students and the hours and times they are allowed to work.&nbsp; By starting dinner at 4pm and running till 7pm, it means that students can work and finish at the right time.&nbsp; And, as one of our hosts said &ldquo;Lots of us like to eat early once we get a bit older.&rdquo;</span><p /><br /></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis???s ???surprise??? on Saturday last was to go to a massive gated complex for ???seniors???, meet their Ukelele Group and play with them and for them. But we didn???t know that before we got there; just that Lloyd had to bring his uke and I was ask...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Mar 08 14:54:25 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[mercpol]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Mon Mar 08 15:18:37 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Mon Mar 08 15:18:37 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[This made me remember this song that Lloyd played a year or so ago - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BQjNrOjLAeU. So I played it, and I grinned, and I am still grinning. :)]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Mon Mar 08 17:07:59 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Mon Mar 08 17:07:59 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Wonderful story, thank you!]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Tue Mar 09 07:33:02 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Mar 09 07:33:02 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Good to hear Lloyds years at drama school have not been wasted. although am disappointed he didn't give them his audition piece as an added extra. Isn't music a wonderful thing, isn't there such power in the language of music and the camaraderie of it's community - a perfect accompaniement to a social media mission such as Tuttle2Tex. Singing for your early dinner, wonder what you'd have to do for a nights B&amp;B at the Waldorf?]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Mar 11 18:58:40 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Mar 11 18:58:40 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Thank you so much for your wonderful comments - I've also had messages on Twitter about this post. It was very hard to write; and I'm very grateful for the feedback. Brian]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Daily Story Digest #2</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/daily-story-digest-2</link>	<pubDate>Wed Jul 28 07:46:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/daily-story-digest-2</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>These stories originally went out by e-mail - if you'd like to join the list and get a nugget every weekday you can <a href="http://eepurl.com/GcpJ">sign-up here</a></p><p>??</p><p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4419908154"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4023/4419908154_e604312897_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"All part of the story"</span><p /> I was so pleased when <a href="http://heathertaylor.co.uk/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Heather Taylor</a> confirmed she'd be coming on this trip.?? I developed a huge artist's crush on her soon after she came to Tuttle - she is always *doing* stuff, making beautiful things?? - she had to rush off because she was screening her <a href="http://heathertaylor.co.uk/content/view/116/117/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">latest documentary</a>, no she couldn't be here next week because she was reading??<a href="http://heathertaylor.co.uk/content/view/39/59/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;"> her poetry</a> to an excited audience in Serbia.<p /> You can hear Heather talking a week or so before the trip <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/10-days-til-tuttle2texas-my-thoughts-and-than-0" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">on this audioboo</a><p /> Heather decided early on that her contribution to Tuttle2Texas would include making a documentary film of the trip.?? Now the planning instinct of the film-maker can clash with the free and easy social artist's spirit of improvisation.?? "Ooh look at this shiny thing!" - "Yes, but could we just walk over here again to get a long shot?"<p />The compromise was "It's all part of the story" - whenever something happened that wasn't in the original plan (the plan that I didn't write down you understand, the made-up plan that I kept rattling around in my head) it became "part of the story" and whenever I had a teenage strop because we needed to wait for like a whole minute and a half for Michelle to catch up with the camera gear, I restored my sanity by reminding myself that it was "all part of the story"<p />And for those who are wondering when, exactly this whole story is going to get going... be patient, this is all important stuff.?? <p /><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jamescridland/2375087492/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2253/2375087492_022e9e31ae_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Terminal 5 is pretty"</span><p /> Though clearly not pretty enough for me to take a picture when I arrived at LHR on the morning of 2nd March.?? I was more interested at the time in getting to take my ukulele onto the plane as a second piece of carry-on luggage.?? The lady at check-in seemed doubtful and worried me further by telling me there was an added security screening for flights into the US.?? I had visions of Darrin (that's the name of my smaller, black Les Paul-ish uke) being dismantled or simply smashed to pieces by over-zealous guardians of the nation's safety.?? She urged me to get in as quickly as possible.<p />Well I needn't have worried.?? The?? ukulele has magical charming properties which combine well with my new-found "bearded charisma".???? Photographers might be easily mistaken for terrorists, but honestly, who's going to suspect a ukulele player with facial hair??? Nonetheless I passed the time in the queue trying to remember the chords to "<a href="http://media.libsyn.com/media/perfectpath/palms090820.mp3" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Down among the sheltering palms</a>" in case I was challenged to actually play.<p /> So I made it to the gate much earlier than I expected and had time to soak up what a pleasant air-side experience it is.?? I tweeted the same and had an almost instant response from the Heathrow twitter team saying they liked it too.?? I was early, but there was no sight of Heather and Michelle.?? I reflected (quietly, to myself) that this was the first time I'd ever travelled with women before who'd been comfortable turning up at the airport later than me.?? Then the flight was called and I still couldn't see them.?? What if we'd done all that preparation and then I ended up going on my own?<p />(photo credit: <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jamescridland/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">James Cridland</a>)<p /><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4786177254/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4118/4786177254_e8aca0e001_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /> <span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Somewhere over Nova Scotia"</span><p />The picture above is from the day before we left when I was packing away all the goodies that Nokia and Canon had provided me with to help document the trip.?? I had a <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nokia_N900" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Nokia N900</a> (with which the photo was taken) a <a href="http://europe.nokia.com/find-products/mini-laptops" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">3G Notebook</a> and a set of <a href="http://www.nokia.com/microsites/bh-905" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">noise cancelling earphones</a>.?? From Canon I had a <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canon_EOS_500D" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">500D</a>, though unfortunately I had no lens for it until the next day when Mike lent me his.?? (It's still sitting on my desk by the way Mike... I haven't forgotten, really!)<p />So the first few hours of the flight, I spent picking over this kit, trying to work out how I was going to use it all, wondering how easy it was going to be to get a US sim card for the notebook and the phone and whether it would all work.?? Also cursing the multitude of power adapters I needed.?? You can see from the photo that one of the Nokia devices came with a European plug on it, so I would need a Euro -&gt; US adapter when I arrived.?? I've since seen those lovely multi-adapters that you can stick anything into anything with, but that's for next time.?? Also in the photo, if you squint hard, up at the top you can catch a glimpse of my bottom bookshelf.?? Yes, that really is a book on LOGO next to "The C Programming Language" next to something on PHP &amp; MySQL and then along a bit a nice one on CP/M Assembly Language.<p />About an hour and a half before landing at the most boring part of the flight, after I'd tried everything out thoroughly and failed to have a nap, I made my first <a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/102161-somewhere-near-nova-scotia-i-guess" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">queued upload Audioboo</a> containing the phrase "I'm really excited" delivered in possibly the most deadpan way ever.<p /> PS Oh yeah, of course Heather and Michelle made the flight, what on earth were you worried about? :)<p /><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4401502943/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2791/4401502943_e25a57e996_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /> <span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Hello Boston!"</span><p />Some short shenanigans before we get out into the city.?? Immigration is weird going into the states.?? Why??? Because the guys on the desk speak Engl-ish and you get to have a chat with them.?? This is not like popping across the channel when you just get a cursory, bored glance from the French border guard type and anyway I know I have a right to wander within the EU.?? Here they could really say "No, sorry, you can't come in."?? I know it's not likely, and the ukulele and bearded charisma do help enormously, but y'know, it would be a pain in the bum to have to fly all the way back at this stage.<p />Plus I knew <a href="http://blarmcast.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Dana</a> was waiting for me on the other side.?? And that was going to be weird - we'd been "seeing each other" in a bizarre long-distance internet-enabled way since December, but this was first time face to face, same time-zone and everything..?? And it was weird.?? She ran away from me.?? Then I ran away from her. We slowly worked our way next to each other and exchanged some tentative touches.?? There may have been a kiss.?? It's all a bit blurry. <p />It gets blurrier when we're outside trying to talk to <a href="http://twitter.com/keramurphy" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Kera</a> from <a href="http://www.techsuperpowers.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">TSP</a> via twitter. She's coming to pick us up in an SUV apparently, but none of us can quite agree on what one of those looks like.?? Finally we find the poor girl and we let her drive us away from Logan Airport and around Boston's baffling traffic system (Ooh! Charles River. Aah! Fenway Park!) me sitting quietly with four women who all really do like to talk, a lot, to <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/were-doing-tuttle-boston-on-march-3rd" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">our home for the next couple of days.</a> ?? <p /> <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4419907056"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2743/4419907056_161dbb13fa_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Dr Weinberger, I presume(?)"</span><p />  I hate jetlag.?? Who doesn't??? In particular, though it undermines my predeliction for flying by the seat of my pants.?? I can't.?? I don't have all my faculties.?? I make mistakes that I would normally see coming and cut off at the pass.<p />  I first heard of <a href="http://www.hyperorg.com/blogger" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">David Weinberger</a> when <a href="http://www.euansemple.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Euan Semple</a> introduced me to blogging in 2002.?? David was one of the authors of the <a href="http://cluetrain.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Cluetrain Manifesto</a> which Euan was blabbing on about and the fact that these guys were writing on the internet, like nearly every day, just posting what they thought and were doing with nobody else involved in deciding whether it should be published.?? It's what saved me from a life of managing corporate intranets.<p />  So, a year ago, when I saw that he was <a href="http://www.hyperorg.com/blogger/tag/2b2k/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">writing a new book</a> on the changes in our attitudes to expertise and knowledge in a highly networked world, I sent him details of the <a href="http://tuttleclub.wordpress.com/2009/07/15/our-first-consulting-gig/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Tuttle Consulting gig</a> we did as an example of how I think we're making use of networked knowledge in a new way.?? I then followed this up with a suggestion that we meet while we were in Boston to see whether we could help any further.<p />  We sat in the <a href="http://www.techsuperpowers.com/digilounge" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">TSP DigiLounge</a> and chatted for about an hour.?? Well, actually what happened was I rambled on through my jetlag about Tuttle for an hour and David typed copious notes.?? Then, after Heather had interviewed him, we had a little "learning experience" by asking a Berkman fellow to sign a non-creative-commons release form.?? We further trod on his toes (at the other end of the privacy spectrum)?? by releasing an audioboo of our conversation instantly.?? Ouch!?? Many apologies ensued, but it was a timely reminder that we weren't at home among those who know and already trust us.?? And it helped us to quickly clarify our approach to content licensing and checking permissions *before* capture.?? Just what you need when your body *knows* it's mid-afternoon, but everyone around you is still having breakfast.<p />  On a good note, David was pleased to find that our meeting was taking place in an Apple repair shop, so we left him talking about some problem with his macbook while we went out into the snow to cross the river to Cambridge.</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[These stories originally went out by e-mail - if you'd like to join the list and get a nugget every weekday you can sign-up here "All part of the story" I was so pleased when Heather Taylor confirmed she'd be coming on this trip. I developed a hug...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Jul 28 07:46:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name>daily-story-digest-2</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>SXSWi in 2010 via oh I don't know loads of places</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/sxswi-in-2010-via-oh-i-dont-know-loads-of-pla</link>	<pubDate>Sun Jan 17 04:11:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/sxswi-in-2010-via-oh-i-dont-know-loads-of-pla</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/3349666913/" title="homage to wankergirl by Lloyd Davis, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3633/3349666913_25d00812f8_m.jpg" align="right" height="180" alt="homage to wankergirl" width="240" /></a>So here's my poorly thought-out, unplanned, half-baked, undetailed, but totally awesome idea for the Spring of 2010.</p><p>I'll be attending <a href="http://sxsw.com">SXSWi</a> in Austin, Texas again.  My <a href="http://panelpicker.sxsw.com/ideas/view/4544">panel was not picked</a>, but emotion aside all that means is that I'll have to pay $blah or so for a ticket. So I'm definitely still going to go - it's just well, you know, <a href="http://www.broadstuff.com/archives/1612-SXSW-the-Spice-Girl-Cometh.html">too lovely and awesome</a> not to.</p><p>Last year we flew over a few days before and had some holiday time hanging out and getting acclimatimed and then flew back the day after interactive closed.</p><p>This time I want to take it a bit more gently.  Here are the bare bones of the evil plan, which I'd prefer to do with a gang of tuttle-istas if we can find ways of funding it:</p><p>1.  Find the shortest flight to North America possible (does that mean least-polluting? I don't know but that seems like a good aim to bear in mind) and fly at least a week before SXSWi opens ie arrive March 5th at the latest.</p><p>2.  Devise a series of train journeys from wherever I land, down to Austin, preferably going via New Orleans to visit that good friend of Tuttle, <a href="http://www.taylordavidson.com/writing/">Mr Taylor Davidson</a> and see how his Crescent City adventure is panning out.  Yes, you read that right, train journeys.  I understand that the US train system is not quite as beautiful or efficient as <a href="http://perfectpath.co.uk/2009/08/18/interrail-day-7/">its European sisters</a>.  However, train travel rocks, it just does.</p><p>3.  At stopping places throughout the journey hold <a href="http://perfectpath.co.uk/2009/07/09/what-i-did-at-rebootbritain/">Human-scale Conversation</a> sessions with local people talking about differences between US and British culture - not trying to solve anything particularly, just getting the subject out on the table and seeing what comes of it.  There will be heavy-duty social reporting of these conversations. Note that the format has been refined since July with some extra flourishes - <a href="http://digitalcitizen.posterous.com/social-planet-conversations">this is how I introduced something like it at the Tuttle/Counterpoint event in December</a>.</p><p>4.  Once in Austin, continue to hold Human-scale Conversation sessions on the same subject and present <a href="http://fionacullinan.com/2009/03/hashtag-kebab-aka-%E2%80%98the-art-of-conference-jacking%E2%80%99/">#kebab-style</a> what we heard, found, learned, saw along the way.</p><p>5.  Make our way back to the east coast overland again, putting together a documentary film from the footage shot during the first part of the trip, so that we have something ready to show when we get back to London.</p><p>Howzat grab ya?</p><p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/3356939241/" title="150320091095 by Lloyd Davis, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3635/3356939241_5de80e6f57_m.jpg" height="180" alt="150320091095" width="240" /></a></p><p>Here's 8 ways you can help (and I'm sure you'll come up with more)</p><p>1. Tell me how you'd improve on the plans and make them even more exciting.</p><p>2. Tell me why this is oh so very wrong-headed, misguided and stupid (I won't listen very much, but I'd rather ask you for this than you just provide it out of the blue!).</p><p>3. Help me work out rough costings for each variation.</p><p>4. Provide money (just loads of it, regardless of the costs!)</p><p>5. Suggest routes and interesting stopover points, tell me why you think it's interesting.</p><p>6. Volunteer to tag along and tell me how we'd pay for that.</p><p>7. Find other supporters with more money than time who'd like to see this happen.</p><p>8. Introduce me to sponsors who might provide help in terms of cash, food, shelter, transport as well as social reporting equipment.</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[So here's my poorly thought-out, unplanned, half-baked, undetailed, but totally awesome idea for the Spring of 2010. I'll be attending SXSWi in Austin, Texas again. My panel was not picked, but emotion aside all that means is that I'll have to pay...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Jan 17 04:11:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Sun Jan 17 04:24:25 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Sun Jan 17 04:24:25 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[This was originally posted on Perfect Path, go there to see more comments... http://perfectpath.co.uk/2009/12/30/sxswi-in-2010-via-oh-i-dont-know-loads-of-places/]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Boston to NYC - our first train ride</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/boston-to-nyc-our-first-train-ride</link>	<pubDate>Thu Mar 04 13:59:39 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/boston-to-nyc-our-first-train-ride</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">Woah, this is a shaky old train. Difficult to type because the tray is up close to me but anyway it&#39;s better than having it on my lap. The Amtrak trains are like big tin cans, they look like they&#39;re just slats of aluminium stapled together. And this ride south out of Boston feels like it too. Everything rattles and judders.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">It&#39;s snowing outside and we&#39;re getting out of the city and into more countryside space. We just stopped at a station called Route 128 ??? the train station is named after a road? OK it&#39;s also University Park.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">I&#39;m unreasonably excited about being on an American train. I&#39;ve lived around London and commuted for 20 years. I know what trains are like, and I&#39;m used to the experience. However, this feels weirdly different. The conductor we met was friendly and um, American, confidently in charge, rather than being officious and jobsworthy.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">I realised what it was that I was getting excited about - American rail reminds me of Casey Jones. Casey Jones was to me an exciting and exotic part of my television childhood. Plucky Alan Ladd driving a train regardless of bandits and rockfalls and anything else that might have gotten in his way He always got through. He just did. Anyway he wasn&#39;t a train driver he was an Engineer ??? American usage, I blame the literal German immigrants ??? he drives and engine so he must be an engineer. Maybe that&#39;s what we originally meant by engineer too. Maybe i&#39;m jetlagged and I&#39;m writing stuff that I ordinarily wouldn&#39;t let out of my head. And of course now I&#39;ve also got the theme to the show stuck in my head, squeezing out Chatanooga Choo Choo - ???Casey Jones, steamin&#39; and a&#39; rollin&#39;???</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Woah, this is a shaky old train. Difficult to type because the tray is up close to me but anyway it's better than having it on my lap. The Amtrak trains are like big tin cans, they look like they're just slats of aluminium stapled together. And th...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Mar 04 13:59:39 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[boofulls]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email> susandavis45@hotmail.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Mar 04 14:48:50 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Mar 04 14:48:50 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[ I told you never go down to the end of town etc and there you are on a tin train wobbling about in America]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Party. Tonight. 23rd February</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/party-tonight-23rd-february</link>	<pubDate>Tue Feb 23 00:44:37 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="c4cc"><![CDATA[c4cc]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="fun"><![CDATA[fun]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="fundraising"><![CDATA[fundraising]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/party-tonight-23rd-february</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It's one week today till we start our trip in Boston.</p><p>We're having a party this evening from 5.30pm until we get tired and need to tidy up. &nbsp;Everyone's welcome, but please <a href="http://t2t-fundraiser.eventbrite.com" target="_blank">sign up here</a> to let us know you're coming. &nbsp;We're at the <a href="http://www.creativecollaboration.org.uk" target="_blank">Centre for Creative Collaboration</a>, 16 Acton St, London WC1X 9NG - y'know the place we've been doing Tuttle for a few weeks.</p><p>There'll be ukulele, poetry, folk guitar, something we don't really know about yet, and other things that will no doubt be entertaining but haven't yet been confirmed. &nbsp;Come and do your thing and if you have anything you'd like to donate as a raffle prize that'll get people buying tickets, do let us know and bring it along.</p><p>No matter what, in potluck style, please bring something to nibble on, something to swig and someone with deep pockets and a weakness for giving money to starving social artists.</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[It's one week today till we start our trip in Boston. We're having a party this evening from 5.30pm until we get tired and need to tidy up. Everyone's welcome, but please sign up here to let us know you're coming. We're at the Centre for Creative ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Tue Feb 23 00:44:37 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Whose stupid idea (redux)</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/whose-stupid-idea-redux</link>	<pubDate>Mon Apr 05 07:05:26 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/whose-stupid-idea-redux</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; margin-top: 8px; margin-right: 8px; margin-bottom: 8px; margin-left: 8px; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"> <p>I&#39;m on the floor.</p><p>I&#39;m actually lying on the floor of the train carriage. ??In the baggage section at the back. ??I just filmed out of the back window as we left Austin and now after a couple of hours or so down to San Antonio we&#39;re on a 7 hour layover there in the sidings. ??I can&#39;t sleep next to this guy that I&#39;ve just met. Is this because I&#39;m a soft English scaredy-cat or because I have justifiable reservations about falling asleeep on a train, thousands of miles from home next to a complete stranger. ??Would you? ??You would? Well I think you&#39;re weird.</p> <p>A crazy spanish-speaking lady is talking to a girl who got on in Austin. ??The lady has a lot to say. ??The girl is just smiling. ??The lady isn&#39;t going to sleep in her seat she&#39;s going to sleep on the floor. ??And I decide to copy her.</p> <p>Where did all this start? ??Why am I doing it anyway? ??Where do any ideas begin? ??We don&#39;t really know, do we? ??In my experience, every time we say it was this moment when it came together there&#39;s always some pre-cursor, some other thought or conversation that can legitimately lay claim to leading up to this one.</p> <p>So we just have to grab at one. ??I don&#39;t think it&#39;s too much of a stretch to take this back to march last year, when I returned from my first SXSW, full of excitement and inspiration and induced enthusiasm simply from being in the presence of so many excitable American entrepreneurs. ??but yes, back then I was thinking of how I could get back to Austin. ??I had to borrow money in order to pay my hotel bill and that was not something I was comfortable with. ??and so while I wasn&#39;t giving it much thought, I had decided that I would want to go, but needed help from some other source. ??I tried first to get a panel slot. ??I proposed, got support from the community and it ll seemed well received but then in each of the rounds of announcements of who was speaking I found myself understanding that it wasn&#39;t going to be me. ??And so I started looking for other ways to make it happen anyway. ??and of course I started to talk about it. ??I started to socialise the idea, sound it out with people. ??&quot;I wonder how we could do this...&quot; Which is, by the way, exactly the same process that we went through with both Tuttle itself and Tuttle Consultingl. ??I don&#39;t know at what point it became a thing. ??A real thing that we were trying to do. ??but I think it was December 3rd when we presented all the work for Counterpoint and we were all sitting round afterwards.</p> <p>Was that Brian&#39;s birthday? ??I think it was, yes. ??anyhow we did talk about it then. ??I confessed it, as a half-formed idea, that we should see whether we could fly to an eastern part of North America and then find our way across by train - surely that must be doable. ??And lots of people, of course, said &quot;yes, yes we&#39;d like to do that&quot; ??We, as a group, were full of &quot;what&#39;s next&quot; energy. ??The thrill of having delivered and the excitement of seeing another project come alive. ??And then, like it&#39;s elder siblings, it needed to percolate for a while. ??Over Christmas I decided that it was something I wanted to do and that I wanted to pull other people in.</p> <p>So naturally, I wrote a blog post.</p> </div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I'm on the floor.I'm actually lying on the floor of the train carriage. In the baggage section at the back. I just filmed out of the back window as we left Austin and now after a couple of hours or so down to San Antonio we're on a 7 hour layover ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Apr 05 07:05:26 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Dawn in Georgia (DC to ATL)</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/dawn-in-georgia-dc-to-atl</link>	<pubDate>Wed Mar 10 13:39:16 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/dawn-in-georgia-dc-to-atl</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='164' poster='http://getfile6.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/1UT7Cz8YRN7CJDtsoVSUft9LUN26MA2KoWzGm6HwgjpzsQMWutSQqBBE24ll/early_morning_georgia.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile4.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/1UT7Cz8YRN7CJDtsoVSUft9LUN26MA2KoWzGm6HwgjpzsQMWutSQqBBE24ll/early_morning_georgia.mp4'></source></video></div><p>dark to start but stick with it...</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[dark to start but stick with it...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Mar 10 13:39:16 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>My Maryland &quot;surprise&quot;</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/my-maryland-surprise-0</link>	<pubDate>Wed Mar 10 14:07:31 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/my-maryland-surprise-0</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[I hadn&#39;t read Brian&#39;s post about this when I recorded the following boo. ??If I had, I might have been even more emotional about it...<p /><div><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=My+maryland+surprise&amp;mp3Time=03.28pm+09+Mar+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F104089-my-maryland-surprise.mp3&amp;mp3Author=Lloyddavis&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F104089-my-maryland-surprise" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/104089-my-maryland-surprise.mp3">http://audioboo.fm/boos/104089-my-maryland-surprise.mp3</a>">Listen!</object></div> <p /><div>We won&#39;t have video of the session for a while because it was shot on the big grown-ups camera and those of us who normally whip out our little cameras at ??the first sign of excitement where otherwise overcome. ??But to give people some idea of what they&#39;re like here&#39;s a clip of the Riderwood Ukes from YouTube</div> <p /><div><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/EvmeDxQNYbE?wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen frameborder="0" height="417" width="500"></iframe><br /></div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I hadn't read Brian's post about this when I recorded the following boo. If I had, I might have been even more emotional about it...http://audioboo.fm/boos/104089-my-maryland-surprise.mp3">Listen! We won't have video of the session for a while bec...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Mar 10 14:07:31 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Hanging around outside Whole Foods in Austin</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/hanging-around-outside-whole-foods-in-austin</link>	<pubDate>Wed Jun 16 11:17:59 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/hanging-around-outside-whole-foods-in-austin</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/FRJ0Be-VZvo?wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen frameborder="0" height="417" width="500"></iframe></div><p />Just found this snippet - notable mostly for the grackle soundtrack. As it happens I was waiting for @irinaslutsky whom I&#39;d never met before to come along and pick me up in a taxi. ??Much better than another night when I stood on the opposite corner trying to hail a cab and got pooped on by the birds in the trees above.]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Just found this snippet - notable mostly for the grackle soundtrack. As it happens I was waiting for @irinaslutsky whom I'd never met before to come along and pick me up in a taxi. Much better than another night when I stood on the opposite corner...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Jun 16 11:17:59 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Daily Story Digest #3</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/daily-story-digest-3</link>	<pubDate>Wed Jul 28 08:43:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/daily-story-digest-3</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To get these nuggets as daily updates in your mailbox <a href="http://eepurl.com/GcpJ">sign-up here</a><p /><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4403688969/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4047/4403688969_5fe7141f00_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /> <span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"To the Massachusetts Institute of Technology"</span><p /> Cultural dissonance #1: Taxi drivers who don't know where they're going - no really they don't, you have to tell them, they're not just faking it because they don't want to go south of the river this time of night.&nbsp; In London of course it happens too, but there you just wait for another one (or <a href="http://twitter.com/tweetalondoncab" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">@tweetalondoncab</a> !).&nbsp; but it's snowing, you have jetlag, you don't really know where your going either, you've just upset an internet blue blood - can't we jut get there?<p />  No, tantrums won't work, that'll just get your luggage thrown in the snow.&nbsp; Deep breaths and we can work this out together...<p />  And the reward for patience and perseverance is #TuttleMIT - we're at the MIT Sloan Business School and we're drinking coffee and chatting with <a href="http://twitter.com/CambridgeCarrie" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">people</a> we've only met before on the internet and suddenly the spirit of Tuttle is there.&nbsp; Wow.&nbsp; It works, it just does.&nbsp; And then <a href="http://twitter.com/philwyman" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">people arrive that we weren't expecting</a> and we didn't know.&nbsp; But they know us, well, they at least they're curious enough to travel for an hour through the snow to find out if we're for real.&nbsp; And we're making new connections and having interesting conversations - about Bangor and Haiti and Kazoos - hurrah! It's home from home.<p /> <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/stevegarfield/4406365590"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2789/4406365590_7e9cb821b3_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Livestreams and Ukulele"</span><p />  In the evening, we did #TuttleBoston in the lovely DigiLounge.&nbsp; Mike and Kera did us proud with food and drink for all.&nbsp; Brian tucked himself away in a corner and then proudly announced that we were livestreaming to the internetz - he then carried on a great tuttle tradition of talking to people somewhere else in the world while attending a face to face meetup.&nbsp; I think we all had a go at manning the live stream, with the bizarre thing being that practically everyone watching was in the UK and it was 7pm EST/midnight GMT when we started.&nbsp; We also witnessed the emergence of a new livestreaming double act in the shape of Heather and <a href="http://stevegarfield.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Steve Garfield</a>.&nbsp; Fortunately for the cultural edification of future generations, the whole thing <a href="http://www.ustream.tv/recorded/5166245" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">is archived here</a>.<p />  This was one of the things I wanted to really test out on this trip, whether people would come out on a snowy evening in March to meet some crazy English (OK and Irish) and Canadian folk,&nbsp; just because they'd seen people talking about it on Twitter - yup, people are just as funny in America as they are in London!<p />  It was also time to try out the "thank you" present of entertaining them with my singing and ukulele - you can hear how it went down on <a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/102265-lloyd-entertaining-the-tuttleboston-crew-tuttle2texas" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Heather's audioboo</a>.&nbsp; All too soon it was time for bed, we had a train to catch in the morning.<p />  (photo credit cc <a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/2.0/deed.en_GB" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">by-nc-sa</a> <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/stevegarfield/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Steve Garfield</a>)<p /> <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4475899987"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2706/4475899987_18c88fb47a_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"All Aboard!"</span><p />  So just as I was starting to feel I knew where I was and that things were OK and working as expected, we throw ourselves off another cliff.&nbsp; It's time to get our first train.&nbsp; Why is this difficult?&nbsp; I did a 40 minute train commute from Surrey into London pretty much every day for about 15 years.&nbsp; I've travelled on all the mainlines in the UK and delved into some of the most obscure branches too.&nbsp; I spent a couple of weeks last year<a href="http://perfectpath.co.uk/tag/interrail/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;"> travelling around Europe</a> on an Interrail pass.&nbsp; I know how to travel on trains, I like travelling on trains, why am I restless and irritable waiting for this Amtrak from Boston down to New York City?<p />  Because I don't know what I don't know.&nbsp; My fear of making an awful faux-pas is heightened.&nbsp; Have I got the right ticket?&nbsp; What are those <a href="http://www.amtrak.com/servlet/ContentServer/Page/1241267362176/1237405732517" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Red Caps</a> up to?&nbsp; Do they expect an extortionate tip for taking your luggage to the train?&nbsp; Will they set fire to it in disgust if you give them a couple of bucks instead of five?&nbsp; How do we know which is our train?&nbsp; Do we really need to be here 30 minutes before departure?&nbsp; What will happen if we aren't? How does queueing work in this country?&nbsp; Am I in the way?&nbsp; What don't I know that is suddenly and unexpectedly going to get me into trouble?<p />  Then it hits me.&nbsp; I am one of those people that, back in London, I stand behind and tut at. I am a foreigner who hasn't a clue and I forgive every stupid Italian I've ever wanted to strangle, every Yank whose baseball cap I wanted to stuff in their loud mouths, every Yorkshireman that I've wanted to scream at "WAKE UP! LOOK WHERE YOU'RE GOING".&nbsp;&nbsp; I am filled with forgiveness for them all and for myself and I'm ready to just go and see how it all works.<p />  OMG, they really do shout "All Aboooooaaaard!"<p /> <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4422022065"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4052/4422022065_2cbeb5a882_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Next Stop: Big Apple"</span><p />  "The Amtrak trains are like big tin cans, they look like they're just slats of aluminium stapled together."&nbsp; <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/boston-to-nyc-our-first-train-ride" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">I wrote as we juddered our way</a> down along the New England coastline.&nbsp; Of course they're not.&nbsp; They're actually slats of aluminum stapled together.<p />  This first leg reminded me how difficult it is to actually write while&nbsp; you're on a train.&nbsp; When rushing around a city it feels like the train time's going to be a great time to "get all this down" - actually, there's still plenty going on that you don't want to miss.&nbsp; What does the countryside look like between Boston and New York?&nbsp; I realise that there are lots of big empty chunks in my conceptual map of the United States that are going to get filled on this trip - I knew Boston was going to be a little Good Will Hunting, and I expected NYC to be Kojak and Starsky and Hutch but what's inbetween?&nbsp;&nbsp; Well it turns out, for a British Rail traveller, that it's quite like that bit of the South Wales coast beyond Cardiff - Port Talbot and Swansea, tired old industrial ports and factories interspersed with breathtaking natural beauty - not lush mountainsides of course, still gorgeous, but different, American.<p />  Then before we know it, and just as I was ready for a little snooze, there's the island of Manhattan our of the right hand window.&nbsp; Rarely photographed from this angle, and I can see why - it didn't inspire me to leap out of my seat and snap away.&nbsp; Approaching from the north-east by rail doesn't capture it's best side, but yes, that's definitely New York.<p />  <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4422814520"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4001/4422814520_c4b5a39c93_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p /><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Welcome to 7th Avenue!"</span><p />  So this is my postcard-y shot from the <a href="http://www.bartleboglehegarty.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">BBH offices</a> down towards the bottom of 6th Avenue.&nbsp; Don't talk to me about postcards.&nbsp; if you want to hear my postcards from New York story, talk to <a href="http://blarmcast.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Dana</a> - she tells it with great relish and glee...<p />  Anyway, back to getting off the train.&nbsp; Penn Station isn't really like any station in London.&nbsp; I guess its closest British counterpart would be <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Birmingham_New_Street_railway_station" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">New St in Birmingham</a> in that it's dirty,&nbsp; mostly underground and you come out into a tired shopping centre full of crazy people whose accent you can't understand.&nbsp; Classy.&nbsp; Which&nbsp; reminds me of Big Cultural Difference #2 - the significantly larger number of people clearly suffering from mental health problems and living (or at least begging) on the streets.&nbsp; My assumption is that the NHS tidies much of this away - it's not that we're any less crazy, just that we can get our drugs for free.<p />  My senses already heightened by men wearing two overcoats tied up with string, I emerged onto 7th Avenue ready to see what the isle of Manhattan had to offer.&nbsp; Well the first thing was a couple arguing - not the sort of low-level passive aggressive bickering you see from couples in IKEA - no, full on, sassy. "you ain't nevah gonna see yo' children agin mofo" screaming match - just marching straight through the tourists.&nbsp; Tired, jetlagged, uptight and suffering from an imagination overfed with way too many nights under the blankets reading <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Amazing_Spider-Man_%28comic_book%29" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Amazing Spiderman</a> as a youngster, I really didn't know whether to laugh out loud or hit the deck because the shooting was going to start.&nbsp; So I looked to Dana.&nbsp; Who was laughing.&nbsp; Not at the couple but at me, for being such an out-of-towner.&nbsp;<p />  Oh New York!</p><p>EAVB_OOBYIKSCBU</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[To get these nuggets as daily updates in your mailbox sign-up here "To the Massachusetts Institute of Technology" Cultural dissonance #1: Taxi drivers who don't know where they're going - no really they don't, you have to tell them, they're not ju...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Jul 28 08:43:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name>daily-story-digest-3</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Social Art and Healthcare Metaphors</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/social-art-and-healthcare-metaphors</link>	<pubDate>Sun Feb 28 10:41:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Condon]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/social-art-and-healthcare-metaphors</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class='p_embed p_image_embed'><img alt="Ocad" height="320" src="http://getfile7.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/Jng0BL96O7mBiBXudlH3jlKnDo5sUDLpeZLeloeT72BtP7MscIchEKRTD6IU/OCAD.png" width="319" /></div></p><p>To the wonderful Ontario College of Art and Design for a seminar by Natalie Jeremijenko hosted by Greg van Alynstyne and his colleagues at the sLab of the OCAD (<a href="http://slab.ocad.ca/)">http://slab.ocad.ca/)</a>. <p /> The themes that emerged for me were about co-creation, collaboration and creativity. And the use of a well-known metaphor - that of healthcare, to explore how the 'health' of a neighbourhood can be improved by "Impatients" - who are unwilling to wait for 'the Man' to intervene through legislation. The use of the healthcare metaphor is interesting and, as participants pointed out, as well as the positive aspects of caring, nurturing, curing and well-being; there are also some potentially negative aspects related to the power relationships between clinicians and patients, the financially burdensome nature (some said 'broken' nature) of healthcare in developed countries and the fact that healthcare needs so much in terms of resources (both human and natural). Having said all that, treated carefully and not subject to everyone going into 'metaphor overdrive' - it's a helpful framework for thinking and is being used successfully in New York. <p />  I made an Audioboo yesterday thinking about the seminar and Natalie's approach: <p />  <object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=Outside+MaRS+discovery+district&amp;mp3Time=09.54am+26+Feb+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F100982-outside-mars-discovery-district.mp3&amp;mp3Author=brian_condon&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F100982-outside-mars-discovery-district" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/100982-outside-mars-discovery-district.mp3">Listen!</a></object><p /> I also made a liveblog in realtime during the event - this is here:</p><ul><li><strong>2:38 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Background to the event (from the sLAb Explorations site): <a href="http://bit.ly/9ILvAS">bit.ly<span class="bittip"><span><span><iframe name="bigurlframe" scrolling="no" class="bigurlframe" rel="" src="http://bit.ly/plugins/iframe?hashUrl=http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2F9ILvAS" frameborder="0"></iframe></span></span></span></a><p /><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>What happened at Copenhagen, what worked, what didn&rsquo;t, and most importantly &ndash; what now?</strong></span><p />Those who expected decisive agreements and large-scale governmental action from the recent Copenhagen negotiations are disappointed. However, now the emphasis falls on other strategies and technological opportunities we face to coordinate environmental movement, raise the standards of evidence and facilitate diverse responses to environmental challenges. How can distributed sensing and public publishing of data reveal this evidence, support local organizations and actions? How does Pachube &ndash; a kind of Facebook/YouTube for data &ndash; change the game? How can social networking be used in collective sense-making and lifestyle experiments to localize responsibility for environmental health? Is it the big opportunities &ndash; or not?</li><li><strong>2:43 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Greg Van Alystyne (<a href="http://gregvanalstyne.com/)">http://gregvanalstyne.com/)</a> introduces sLab - foresight and a combination of practitioners and academics.  It's about finding ways of collaborating. </li><li><strong>2:46 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Natalie's going to talk about how to aggregate and use data. </li><li><strong>2:47 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Greg introduces #sLab session on Post Copenhagen - what next? <a href="http://twitpic.com/15aelw">http://twitpic.com/15aelw</a></li><li><strong>2:47 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em>&nbsp;</li><li><strong>2:53 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em><span style="font-size: medium;"> <strong>Natalie Jeremijenko;</strong></span><br />About the Speaker [from the sLab site]: <p /><em>Natalie Jeremijenko is an artist whose background includes studies in biochemistry, physics, neuroscience and precision engineering. Jeremijenko is a recipient of the 2008-2009 Van Alen Institute-New York Prize Fellowship in Sustainable Cities and the Social Sciences, and was recently named one of the 40 most influential designers by I.D. Magazine. She is an artist not-in-residence at the Institute for the Future (IFTF) in Palo Alto. Jeremijenko directs the xDesign Environmental Health Clinic [<a href="http://www.nyu.edu/projects/xdesign/">http://www.nyu.edu/projects/xdesign/</a>] at NYU. Her work is described as experimental design, hence xDesign, as it explores opportunities presented by new technologies for non-violent social change. Her research centers on structures of participation in the production of knowledge and information, and the political and social possibilities (and limitations) of information and emerging technologies &mdash; mostly through public experiments.</em><p />Natalie explains that her approach is influenced by the work of John Dewey (he of the system) and his later thinking of exploration and experiment) she also cites a "Bauhaus" moment of involvement in partcipatory democracy.  The ideas of co-creation  and collaboration are also very important aspects of her approach.<p />An analysis of what pediatricians spend their time on in Manhattan - is that a significant number of the diseases they work on have a strong environmental component (air quality for example).</li><li><strong>2:57 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> But how do we make these kinds of issues globally relevant and through social media and citizen journalism make these things more visible and actionable.  [Shows a video and other examples]</li><li><strong>2:59 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Use a familiar script to highlight the issues - that's why the health services model is useful.  Not everyone needs to be an environmental activist to engage with the issues.</li><li><strong>3:01 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Natalie gives the example of water quality changes and the increased incidence of certain types of cancer.  They name tadpoles after local officials responsible for water quality and grow them in the same water that the official is responsible for [laughter].</li><li><strong>3:03 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> The activists take the tadpoles and introduce them to the officals they are named after  - and they take then tadpole walking.  Creating a kind of 'environmental commons'.  Tadpoles are about 3 orders of magnitude more sensitive than electronic sensors.</li><li><strong>3:06 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Another example is to use domestic mice to monitor environmental health factors - as mice share many things with us - air, water and food. They invented a mousetrap - that enabled mice to self-dose themselves (with stuff like prozac, vodka, zoloc). They take blood samples from the mice and samples of their droppings. An important aspect is that the mice are geographically limited - and so effects are locally verifiable.</li><li><strong>3:12 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> The idea is to find monitoring protocols that are simple, accessible and understandable at local level - and air quality is a good example of this.</li><li><strong>3:15 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> About 80% of Manhattan's carbon footprint is related to the energy use of buildings </li><li><strong>3:17 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> <br /> <object height="243" width="300"><param name="AllowScriptAccess" value="never" /><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/lr__R_tlaWA&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" /><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" /><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/lr__R_tlaWA&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" wmode="Transparent" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="243" width="300"></embed><param name="wmode" value="Transparent" /></object></li><li><strong>3:19 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> She covers the idea of the greenlight project - "You may not be able to use solar to run your drier or dishwasher but it can be very useful if you think about it the right way" it is also important to have a conceptual awareness of where the sun is. </li><li><strong>3:24 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> The idea of 'surgically' inserting low level trees and shrubs by putting plants in emergency vehicle parking spaces - they can recover quickly and for 99% of the time they are helping to 'cure' the environmental damage - this idea of low parks puts better air quality at the level of the stroller. </li><li><strong>3:26 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Habitat provisioning for butterflies in Manhattan - 3 species of butterfly landed on the No-Park within 15 minutes of it being installed. </li><li><strong>3:27 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> There is a strong focus on co-creation and collaboration in the development of these projects.  The term Impatient is used to describe the local people who get involved - because they don't want to wait for the 'official' solution to be done and they want to get on with it.</li><li><strong>3:30 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> <br /> <object height="243" width="300"><param name="AllowScriptAccess" value="never" /><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/1tpVg6ITSd0&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" /><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" /><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/1tpVg6ITSd0&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" wmode="Transparent" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="243" width="300"></embed><param name="wmode" value="Transparent" /></object></li><li><strong>3:31 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> The Urban Space station is an open source project - and the video is a scale version done in Spain in 2009.</li><li><strong>3:36 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Using solar chimneys to extract carbon black from the atmosphere, extract amorphous carbon and turig it into pencil leads in the Bronx Manhattan and New Jersey.</li><li><strong>3:42 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> <br /> <object height="243" width="300"><param name="AllowScriptAccess" value="never" /><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/O2uHva6kKFY&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" /><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" /><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/O2uHva6kKFY&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" wmode="Transparent" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="243" width="300"></embed><param name="wmode" value="Transparent" /></object></li><li><strong>3:42 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> This is the video for the No-Parks project.</li><li><strong>3:44 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> As water quality improves, and we create more urban green spaces we simultaneously improve our environment and encourage non-human species to 'colonise' our places - this is good for all of us.</li><li><strong>3:48 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Move from a position of trying to find out what you can do rather than over-focus on what you can't do.    For example the idea of nutritionally valid food for fish or other aquatic creatures (rather than white bread).  This food can also be configured to cause the fish to process the heavy metals in a way that 'fixes' them and they fall into the silt - and are no longer bio-avialbale to the animals ind plants in the system.</li><li><strong>3:53 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> <br /> <object height="182" width="300"><param name="AllowScriptAccess" value="never" /><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/51qTAbLiziI&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" /><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" /><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/51qTAbLiziI&amp;hl=en_US&amp;fs=1&amp;" wmode="Transparent" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="182" width="300"></embed><param name="wmode" value="Transparent" /></object></li><li><strong>3:53 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> She's talking about the Icon Aircraft and the Strap-on flight simulator - as a form of playful engagement.</li><li><strong>3:57 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> Re-imagining urban mobility using the Strap-on flight simulator - and using some of these ideas to change our relationships with natural systems. </li><li><strong>4:00 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> <em>Question - on models of collaboration with Natural History as an example in 19th C, Astronomy from different locations across the globe.  Protocols are established; the idea of the person as an observer  -and the Map of the Sky produced.  In 20th C we had SETI@home and folding.it.  Can you have the same kind of rigourous standardisation in your projects?</em></li><li><strong>4:04 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> She says that by using Pachube for example you can parametrise some of the measurements and data collection protocols.  [She's arguing that by standardising the protocols across wider areas you 'wash out' the ability to involve local people; they end up collecting data for some central authority that loses its relevance to them and which doesn't help understand the system effects at local level].  "You don't have to be a thinking person to work with SETI@home, you're just being a computer by using your spare capacity.</li><li><strong>4:05 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> The questioner mentions the idea of 'emancipatory technology' - that it's about access to these.</li><li><strong>4:07 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> <em>There is a case for serious science based on some data versus no data at all.  There is new thinking going on - say in the monitoring of air quality; quantity vs quality of data can help to limit errors through extent of data</em></li><li><strong>4:13 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> She's saying that the internet demands that we re-examine where the knowledge is in the system - and its probably not in the Library anymore.  It's in the community of practice and the people relationships.</li><li><strong>4:14 PM</strong>: <em>brian_condon</em> [That's the end of the seminar - there will be an xCamp session beginning at 1530 - I don't know whether that will be bloggable]</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[To the wonderful Ontario College of Art and Design for a seminar by Natalie Jeremijenko hosted by Greg van Alynstyne and his colleagues at the sLab of the OCAD (http://slab.ocad.ca/). The themes that emerged for me were about co-creation, collabor...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Feb 28 10:41:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>10 days til #tuttle2texas: my thoughts &amp; thanks</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/10-days-til-tuttle2texas-my-thoughts-and-than-0</link>	<pubDate>Sat Feb 20 12:53:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/10-days-til-tuttle2texas-my-thoughts-and-than-0</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F99493-10-days-til-tuttle2texas-my-thoughts-thanks.mp3&amp;mp3Author=Propgrl&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F99493-10-days-til-tuttle2texas-my-thoughts-thanks&amp;mp3Title=10+days+til+%23tuttle2texas%3A+my+thoughts+%26+thanks&amp;mp3Time=11.24am+20+Feb+2010" /></object></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sat Feb 20 12:53:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>It took a while to get out of Austin</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/it-took-a-while-to-get-out-of-austin</link>	<pubDate>Tue Jun 15 23:24:36 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/it-took-a-while-to-get-out-of-austin</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/tbHHZjb2O1w?wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen frameborder="0" height="417" width="500"></iframe><p /><div><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tbHHZjb2O1w"></a>In which our hero waits for a train and then gets on it. ??And stuff.</div> <p /><div>This is part 1 of oh I don&#39;t know how many yet of the final 36 hour journey from Austin to Los Angeles.??<p /></div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[In which our hero waits for a train and then gets on it. And stuff. This is part 1 of oh I don't know how many yet of the final 36 hour journey from Austin to Los Angeles.]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Tue Jun 15 23:24:36 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>First stop Boston</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/first-stop-boston</link>	<pubDate>Thu Mar 04 04:25:02 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/first-stop-boston</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[So actually we&#39;re just going to leave Boston in a couple of hours and I&#39;m realising that we&#39;ve put out very little so far - we&#39;ve been active on twitter, but the combination of jetlag, an overfilled schedule and unfamiliarity with the city, despite lovely help from Mike Oh &amp; Kera Murphy and the gang at TechSuperpowers has meant it&#39;s been really difficult to get some real writing done. ??<p /><div>Well that should be what the train journey&#39;s are for. ??In the meantime I&#39;m waking up in Boston again, it&#39;s cold, but not much colder than London has been and today we have no snow. ??</div><p /><div>To recap what we&#39;ve done as placeholders for longer reflections later:</div><p /><div>Last night we did #TuttleBoston at the digilounge we had lots of lovely people come along to cheer us on our way. ??We need some easy way of collating those people&#39;s details so that we can thank them and point you to them. ??I guess some of it is in eventbrite....</div> <p /><div>At lunchtime we were the guests of MIT at Venture Cafe in the Cambridge Innovation Center - great simple human-scale conversation and good to meet Carrie Stalder, Cyndi Hernandez, Michael Davies, Phil Wyman and Mary??<span style="font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; border-collapse: collapse; color: rgb(136, 136, 136);">Nykoruk and Peter Hirst joined us again. ??Carrie&#39;s plans for Venture Cafe - bringing entrepreneurs together to talk about &quot;stuff&quot; chimed very well with what we were thinking when we talked about a Social Media Cafe all those years ago.</span></div> <p /><div><span style="border-collapse: collapse;">Before lunch David Weinberger popped into the digilounge to hear about Tuttle &amp; Tuttle Consulting as part of research for his latest book - fascinating stuff about how our concept of knowledge ??is taking on the characteristics of the network. ??I told the too long version of the creation story - we could really have done with longer, but hey, we have e-mail! ??We also realised we&#39;d inadvertently put some inflexibility into the shooting of the documentary. ??Heather has standard copyright release forms because the film she will make is intended for TV and that will require all the rights to be nailed down old skool. ??Unsurprisingly, enlightened individuals like David are not so keen on being interviewed on camera and not having the result released under creative commons. ??Is fine. ??We now know there are two streams - content that will be free to use (we haven&#39;t agreed between us which licence is best to use btw - that might be a discussion for this upcoming train ride) ??and stuff that only makes it into the TV film. ??And of course, there will probably actually be more than one film - it seems cool actually that ??you might get less value from watching the copyright version because the cool folks who insist on CC are only in the free one :)</span></div> <p /><div><span style="border-collapse: collapse;">Oh there&#39;s so much more to say about all of these, but I have to run to get a train to New York, New York.</span></div> <p /><div><span style="border-collapse: collapse;">Hot diggity dog!<br /> </span> <br /></div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[So actually we're just going to leave Boston in a couple of hours and I'm realising that we've put out very little so far - we've been active on twitter, but the combination of jetlag, an overfilled schedule and unfamiliarity with the city, despit...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Mar 04 04:25:02 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Looking at the Lower Ninth Ward in NOLA</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/looking-at-the-lower-ninth-ward-in-nola</link>	<pubDate>Fri Mar 12 09:51:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Condon]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/looking-at-the-lower-ninth-ward-in-nola</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='217' poster='http://getfile4.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/IeIktkGcchvlvkyiftDhEjxHFwlDIjegFtezHotIyHehjaCIqmzBcsxnbCJj/IMG_0070.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile7.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/IeIktkGcchvlvkyiftDhEjxHFwlDIjegFtezHotIyHehjaCIqmzBcsxnbCJj/IMG_0070.mp4'></source></video></div></p><p>I also made some Audioboo about what I saw:</p><p><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=Driving+round+the+lower+ninth&amp;mp3Time=10.32am+12+Mar+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F104672-driving-round-the-lower-ninth.mp3&amp;mp3Author=brian_condon&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F104672-driving-round-the-lower-ninth" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/104672-driving-round-the-lower-ninth.mp3">Listen!</a></object></p><p>And finding my way back to <a href="http://www.lowernine.org">www.lowernine.org</a></p><p><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=Finding+my+way+back+to+lowernine.org+tuttle2texas&amp;mp3Time=11.05am+12+Mar+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F104673-finding-my-way-back-to-lowernine-org-tuttle2texas.mp3&amp;mp3Author=brian_condon&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F104673-finding-my-way-back-to-lowernine-org-tuttle2texas" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/104673-finding-my-way-back-to-lowernine-org-tuttle2texas.mp3">Listen!</a></object></p><p>And from lowernine.org here's a video from Rick which gives more background and starkly portrays the issues:</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p><object height="360" width="480"><param name="allowfullscreen" value="true" /><param name="allowscriptaccess" value="always" /><param name="movie" value="http://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=306130&amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;show_title=1&amp;show_byline=1&amp;show_portrait=0&amp;color=ffffff&amp;fullscreen=1" /><embed src="http://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=306130&amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;show_title=1&amp;show_byline=1&amp;show_portrait=0&amp;color=ffffff&amp;fullscreen=1" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="360" width="480"></embed></object></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I also made some Audioboo about what I saw: Listen! And finding my way back to www.lowernine.org Listen! And from lowernine.org here's a video from Rick which gives more background and starkly portrays the issues:]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Fri Mar 12 09:51:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Sun Mar 14 08:26:48 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Sun Mar 14 08:26:48 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Beautifully summed up audio boos about the lower nine. Glad you lived out your little boy's dream of driving a pick up truck! Yeehaw! mx]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>My photos so far</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/my-photos-so-far</link>	<pubDate>Sun Mar 14 15:52:12 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/my-photos-so-far</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<object height="375" width="500"> <param name="flashvars" value="offsite=true&lang=en-us&page_show_url=%2Fphotos%2Flloyd-davis%2Fsets%2F72157623593389624%2F%2Fshow%2F&page_show_back_url=%2Fphotos%2Flloyd-davis%2Fsets%2F72157623593389624%2F&set_id=72157623593389624&jump_to=" /></param> <param name="movie" value="http://www.flickr.com/apps/slideshow/show.swf?v=71649" /></param> <param name="allowFullScreen" value="true" /></param><embed src="http://www.flickr.com/apps/slideshow/show.swf?v=71649" allowFullScreen="true" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="375" flashvars="offsite=true&lang=en-us&page_show_url=%2Fphotos%2Flloyd-davis%2Fsets%2F72157623593389624%2F%2Fshow%2F&page_show_back_url=%2Fphotos%2Flloyd-davis%2Fsets%2F72157623593389624%2F&set_id=72157623593389624&jump_to=" width="500"></embed></object>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Mar 14 15:52:12 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[billingtonart]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Sun Mar 14 16:00:04 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Sun Mar 14 16:00:04 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Nice set of photo's there Lloyd]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Yes. We're going on the train.</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/yes-were-going-on-the-train</link>	<pubDate>Tue Jan 19 07:57:17 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/yes-were-going-on-the-train</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People keep trying to persuade me to give up the train idea.</p><p>But it's *the* idea!!!</p><p>Anyhoo.</p><p>Just to give you a picture of what we'll be doing, I've been looking at how long it takes to get from place to place.&nbsp; Here's a first stab.</p><p>5th&nbsp; arrive Boston from LHR.&nbsp; Run conversation space in collaboration with Boston Tuttle (oops haven't spoken to @hobbesoh about that yet!)</p><p>6th Train to NYC leaving about 9am takes 4 hours</p><p>7th Train to DC leaving about 10am takes 3.5 hours</p><p>8th Train to Atlanta leaves about 6.30pm takes 14 hours overnight (arrives 08.13)</p><p>9th Train to New Orleans leaves at 08.38 (tight!) takes 12 hours.</p><p>10th Day in NOLA.&nbsp; Oh wait, when's Taylor's gang going over to Austin from NOLA? (a day's drive at least...) Eeek!</p><p>Oh.&nbsp; OK.&nbsp; Looks like we ran out of time gonna have to rejig, maybe stretch it back a few days?&nbsp; You see I'd really like to be able to spend some more time in these places on the way.&nbsp; I'd especially prefer to have a day in Atlanta rather than hop off a 14 hour trip and onto another 12 hour one... hmmm....</p><p>in the meantime, does anyone know anyone in marketing at Amtrak who might like to give us some free rail passes to do this and publicise their fantastic service all over the interwebs?</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[People keep trying to persuade me to give up the train idea. But it's *the* idea!!! Anyhoo. Just to give you a picture of what we'll be doing, I've been looking at how long it takes to get from place to place. Here's a first stab. 5th arrive Bosto...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Tue Jan 19 07:57:17 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>mail@taylordavidson.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Wed Jan 27 11:59:26 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Wed Jan 27 11:59:26 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[We need to talk scheduling. 10th may work.  Going to drive to Austin either the 10th or the 11th.  But you NEED more than one day in New Orleans.And you need to let me help you find awesome people in Atlanta and DC.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>An air of unreality</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/an-air-of-unreality</link>	<pubDate>Tue Feb 23 06:41:03 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Condon]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/an-air-of-unreality</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[There's an air of unreality about my preparations to go on the tuttle2texas trip. Apart from the obvious problem that I'm not actually going to make it as far as Texas as I will return from New Orleans (via Toronto!) on 13th March. <p /> I've been focused on trying to get the Centre for Creative Collaboration up and running (<a href="http://www.creativecollaboration.org.uk">www.creativecollaboration.org.uk</a>) with my collleagues Thias Martin and Neil Gregory; trying to get the internet into the space (do you realise that you can't actually call BT to order a business phone line - you have to do it all online); working with Lloyd and meeting lots of people who want to visit Acton Street and trying to keep other stuff moving. <p /> The main reason for my trip to North America is to go to see the MaRS Discovery District in Toronto (<a href="http://www.marsdd.com/aboutmars/mission)">http://www.marsdd.com/aboutmars/mission)</a> which combines innovation and social entrepreneurship. I've studied this project from afar and heard about it from people who've been there; but this is the first time I'll be seeing it. I'm also organising other meetings in Toronto. <p /> Then, on Saturday, I'm taking the train to the USA - an overnight stop in Albany; then another train to Boston. Why the train? Why not? <p /> To add to the air of unreality, when I should probably be at home getting sorted for the trip; I'm going to be at the tuttle2texas fund-raiser this evening. See you there!]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[There's an air of unreality about my preparations to go on the tuttle2texas trip. Apart from the obvious problem that I'm not actually going to make it as far as Texas as I will return from New Orleans (via Toronto!) on 13th March. I've been focus...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Tue Feb 23 06:41:03 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>mail@taylordavidson.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Tue Feb 23 18:30:50 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Feb 23 18:30:50 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Brian, there are great people in Toronto like @josephdee, @igniter, @ryancoleman, and some of the people at @MaRSDD.  Let me know if I can help intro from afar...]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Feb 25 12:58:10 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Feb 25 12:58:10 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Hi Taylor - that would be great!  I'll tweet you.Thanks a lot.Brian]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Getting back to the real purpose of the trip</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/getting-back-to-the-real-purpose-of-the-trip</link>	<pubDate>Wed Feb 10 23:55:06 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/getting-back-to-the-real-purpose-of-the-trip</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[Some helpful confusion arose yesterday that showed me where I was getting a bit uncomfortable.?? In talking about getting support for the trip, we&#39;ve naturally focussed on the tangible outputs that we&#39;ll create.?? It sounds so cool that we&#39;ll be making a documentary movie of our trip to show to people when we get back, that I think I&#39;d temporarily lost sight of what we&#39;re actually best at, why we&#39;re doing the trip and therefore why we think people might be interested in helping make it a reality.<p /> I&#39;m a blogger.?? I can&#39;t help it.?? I write on the internet.?? I can&#39;t stop.?? Over the years I think I&#39;ve become quite good at it and I know that people enjoy reading what I write and connecting with me through the various things I do online.?? I&#39;ve also been playing with creating works in other media ever since they worked out how to put enclosures into RSS.<p /> And what that&#39;s done for me is that it&#39;s help me connect with people all over the world, build relationships, working arrangements, friendships and yes a little bit of flirting, romance and downright naughtiness.<p /> So when I started Tuttle, it was above all to explore this concept of building of rich relationships through the emerging social web and experiencing them face-to-face as well as online.?? I wrote and talked a lot at the time about the importance of bootstrapping relationships through meatspace interaction as well as through the net.?? The way that successful meetups complement online social networks and they feed each other.?? <p /> The Tuttle Club and the many social media cafes it&#39;s spawned is a powerful example of this - that&#39;s why I steer us away from too much structure and direction - I want it to have that flavour of the web but with people whose eyes you can look into.?? <p /> The fundamental tool that we&#39;re learning to use is conversation, real conversation - not &quot;conversational marketing&quot; conversations, not &quot;big conversation&quot; conversations and not the transactional chit-chat of the traditional networking event.?? <p /> Real conversations between ordinary people who are doing stuff and are interested in stuff and like talking about it and finding out about it from others.?? These conversations have become the staple at Tuttle and are the killer app in our consulting practice.?? They are hugely powerful forums for changing individuals, groups and organisations, one thought at a time.<p /> And so that is what this trip is about.?? Yes, we&#39;ll have a movie at the end of it, hashed together from all the video we have.?? Heather is also taking the opportunity to make a broadcast-quality documentary about cultures which neatly complements what else we&#39;re doing - she&#39;s a filmmaker, that&#39;s what she does.?? Yes we&#39;ll run some extremely interesting and valuable workshops afterwards on what we&#39;ve learned, and who knows what other things we&#39;ll think of.?? All these things are great and I&#39;m really looking forward to helping make all of them.<p /> But none of those are the real purpose of the trip.<p />The real purpose of the trip is to make connections and build relationships through conversation.?? That&#39;s what Tuttle is really good at.?? That&#39;s why we&#39;re travelling slowly across America in such a crazy, old-fashioned, inefficient way.?? I want to meet old friends with whom I&#39;ve only ever tweeted.?? I also want to meet new people and get to know them and think about who we are and what we have in common and how we&#39;re all trying to make sense of this world that has been turned upside-down in our lifetimes.<p /> If we do all that, then the trip is a success and I&#39;ll have done what I set out to do.?? And then, if we&#39;re lucky, after some reflection, we all might have some stories to tell.]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Some helpful confusion arose yesterday that showed me where I was getting a bit uncomfortable. In talking about getting support for the trip, we've naturally focussed on the tangible outputs that we'll create. It sounds so cool that we'll be makin...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Feb 10 23:55:06 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[kamintone]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Feb 11 06:02:44 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Feb 11 06:02:44 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I was startled and bemused by the term &quot;meatspace interaction&quot; until I realised that it should have been &quot;meetspace&quot; (shouldn't it?)]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Feb 11 11:57:22 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Feb 11 11:57:22 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[nope... http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meatspace]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Take 2</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/take-2</link>	<pubDate>Tue Nov 09 03:49:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/take-2</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I'm going to write here for a bit while I decide whether to set up a whole new space for the forthcoming 2011 trip.&nbsp; There's something nice about leaving tuttle2texas as a completed artefact, but also something attractive about keeping the continuity.&nbsp; It's all tied up too in whether talking about Texas is too confusing - it's really about a coast-to-coast trip that includes a big chunk of time in Texas. Open to ideas on this one, as ever.</p><p>So</p><p>I am going again.&nbsp; My plan is still to start somewhere on the West Coast at the beginning of March, take my time to get over to Austin for the opening of Interactive &amp; Film on 11th.&nbsp; I'd like to get a Gold Pass this year and see more of the Film festival as well as hanging out with my webby pals.</p><p>And then onto all the places we visited last year to see how those new friends are getting on and give them a taste of what the rest of the adventure was like.</p><p>I want to do the bulk of the journey by train again.&nbsp; It's an excellent creative constraint to be held to the timetable.&nbsp; I'm going to try to let go of any other rules completely.</p><p>So for starters, I don't know where to start on the West Coast.&nbsp; There's something nice about beginning in Long Beach with the #tuttlela crowd but I'm also aching to see San Francisco, Portland and Seattle *and* ideally too, I'd love to stop off in Alpine TX just before SXSW to see my mate <a href="http://gapingvoid.com">Hugh</a> in his native surroundings. I may be being greedy here, it has been known.</p><p>So <strong>your first task</strong> is help me decide - tell me where to start and why. And then how, in an ideal world, I'd make my way to Austin.</p><p>Secondly, I'm going to focus on *my* journey rather than try to get a bunch of people to come along with me and do it all together.&nbsp; It's just too complex.&nbsp; I am going.&nbsp; If you want to come with me for any leg of the trip or meet up in any of the cities I visit, then you are very welcome to do so, but it's up to you to work out the details.</p><p>Thirdly, I want to create some collaborative, lasting, social artefact for people to contribute to whether they're able to join in, in the States, or not.&nbsp; It's as poorly thought through as that so far.&nbsp; Ideas welcome.&nbsp; If you're somewhere on or near the route and you have fun things to do there that I could join in with also let me know, a theme might emerge...</p><p>I'm starting to refine the pitch for sponsors.&nbsp; If you have a client who you think would be interested in being associated with this thing, let me know.</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I'm going to write here for a bit while I decide whether to set up a whole new space for the forthcoming 2011 trip. There's something nice about leaving tuttle2texas as a completed artefact, but also something attractive about keeping the continui...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Tue Nov 09 03:49:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name>take-2</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Airport bound: #tuttle2texas</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/airport-bound-tuttle2texas</link>	<pubDate>Tue Mar 02 00:45:47 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/airport-bound-tuttle2texas</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span style=""><span>So it's beginning today. In some ways it's already began, but now the bags are (over) packed and I'm on a very slow 137 on the way to the Piccadilly line.</span><br /><span></span><br /><span>People have asked me if I am excited. I'm not sure yet. It seems all surreal. And though I do have a calm vaneer about our travels I am worried as well. I think if I was just doing the journey, and leading discussions and taking too long train journeys, that wouldn't worry me as much. But shooting a documentary in 6 cities in 10 days and socially documenting it is making me more naceous than excited I think.</span><br /><span></span><br /><span>Am I ready? No. As usual, the night before travel all technical things that could go wrong did. But it's all par for the course, so I shrug and get on with it.</span><br /><span></span><br /><span>It's a bit strange - for this journey Im using the backpack that I used on my way to England, my first great adventure. I packed all of my belongings in this bag on 31 December, 2001 &amp; started a new life on New Years Day. Now I feel the same - all my favourite clothes &amp; electronics are packed (except my Zi8 which maddingly has decide to play hide &amp; seek with me, and still hasn't been found.) And I'm off on one of the greatest adventures &amp; challenges I've ever been on. There's even a maple leaf on my bag - but that's more because I couldn't get it off. Though, as this whole trip is about culture, it does become a reminder of where I came from.</span><br /><span></span><br /><div><p><img border="0" width="300" /></p></div></span>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[So it's beginning today. In some ways it's already began, but now the bags are (over) packed and I'm on a very slow 137 on the way to the Piccadilly line.People have asked me if I am excited. I'm not sure yet. It seems all surreal. And though I do...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Tue Mar 02 00:45:47 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Make or Break</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/make-or-break-5</link>	<pubDate>Sun Feb 14 15:45:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="fundraising"><![CDATA[fundraising]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="ideas"><![CDATA[ideas]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="tuttle"><![CDATA[tuttle]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="tuttle2texas"><![CDATA[tuttle2texas]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/make-or-break-5</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-family: arial, sans-serif; border-collapse: collapse;">It's two weeks on Tuesday before we're due to fly out to Boston. &nbsp;We've had lots of fabulous support, of both the moral and the practical kinds. But if we had to leave tomorrow, with the current levels of sponsorship, we would have to be thinking very hard about whether to go or not. &nbsp;If we're still having to worry about where we're sleeping or how much we can spend on food then we're going to be distracted from the important work of connecting with people and having meaningful conversations with them. &nbsp;It might still be a great adventure, but probably a more stressful adventure than we thought we were signing up to. &nbsp; </span></p><div><br /><div>So it's make or break time.</div><div>If you're not sure what it is that we're doing this for, take a look at <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/getting-back-to-the-real-purpose-of-the-trip" target="_blank">my previous post</a>. &nbsp;The nub of it was:</div><div><span style="border-collapse: separate; color: #424037; font-family: Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 12px; line-height: 21px;">"The real purpose of the trip is to make connections and build relationships through conversation.&nbsp; That's what Tuttle is really good at... &nbsp;I want to meet old friends with whom I've only ever tweeted.&nbsp; I also want to meet new people and get to know them and think about who we are and what we have in common and how we're all trying to make sense of this world that has been turned upside-down in our lifetimes."</span></div><div>This is certainly not something that I can do on my own and it's not even something that Heather, Brian, Al, Patrick, Rose and I or any other individuals can do without your help. &nbsp;</div><div>We're taking Tuttle to Texas and that means Tuttle is going to make it happen.</div><div>There are two approaches to making things easier - increase funds and decrease costs (by sponsorship in kind - particularly accommodation) - we're pushing on the former but both are valid. &nbsp;Any hotel chains want to put us up all along the route? Anyone know a real person we can talk to in media relations at Amtrak rather than the anonymised e-mail address?</div><div>I'm setting up a Facebook fanpage for you to show your support - the more the merrier - it will help show potential sponsors exactly where the love is for this project.</div><div>On the londonsocialmediacafe wiki we've set up <a href="http://londonsocialmediacafe.pbworks.com/tuttle2texas" target="_blank">a main page with a description of what we're doing</a> and a set of city pages to collect information about what the plan is for each stop off point on the way to Austin.</div><div>Please don't worry about getting the message to the "right" people (although if you can put us in touch directly with decision-makers and budget-holders that's great) get it to as many people as you can - our experience is that the most unexpected connections can often be the most valuable.</div><div>Here's some things you can do.</div><div><ul><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Use the hashtag #tuttle2texas to make a noise.</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Pass this message on on Twitter (or Google Buzz or your microblogging platform of choice ) - that we need help, we need friends, we need cash</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Become a <a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Tuttle-2-Texas/307800467715" target="_blank">fan of the project on Facebook</a></li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Fill in any gaps on the city pages on the wiki - if you're going to be in that city or you know folk who can help organise venues and or give some or all of us hospitality in exchange for being part of a great conversation and a great adventure, please let us know</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Join in with a fundraiser w/c 22nd Feb - pledge objects &amp; services for auction, come ready to spend your cash and invite other rich people...</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Write a message of support about us on your blog, letting people know what we're doing, why you think it's cool and that you'll be watching. Tag it with #tuttle2texas</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Talk to other people about whether and how they can help</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Point Marketing &amp; PR people at the <a href="http://bit.ly/t2t-sotd" target="_blank">daily sponsorship post</a>&nbsp;and tell them why they should support us</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Think of other things you can do to help - just please don't do anything illegal, dishonest or immoral - if in doubt, check with us (not just me) - tweet it with the hashtag #tuttle2texas :)</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Tell us other ways you can think of specifically to raise funds</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Tell us what else you need in order to sell this to people</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Take it easy and keep it in perspective - this is *not* the most important thing in the world right now. &nbsp;If you're having to choose between helping us and helping people survive day to day in Haiti - please, please, please give it to them.</li></ul></div></div><p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[It's two weeks on Tuesday before we're due to fly out to Boston. We've had lots of fabulous support, of both the moral and the practical kinds. But if we had to leave tomorrow, with the current levels of sponsorship, we would have to be thinking v...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Feb 14 15:45:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name>make-or-break</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Mon Feb 15 10:07:56 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Mon Feb 15 10:07:56 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[i wish you the best with this lloyd - retweeted out.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Tue Feb 16 02:53:11 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Feb 16 02:53:11 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[thanks Phil, would still love to take you and others if we can raise more cash  - I saw roadcamp isn't happening, you still interested?]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[tdavidson]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Wed Feb 17 21:33:03 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Wed Feb 17 21:33:03 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Email with contact points, sent.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>My SXSWi experience</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/my-sxswi-experience</link>	<pubDate>Sun Apr 04 15:33:33 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/my-sxswi-experience</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[[<i>Note: I wrote this on Thursday 18th - which means it must have been during the 36-hour train ride. ??Don&#39;t know why I didn&#39;t post immediately. ??Not sure if I still draw the same conclusion - I&#39;m mellowing on it, or maybe the memory is slipping away</i>]<p /> Well it&#39;s over now.<p />This was my second time at SXSW interactive. ??I was ready for it to not be as exciting as the first time. ??On the first day I took everything in, cameras, phones, laptops, chargers, cables etc. and I got tired out carrying it all around. ??On the second day I went minimalist and realised I hadn&#39;t got some things that were really important. ??That&#39;s a micro version of my south-by experience - the first time I went I tried to do as much as I could and felt exhausted, this time I took it really easy, only went to a handful of sessions and ended up feeling like I&#39;d probably missed something.<p /> Truth is, everybody misses something. ??You cannot do it all. There is too much. ??It&#39;s OK to have a light time - I still made lots of new connections and built on existing relationships. However, I also had Taylor&#39;s advice ringing in my ears.<p /> <iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/Q6MCAieMEUg?wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen frameborder="0" height="417" width="500"></iframe><p />In addition, the festival has simply grown again. ??Whether it&#39;s too big or still not big enough, I don&#39;t know. ??My interpretation of what was happening was that there were an awful lot of people there who had been sent by their employer because everyone knows it&#39;s a cool place to be. ??They didn&#39;t necessarily know how or why it was cool, but they were there to rub shoulders with the cool kids. ??They were not contributing particularly to any coolness - they were there to observe and appreciate it. ??And that, I think, is why SXSWi has moved on from being a must-do event to a &quot;might-do if I can get someone to pay for me to go&quot; ??]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[[Note: I wrote this on Thursday 18th - which means it must have been during the 36-hour train ride. Don't know why I didn't post immediately. Not sure if I still draw the same conclusion - I'm mellowing on it, or maybe the memory is slipping away]...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Apr 04 15:33:33 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Walking in Boston</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/walking-in-boston-1</link>	<pubDate>Thu Mar 04 04:22:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/walking-in-boston-1</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=Walking+in+boston&amp;mp3Time=01.26pm+03+Mar+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F102164-walking-in-boston.mp3&amp;mp3Author=Lloyddavis&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F102164-walking-in-boston" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/102164-walking-in-boston.mp3">Listen!</a></object><p /></p><div>recorded yesterday between my hotel and the <a href="http://techsuperpowers.com/digilounge">digilounge</a></div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Listen! recorded yesterday between my hotel and the digilounge]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Mar 04 04:22:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Day 3: New York &amp; our venture into Brooklyn</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/day-3-new-york-and-our-venture-into-brooklyn</link>	<pubDate>Sun Mar 07 05:34:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/day-3-new-york-and-our-venture-into-brooklyn</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-size: small;"><span style="font-family: Times New Roman;">It&rsquo;s Day 5 of Tuttle2Texas and we&rsquo;re leaving NYC about an hour late to Washington.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>I can&rsquo;t believe we&rsquo;re already leaving New York as it feels like we were just getting started.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>This leg of the trip Michelle and I stayed with Nick and Martha Desbiens and their 2 year old son Adrian. When we arrived on Thursday, we travelled out to Brooklyn where Nick and Martha lived near Grand Army Plaza/ <a href="http://www.prospectpark.org/">Prospect Park</a>. After introductions and making of fake pizza with Adrian, Michelle and I headed out to get some New York shots before we lost the light.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Unfortunately we did lose it in the end as we were having so much fun chatting with Martha, that by the time we got into Manhattan, it was dusk.<span style="">&nbsp; </span></span></span></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: small;">&nbsp;</span></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: small;">Waiting for it to get a bit darker, Michelle and I cruised around the tip of central park, saw the horse and carriages lined up along the road, and rounded back to Carnegie Hall. Then travelling south we headed towards the daylight, I mean lights of time square, getting night shots along the way. Times Square was packed with people and according to our hosts, was only pedestrianised 3 months ago.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>I think that was a wise decision as I looked around at all the tourists with their cameras as they wandered the square.</span></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: small;">&nbsp;</span></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: small;">As it was New York and it was night, pretzels were in order which is why Michelle and I had to partake.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>It wasn&rsquo;t as good as we thought they would be (maybe they needed to be heated up a bit more?) but they were salty and covered in mustard so it was a good between meal snack.</span></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: small;">&nbsp;</span></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: small;">Nick and Martha have been in their Brooklyn flat for the last year and a half and there seems to be tons of room for their son and them to live.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>It&rsquo;s still very small so there&rsquo;s not enough room to really play.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>I now understand why there are play centres and why moms and nannies are always sitting in parks in the movies. We settled on Sushi for dinner and Michelle and I picked up some Brooklyn Pale Ale.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>As I had tried UFO and Samuel Adams in Boston, I had to try something local in New York.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>We actually asked a man in the local grocery store what we should get as there were about 5 coolers full of beer in the shop we went into.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Supposedly, Brooklyn Lager is good for a spicy meal and Brooklyn Pale Ale is perfect for a rich meal.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>It&rsquo;s always good to know local beers like ones from the Brooklyn Brewery&nbsp;&ndash; it makes it easier to impress locals on my next visit.</span></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-size: small;"><span style="font-family: Times New Roman;"><span style="">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; </span><span style="">&nbsp;</span></span></span></span></p><p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: small;">We interviewed the Desbiens the first night we met and Nick commented on how it was the first time he had ever thought or spoke that long about how he used the internet and social media. The next day&hellip;he started following me on Twitter.</span></span></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[It???s Day 5 of Tuttle2Texas and we???re leaving NYC about an hour late to Washington. I can???t believe we???re already leaving New York as it feels like we were just getting started. This leg of the trip Michelle and I stayed with Nick and Martha Desbie...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Mar 07 05:34:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>We need to talk about money</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/we-need-to-talk-about-money</link>	<pubDate>Thu Feb 18 02:22:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/we-need-to-talk-about-money</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/2737785853"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3279/2737785853_693ab249c1_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a></div><p /><p>I believe very strongly in organising without organisations - I've held back from incorporating Tuttle for some time for example until we know that we really, really need to. &nbsp;It's a lesson I learned early on as an Information Manager playing with intranets - you need structure, but if you're trying to grow something organic (is there any other way?) you need as little structure as possible to give people some security but not constrain their imaginations for how hugely something can grow.</p><p /><div>However, when we start to do something like this project and we add up all the pennies and gifts in kind that we'll need to get from London to Boston to Austin to LA and back again (plus all the awesome stuff in between) we realise that we need to take some money from larger organisations - top whack, to do the trip comfortably with all the people we'd like to take requires just over &pound;25k - we can and will do it for less but if there are organisations out there who can benefit from the sort of exposure and conversation we create then we're not being of optimum service if we deliberately turn money from them down. &nbsp;And I like to be of optimum service :)</div><p /><div>We have some very promising leads and possibilities for sponsors of the day and I want to announce them as soon as we can. &nbsp;But this is where it gets tricky. &nbsp;It's difficult for small bands of social media companeros like us to engage with organisations like this quietly - the "way they do things" is that you talk quietly to folk and ask for stuff and they go and talk to other folk and you're left sat waiting and unsure and then request after request comes for specific bits of information because the people making the decision don't know anything at all about what you're trying to do. &nbsp; In the meantime we can't say anything in public and so people think that nothing is happening and they (and sometimes we) lose confidence that it will ever come together. &nbsp;</div><p /><div>On the other hand the way we normally do things is we blog about stuff and we talk loudly on the internet and in real life and people hear and get pulled in and fired up by our passion and enthusiasm and straight thinking and, lets face it, damned good looks, and they open their hearts and their wallets at the same time.</div><p /><div>So in addition to talking quietly to guys and gals in suits, &nbsp;I'm looking for ways to allow the people who love us and wish us well to be able to give us a fiver without it all being gobbled up in transaction fees. Of course the easiest way to do that with people who are in London is to see them face to face and shake the bucket. &nbsp;For people outside London we need something online and in any case I'd love an easy way of letting people know how much they've raised together - tell me the best way of doing this here in the UK, folks.</div><p /><div>In any case we're doing a fundraiser next Tuesday evening (23rd February) at the <a href="http://creativecollaboration.org.uk" target="_blank">Centre for Creative Collaboration</a>. &nbsp;You won't be surprised to hear that there'll be ukulele and poetry and singing and other bits of performance and we'll have some things to auction or raffle or something (if you have something you want to donate as a raffle prize let me know). We'll get something more detailed up on the wiki later today and point you there from twitter. And if you can't make it, but are coming to Tuttle on Friday, you can slip me a brown envelope there. &nbsp;But for now, put the date in your diary and put a few quid aside to throw at us.</div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I believe very strongly in organising without organisations - I've held back from incorporating Tuttle for some time for example until we know that we really, really need to. It's a lesson I learned early on as an Information Manager playing with ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Feb 18 02:22:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[joannejacobs]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Wed Feb 24 02:01:56 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Wed Feb 24 02:01:56 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[You know, looking a that pig, we found a superb way to earn cash at ACID in Australia.  We bought a big plastic box and filled it usually weekly with single serve snack food (fun-size chocolates, sweets, little boxes of sultanas and muesli bars; basically anything that came in a wrapper) and we charged a flat fee for the goods, but a very small payment - the equivalent of about ??0.30.  Now we mostly bought these in bulk from discount stores and could occasionally get very good rates.  Plus some people didn't have exact change so put in a few more cents/pennies to pay for their energy kick.  At the end of every month there was always more cash than was required.  (We found that when you have a micropayments model, people are prepared to pay a little more than if you charge commercial rates.)  Now at ACID and later at Xenial, we used the profits to pay for Friday drinkies or the odd birthday cake.  But you could inject the profits back in to the Centre.  It won't get you a fortune but it will:(a) keep people at the Centre when they are working rather than send them off elsewhere for a snack; and(b) keep tuttlers happy on a Friday morning!Hope that helps!Cheers,jjPS - we genuinely had a piggy bank to pay for what was both the ACID and the Xenial pig!]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Wed Feb 24 02:07:13 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Wed Feb 24 02:07:13 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Thanks Jo, yes, we started asking for contributions to the coffee fund last Friday morning and it worked well, but your idea extends it a bit further.  I'm only just getting over the trauma of the old routine I used to have to go to to extract contributions at the Coach &amp; Horses when we had a weekly rental to find.  This feels very different.  I miss lots of things about using that upstairs room in Greek St, but shaking the bucket like that isn't one of them :)]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Overnight to Atlanta</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/overnight-to-atlanta</link>	<pubDate>Sun Apr 04 15:39:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="amtrak"><![CDATA[amtrak]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="atlanta"><![CDATA[atlanta]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="dc"><![CDATA[dc]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="distractions"><![CDATA[distractions]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="overnight"><![CDATA[overnight]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="relationships"><![CDATA[relationships]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="sleep"><![CDATA[sleep]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/overnight-to-atlanta</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><p>[<em>I wrote this longhand in my notebook and didn't type it up. &nbsp;Soon after I wrote it, I realised that the curry I'd had for lunch was going to give me the full Johnny Cash experience - I didn't sleep much at all...]</em></p><p>I'm on a midnight train to Georgia. &nbsp;Well not quite. &nbsp;It's 7.30pm and we left Washington DC an hour ago for a 14 hour overnight ride to Atlanta GA. &nbsp;So I will be on it at midnight but not sure I'll be awake by then. &nbsp;Well at least I hope I'll be asleep. &nbsp;The train horn seems to sound several times a minute, in case, I guess, wandering wildlife don't hear the rattling of the tracks as we thunder through Virginia. &nbsp;There's a little low chatter in this carriage but mostly the sound is of people sitting together in communal quietness punctuated by those laughing at th eDVDs that they're watching or the shifting of someone in their seat. &nbsp;The woman behind me was oozing into her cellphone when we left DC but she's quietened down now too. &nbsp;This ride is our longest although I don't know yet what I'm going to do after Austin. &nbsp;The 1400 mile trip to LA is no more than a desire to be at LAX on Sunday 21st. &nbsp;Of course it's more than a desire, it's a necessity and it's also still two weeks away.</p><p>I've found it quite difficult to get into the moment on this trip, to stop thinking about what's coming and what might have been and focus on what we're actually doing right now. &nbsp;There have been two reasons for this, I think &nbsp;First was that we didn't have money in place and I couldn't see how it was going to work and got into the frame of mind where I believed somehow that thining about it some more would help. &nbsp;Big mistake. &nbsp;What really helped was to write about it, get it out and get reassured - partly by some lovely donations from friends but uals ojust from the overall reaction that people had - everyone wanted to help out. &nbsp;There isn't anything less to worry about (objectively speaking) it's just that I realised I was worrying about things over which I have little influence and recognising those limits helpe me worry less. &nbsp;</p><p>The other issue is that I was spending time with someone, Dana, whom I've been getting to know well for a while and whom I care for very much. &nbsp;But she also lives in Newfoundland and I in London and so we haven't spent so much time face to face. &nbsp;We've been building a romantic relationship, using these tools, we've talked to each other practically every day by skype, phreadz (thanks Kosso!) IM and DMs and we've written letters and postcards and I sent her flowers for Valentines Day, but... but we hadn't kissed until we saw each other in Boston Airport.</p><p>So yeah. &nbsp;I've been distracted by that too. &nbsp;Getting to build the face to face, hand in hand, gazing into each others eyes part of our relationship. &nbsp;And while that's been lovely, it did make it hard for me to focus on the early part of the trip especially as I struggled with jetlag an dgeneral tiredness after running around getting bits of the trip together. &nbsp;So now, I've stopped worrying (at least for the time being) Dana's gone back to Newfoundland to go back to work and my mind and body are getting used to which part of the world I'm in. &nbsp;And so I feel like I'm ready for the adventurous part. &nbsp;The part where we get far away from places where they're used to hearing English accents. &nbsp;Brian and I have given in on the accomodation part and are relying on the kindness of strangers despite our embarrassment at doing so, and I'm really glad that I'm going to be able to stay with Sarah Vela in Austin and hang out with the other lovelies there. &nbsp;Plus Stephanie Frost has set up big fun for us in Atlanta and Taylor D has done a great job for us on the ground in NOLA. &nbsp;The amazing adventure is getting even amazinger!</p><p /></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[[I wrote this longhand in my notebook and didn't type it up. Soon after I wrote it, I realised that the curry I'd had for lunch was going to give me the full Johnny Cash experience - I didn't sleep much at all...] I'm on a midnight train to Georgi...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Apr 04 15:39:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Day 1. Morning Coffee</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/day-1-morning-coffee</link>	<pubDate>Mon Mar 01 22:35:20 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/day-1-morning-coffee</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='217' poster='http://getfile4.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/FSlKSFuzg0ngw31uAl2fGGHlsmJlWQI2vkPZtdDTvR2TWSeBlBjkj5NjMZhc/02032010055.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile3.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/FSlKSFuzg0ngw31uAl2fGGHlsmJlWQI2vkPZtdDTvR2TWSeBlBjkj5NjMZhc/02032010055.mp4'></source></video></div><p>On my way! <br /></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[On my way!]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Mar 01 22:35:20 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Gearing up for SXSWi 2011</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/gearing-up-for-sxswi-2011</link>	<pubDate>Wed Aug 04 15:34:49 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/gearing-up-for-sxswi-2011</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4446618867"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2719/4446618867_5a4ac6219f_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a><p />There are a couple of things coming up that I wanted to let you know about.<p />Firstly, the panel picker for SXSWi 2011 is going live on Monday 9th August.?? I&#39;ve submitted a suggestion for a session talking about this year&#39;s trip and what we learned and it will be really helpful if you can find my panel and vote for, comment, blog and microblog on it and encourage all of your friends to do the same, twice.?? Naturally I&#39;ll point you to the right place <i>ad nauseam</i> when it all comes out next week<p /> Here&#39;s the blurb I wrote for it:<p /><i>&quot;On March 2nd 2010 members of London&#39;s Tuttle Club set off for SXSWi. The plan for the following 2 weeks was to travel from Boston to Austin by train, meeting up with friends from the social web as we went and just see what happened. We&#39;ve since coined the term Social Art Field Trip to describe sort of thing ??? where Social Art is the ???skilfull bringing together of people online and off- to create a sense of beauty???. Armed with cameras, phones &amp; netbooks, we were ready to make something beautiful and interesting by building new relationships and documenting our journey as we went.</i> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;"><i>We gained huge support from our friends but set out with less money than we thought we needed. Yet we made it and, on our way to Texas, we were repeatedly blown away by the kindness of strangers. From the ukulele-playing old folk in Maryland to the lady in NOLA who left us the keys to her home in the mailbox, we came back with stories galore of kindness and generosity facilitated by the social web.</i></p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;"><i>Our session tells this story of hope, determination and making do with what you have. It shows how powerful the social web can be when applied to organising people to do cool stuff. It shows how social capital built up on the web can be leveraged for real-world results even if those results aren&#39;t directly measurable in cashflow. It shows how creative collaboration thrives among highly-connected people and how we make gorgeous and unexpected things happen when we ask the whole our social graph for help.&quot;</i></p> <br />Of course, implicit in this is the idea that we&#39;re all going to go again.?? My current ideal scenario is that we travel in the other direction next year.?? That is, we start on the west coast shortly before the festival and then travel back through the cities we went to last year doing tweetups with screenings of the movie as we go.<p /> The movie??? Oh yeah, didn&#39;t I say that bit??? Yeah.?? The plan is to have a short to enter into the SXSWi Film Festival too, out of the 24 or so hours of video that Heather and Michelle shot over the two weeks of their bit of the trip.<p /> Heather&#39;s going to be getting it off the DV tape in a couple of week&#39;s time.?? Then when we have it in an easier-to-distribute format we need to transcribe it - we have notes of what&#39;s on each tape, but to pull the whole story out, we need a full transcription.<p /> So we&#39;re going to make it into something that you can all join in, if you want to.?? We&#39;ll chop all 24 hours of it into digestible chunks and allow you to download them, transcribe the contents and submit the transcription to a central repository.?? If you have ideas about how to make it all less of a chore for us all, that would be cool.<p /> We&#39;ll give you more details when we&#39;re ready to go but I wanted to let you know what we were up to.?? Oh, and if you&#39;ve any ideas about how you&#39;d like to take part in or otherwise help with next year&#39;s trip, just give me a shout.]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[There are a couple of things coming up that I wanted to let you know about.Firstly, the panel picker for SXSWi 2011 is going live on Monday 9th August. I've submitted a suggestion for a session talking about this year's trip and what we learned an...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Aug 04 15:34:49 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name>gearing-up-for-sxswi-2011</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Ray Nichols]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>raynichols@cox.net</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Aug 05 14:28:25 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Aug 05 14:28:25 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Great ideas Lloyd!  Really enjoyed our chat re: the struggle between those of us advocating collaboration &amp; those whose engagement is political...Best with this!Ray]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Aug 05 14:38:16 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Aug 05 14:38:16 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Thanks Ray!I keep meaning to say thank you again for the copy of &quot;Telling True Stories&quot; that you gave me when we went out on the tour.  It's full of fantastic stuff that's been really useful and inspiring to me.You should also know that the picture of you on the wall at C4CC that I took when you were driving and which has a glinting fleur-de-lys on your hat is the one that catches most visitors' eye.  Everyone wants to know who you are and why we were with you.  And I tell 'em :)]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Tue Aug 10 09:34:17 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Aug 10 09:34:17 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I'll think of a way I can participate next year...By the way, I have just read a large batch of your daily reports - it works really well reading several in one go! Good stuff.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Tue Aug 10 14:54:34 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Aug 10 14:54:34 -0700 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[thank you! did you read them as e-mails or the digest that I've put here?]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Untitled</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/13004912</link>	<pubDate>Mon Mar 08 15:13:15 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Condon]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/13004912</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class='p_embed p_image_embed'><a href="http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/AEfpzAzifbFlxhpoefFjDdjbndkjqiHdyHDfqbnayEedpdtymcxDGxwxkpzg/IMG_0066.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0066" height="667" src="http://getfile4.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/AEfpzAzifbFlxhpoefFjDdjbndkjqiHdyHDfqbnayEedpdtymcxDGxwxkpzg/IMG_0066.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a></div></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Mar 08 15:13:15 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Tuttle2texas update: you too can &quot;chip in&quot;</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/tuttle2texas-update-you-too-can-chip-in-0</link>	<pubDate>Mon Feb 22 13:02:07 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/tuttle2texas-update-you-too-can-chip-in-0</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F99997-tuttle2texas-update-you-too-can-chip-in.mp3&amp;mp3Author=Propgrl&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F99997-tuttle2texas-update-you-too-can-chip-in&amp;mp3Title=Tuttle2texas+update%3A+you+too+can+%22chip+in%22&amp;mp3Time=05.52pm+22+Feb+2010" /></object><p /></p><p>And if you want to chip in, you can now:</p><p><embed src="http://widget.chipin.com/widget/id/d38e54751b2c1a96" height="250" width="250"></embed></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[And if you want to chip in, you can now:]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Feb 22 13:02:07 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>The countdown has truely begun</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/the-countdown-has-truely-begun</link>	<pubDate>Mon Feb 08 18:11:08 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/the-countdown-has-truely-begun</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today my flights were finally booked and it sunk in that we are leaving 3 weeks from tomorrow to Boston. And there's so much to do.&nbsp; We still don't have funding in place but with tickets booked, I'm going on a wing and a prayer as is the rest of us.&nbsp; I trust that we can make this work and regardless of what is or isn't in place, I know that we will discuss culture across borders and countries unlike any I've had before.&nbsp; I also finally get to go to many of the cities that I've always wanted to see but never have had the chance to.&nbsp; For Michelle, who's coming along to film and take part, she's never been to the states other than a quick trip across the border into Idaho from Canada. It will be facinating to see these new places through her eyes.</p><p>I've also come to the realization that we will be travelling in March and though there is (usually) no snow in England at this time, there will probably be plenty along the East Coast.&nbsp; I so hope it isn't too cold.&nbsp; Today the weather is as follows:</p><p>Boston 1 C | -7 C<br />Washington 1 C | -7 C<br />New York 3&deg;C | -7&deg;C<br />Atlanta 11&deg;C | 3&deg;C<br />New Orleans 13&deg;C | 1&deg;C<br />Austin 8&deg;C | 0&deg;C</p><p>I know I know.&nbsp; I'm Canadian.&nbsp; This snow should be nothing to me. And some of those temperatures snow can't touch.&nbsp; But as I've acclimatized to British language, culture and customs, so have I acclimatized to the weather. So I must remember to pack extra socks amongst the camara equipment and hope to stay in places with good heating.</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Today my flights were finally booked and it sunk in that we are leaving 3 weeks from tomorrow to Boston. And there's so much to do. We still don't have funding in place but with tickets booked, I'm going on a wing and a prayer as is the rest of us...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Feb 08 18:11:08 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Lloyd's technology fail (NYC)</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/lloyds-technology-fail-nyc</link>	<pubDate>Wed Mar 10 13:26:31 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/lloyds-technology-fail-nyc</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='164' poster='http://getfile2.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/gN8dD1FiH76AIyY3f8BwLcKHmjEDl5yxosRezw1V7RYt9Gq71D3axoVei0jU/dick.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile8.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/gN8dD1FiH76AIyY3f8BwLcKHmjEDl5yxosRezw1V7RYt9Gq71D3axoVei0jU/dick.mp4'></source></video></div><p>In which I forget that I left the camera on video not stills, suddenly remember, and cuss myself</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[In which I forget that I left the camera on video not stills, suddenly remember, and cuss myself]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Mar 10 13:26:31 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Retracing our steps</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/retracing-our-steps</link>	<pubDate>Sun Apr 04 14:28:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="afterwards"><![CDATA[afterwards]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="review"><![CDATA[review]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="sensemaking"><![CDATA[sensemaking]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="thinking"><![CDATA[thinking]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="writing"><![CDATA[writing]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/retracing-our-steps</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I got back home two weeks ago tomorrow. &nbsp;</p><p>One week went to jetlag. &nbsp;LAX -&gt; LHR was the furthest I've ever flown and it felt like it. &nbsp;Added to the 7 hours time difference was accumulated tiredness from the trip itself and from the period leading up to it and the fact that I'd been through enough time zone changes including a Daylight Savings Time change to ensure that my body was totally confused about what time it was. &nbsp;Towards the end of that first week a friend gave me some melatonin - it worked beautifully - next time I'm not travelling without it... &nbsp;</p><p>Ha ha! "Next time"! You thought there wasn't going to be a next time. &nbsp;Well. &nbsp;Don't know where, don't know when, but I got the taste for this kind of travelling, meeting new people, studying culture, thinking, writing, talking, stretching and stretching my comfort zone and I'll be definitely doing it again.</p><p>Anyway, during the second week (the one that's just gone) I got more and more frustrated with myself for not being able to write - not being able to write up what we'd done, not being able to type up handwritten notes, not being able to annotate or tag photos. &nbsp;Plus I don't have a powerful enough computer at the moment to edit or even really look at the video I shot. &nbsp;I feel guilty about not writing about the kit I was lent for the trip mixed with a recurrence of the old resentment that these loans are so short and the value exchange so biased. &nbsp;And I feel guilty about not being able to more swiftly tell more of the stories of the amazing people we met along the way. &nbsp;So exhaustion followed by frustration, guilt and resentment - mmmm... attractive!</p><p>And then I started to see light at the end of the tunnel (btw didn't go through many tunnels at all on Amtrak - there's a wee story about it that needs to be written, but it's very wee and it doesn't fit here). &nbsp;I started to see what to do next. &nbsp;</p><p>And of course it happened at Tuttle on Friday. &nbsp;I was talking to Fergus Bell about making sense of it all, I've become obsessed with "making sense of it all" and somehow, I don't know how, neither does he, he helped me to see that my role is not so much to make sense of it all, but to create a process of some kind, to hold the space for others to make sense of it with me. &nbsp;And I felt much better. &nbsp;And then I did a little slideshow of the 956 photographs that I took and that I've uploaded to flickr. &nbsp;And I had the chance to talk about it with a group for the first time instead of the formulaic "How was the trip?" "Amazing" "Oh really what was your favourite part" etc. interview that we fall into so easily one-to-one.</p><p>Now that process, in it's form, is unlikely to be very different from what I was intending to do "to make sense of it all" ie I will be writing about the trip, about what we did, where we went, what I learned, how I changed, how it changed me. &nbsp;However I've let go of the responsibility of having to make it all be manageable and understandable by me and therefore I feel liberated to start doing it. &nbsp;I'm writing again - look... it's happening... as I ummm... write.</p><p>So all that's a bit of a warning, I suppose that what comes next here, and on perfectpath and on the tuttle blog probably, will likely be quite messy and jump around a lot &nbsp;- it won't be a smooth chronological journey back through that month of March 2010 which turned out to be so remarkable and important to me. &nbsp;It will be (at least at the start, I think) a jumble of snippets and glimpses and ramblings and it might not make sense to any of us. &nbsp;</p><p>And that's OK.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I got back home two weeks ago tomorrow. One week went to jetlag. LAX -> LHR was the furthest I've ever flown and it felt like it. Added to the 7 hours time difference was accumulated tiredness from the trip itself and from the period leading up to...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Apr 04 14:28:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>States</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/states-135</link>	<pubDate>Mon Apr 05 07:21:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/states-135</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I travelled through 20 states on my journey. &nbsp;I think Brian may have gone home via Chicago so that would bump up the team total, but from this list, Dana came as far as New York, Brian to Louisiana and Heather and Michelle as far as Texas.&nbsp;</p><div>Some of them I went through in the dark and I only put my foot on the ground in nine of them - can you tell which?<p /><div><ol><li>Massachusetts</li><li>Rhode Island</li><li>Connecticut</li><li>New York</li><li>New Jersey</li><li>Pennsylvania</li><li>Delaware</li><li>Maryland</li><li>DC</li><li>Virginia</li><li>North Carolina</li><li>South Carolina</li><li>Georgia</li><li>Alabama</li><li>Mississippi</li><li>Louisiana</li><li>Texas</li><li>New Mexico</li><li>Arizona</li><li>California</li></ol></div><p /></div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I travelled through 20 states on my journey. I think Brian may have gone home via Chicago so that would bump up the team total, but from this list, Dana came as far as New York, Brian to Louisiana and Heather and Michelle as far as Texas. Some of ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Apr 05 07:21:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Asking for help, again</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/asking-for-help-again</link>	<pubDate>Fri Mar 05 02:54:42 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/asking-for-help-again</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">In summary: We need practical offers of help and support to keep this trip (but more importantly, ourselves) going. This includes, but is not limited to, bringing in immediate funds from sponsors or other sources.??</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">People ask how the trip is going. It&#39;s going well. But that doesn&#39;t mean that it&#39;s necessarily comfortable. As with other things Tuttle, we got started, rather than waiting for the whole thing to be planned, sorted, pinned down. I think it&#39;s important to keep doing this, to keep showing that stuff can be done differently and to recognise that art, including social art, requires someone to take an audacious step into the unknown.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">I think that mostly when people ask that question, they mean have we raised enough money? And that&#39;s actually quite a difficult question to answer beyond ???No???!. Like most creative entrepreneurs we are pulling ourselves up by our bootstraps. We have covered our flights to and from the US in different ways ??? speaking just for myself, I am being supported by Metrotwin in return for running a workshop for them in NYC and writing a blog post about what they&#39;re doing. Heather and Brian have used savings and credit, at their own risk, to pay for their rail passes and some accommodation. I&#39;ve dug into savings for accommodation for the first few nights. I have a personal rule that I don&#39;t use unsecured credit. I don&#39;t have a credit card. That makes my life much simpler in lots of ways. It also makes it more difficult. I am committed to not incurring any personal unsecured debt during this trip ??? I find that it makes for quite a creative if sometimes vexing constraint.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">We have agreements for support with a couple of organisations which amount to ??3250 though we&#39;re still waiting for that money to come through. And I&#39;ve been thrilled daily by the influx of funds donated by friends and family who just want to help make it happen.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">In order to make the whole thing break even though, we raise at least twice as much as that again. Anything you can do to help us find more sponsors of the day is very welcome.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">Our current prominent issue is that Brian &amp; I don&#39;t know where we&#39;re going to stay in Washington DC yet and I&#39;m relying on money flowing through faster in order to pay for it. Beyond that we had to make the decision that we could not afford right now to book a room on the overnight train to Atlanta on Sunday night and will have to sleep in our seats. ??</p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">The important thing when asking for help though is not just to present the problem but to be clear where you think others can be of use. ??So suggestions of which cool hotels you stayed in in Washington are lovely but essentially an added cognitive overhead for us to deal with. ??Offers of somewhere central and free to cheap to stay are much more useful as is finding us a sponsor of the day who can immediately transfer funds. ??We&#39;re open to other ways of doing things and believe me we&#39;re grateful for everyone who offers an idea - we just need more in terms of practical help - people who can do things rather than throw more ideas at us.??</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">Yet again, making it up as we go along and staying flexible is an important part of the work. The project is a bit like a piece of improvisational theatre. Before we arrived it was like waiting in the wings for the moment to step on stage, knowing that there&#39;s nothing you can do yet and once you get started, apart from some simple bits of structure you have no idea what&#39;s going to happen.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">So everyday we don&#39;t know what we&#39;re going to do, who we&#39;re going to meet, what might happen at all. To me that&#39;s what makes it worth doing, but I can see that for some people, that makes it hard to understand.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">Right now I&#39;m in the low spot where we&#39;ve made some bold first moves, we&#39;ve got some laughs and the general support of the audience, but I don&#39;t know quite what to do next to keep it all together. The phrase ???It&#39;s all part of the adventure??? is wearing mighty thin - it&#39;s this point where confidence starts to stray - ???Who&#39;s stupid idea was this? What on earth made me think I could make it work? You should have done X, you should have done Y, you should have should have, should have...??? </p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">But I&#39;ve been here before believe the only answer is to keep making bold moves , keep showing up to the work and above all rely on help from your fellow actors and the audience ??? use whatever comes to hand. And the way we get support from the audience (whether that&#39;s the sort of support I think I need or not) is to blog about it, write about it on the internet, do what we do best, talk the thing through ??? certainly lying in bed at 5am jetlagged and trying to <b>think</b> a solution is only going to get me a headache.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">So yeah. ???Halp. Plz I needs it???</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[In summary: We need practical offers of help and support to keep this trip (but more importantly, ourselves) going. This includes, but is not limited to, bringing in immediate funds from sponsors or other sources. People ask how the trip is going....]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Fri Mar 05 02:54:42 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Jason Jarrett]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>jason@thejarretts.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Fri Mar 05 03:02:35 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Fri Mar 05 03:02:35 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Ok. You need help. My first parse is that you need cash and accommodation in Washington. Is there a hotel that could benefit from you staying there and talking about it. Young, hip place that might help you out? Going to try and help, not sure how, watch twitter.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Fri Mar 05 03:25:49 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Fri Mar 05 03:25:49 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Hi Lloyd... just chipped in ??20 &amp; RT'd. Thanks again for running @metrotwin last night. Look forward to the outputs. Stay bold.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Fri Mar 05 03:30:34 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Fri Mar 05 03:30:34 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Thanks Jason - we had an intro to just such a place in New York and started talking but e-mails weren't replied to :(  Always ready to try again though.  Thanks for all the tweet love!]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Ian B]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>sachanian@aol.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Fri Mar 05 08:04:20 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Fri Mar 05 08:04:20 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Lloydy, just had a look at accn in DC.  Have you tried YHA?  Address is 1009, 11st NW, Washington DC 20001. tel 1-202-737-23333, washingtonDC@hiusa.org.  Single room $69 per night.  Don't know if that is any help at all.  Try www.hihostels.com.  I also hate the word 'should'.  My definition is &quot;inactivity with implied blame&quot;.  All the best amigo, as we used to say in The Mob, 'no plan survives first contact with the enemy'. Strap on yer helmet &amp; fight thru old friend.  cheers Ian]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Crossing the border; geographically and virtually</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/crossing-the-border-geographically-and-virtua</link>	<pubDate>Sun Feb 28 20:51:01 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Condon]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/crossing-the-border-geographically-and-virtua</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;">I spent Saturday on a train from Toronto in Canada to Albany-Rensselear in New York State. &nbsp; It???s apparently very pretty as the route takes you down the Hudson Valley.&nbsp; But in the aftermath of the biggest and coldest snowstorm of the winter; all I could see was low cloud, and not very far through a grey, misty and very snowy landscape. &nbsp;</span></div><p /><div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;">When we got to Niagara Falls and the Border, we were held for a long time while US Customs and Border Protection checked everybody and everything.&nbsp; I was turned off the train with the other foreigners - and carefully, politely and quietly examined.&nbsp; It was interesting to watch them together; about 5 or 6 officers, working as a team.&nbsp; One of the officers requested the passport of the person sitting next to me on the bench in the waiting area.&nbsp; He took it into the office and when he came back, stood some 3 yards or so away, held up the passport and looked, really looked, at the picture and then even more intently at the person.&nbsp; I noticed his eyes; hard and questioning.&nbsp; He was obviously going through some protocol asking himself ???<i>Is this really the person in the passport???? </i>And all of a sudden, he came to a decision, the tension in his stance reduced marginally yet the alert intensity remained. &nbsp;</span></div><p /><div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;">After I had been allowed back on the train with a stamp in my passport (charge $6), I could still see through into the waiting area and beyond that into the office with the computers, cameras and fingerprint machines. The tinted train window partly covered with melting snow obscured any detail and I looked out of the corner of my eye; partly because I didn???t want to look but mostly because I didn???t think the watchers would want to be watched.&nbsp; The lack of detail helped see the patterns of movement and the flow of the work.&nbsp; Very focused,&nbsp; confident in their competent and measured approach.&nbsp; Concentrated in their watchfulness.</span></div><p /><div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;">On the train, some people were getting restless at the time all this was taking.&nbsp; Mostly people who were on the train because they???d been stranded since Thursday by cancelled flights and who were keen to get home.&nbsp; The train guard shrugged - ???It???s typical, neither slower nor quicker than usual, just typical.???&nbsp; A smoke break was announced and I clambered off the train onto the trackbed - just to&nbsp; look and walk in the snow.&nbsp; And&nbsp; I made this video:</span></div><p /><div style=""><object height="360" width="480"><param name="allowfullscreen" value="true" /><param name="allowscriptaccess" value="always" /><param name="movie" value="http://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=9802741&amp;server=vimeo.com&amp;show_title=0&amp;show_byline=0&amp;show_portrait=0&amp;color=ffffff&amp;fullscreen=1" /><embed allowfullscreen="true" src="http://vimeo.com/moogaloop.swf?clip_id=9802741&server=vimeo.com&show_title=0&show_byline=0&show_portrait=0&color=ffffff&fullscreen=1" allowscriptaccess="always" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="360" width="480"></embed></object></div><p /><div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;"><b>Crossing a virtual borde</b>r</span></div><p /><div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;">The virtual border is, of course, a fanciful thought.&nbsp; But since I got to North America, the internet has been a bit in short supply.&nbsp; On grounds of extreme cost more than availability; especially the data charges on the iPhone.&nbsp; It costs ??6 a MB for data, voice calls are ??1.90 a minute and each text is the equivalent of 4 ???normal??? texts.&nbsp; To reduce the cost, I bought a data ???bolt-on??? for ??50 which gives me a ???deal??? of ??1 per MB until it runs out.&nbsp; Which won???t take very long.&nbsp; O2 sends warning texts frequently reminding that an iPhone using data consumes up to 1 MB per minute.&nbsp; I can???t understand how it can possibly cost that much and that these charges reflect the real costs of service provision. &nbsp;</span></div><p /><div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;">The last time I was in the USA would be about 4 years ago - at a conference in Dallas with WiFi at the conference and in the hotel.&nbsp; Then, while travelling, I used a mobile phone as a modem and was careful.&nbsp; In any event, there wasn???t the constant connectedness that that many of us assume is the norm now. &nbsp;</span></div><p /><div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;">And long ago, when the dotcoms were in mid-boom and President Clinton spoke at a tech conference I was at in San Francisco, my communications costs to dial-up back to a Lotus Notes server in London were higher than my hotel bill (and would be again if I switched on data roaming on my iPhone...). &nbsp;</span></div><p /><div style=""><span style="letter-spacing: 0.0px;">It???s come as a bit of a shock to me how much I miss the internet.&nbsp; While awake, I???m pretty much connected most of the time. &nbsp; And even when I???m asleep, various devices are storing stuff for me to look at later.&nbsp; Except there???s no later.&nbsp; It???s all on the other side of the border. &nbsp;</span></div><p /><div style="">And this morning, I made this Audioboo:</div><p /><div style=""><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=An+%27old+school%27+podcast+experience&amp;mp3Time=12.43pm+28+Feb+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F101338-an-old-school-podcast-experience.mp3&amp;mp3Author=brian_condon&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F101338-an-old-school-podcast-experience" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/101338-an-old-school-podcast-experience.mp3">http://audioboo.fm/boos/101338-an-old-school-podcast-experience.mp3</a>">Listen!</object></div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I spent Saturday on a train from Toronto in Canada to Albany-Rensselear in New York State. It???s apparently very pretty as the route takes you down the Hudson Valley. But in the aftermath of the biggest and coldest snowstorm of the winter; all I ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sun Feb 28 20:51:01 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>First sight of the south</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/first-sight-of-the-south</link>	<pubDate>Wed Mar 10 13:53:01 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/first-sight-of-the-south</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='164' poster='http://getfile9.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/NyvlC10lW6BnVnXb6VC3KcXNac0K0F7Nl2IaMZiPmp9zojpnRSSROqpLssDi/first_glimpse_of_the_south.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile8.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/NyvlC10lW6BnVnXb6VC3KcXNac0K0F7Nl2IaMZiPmp9zojpnRSSROqpLssDi/first_glimpse_of_the_south.mp4'></source></video></div><p>the light, the buildings, the first glimpses of green,??<p /></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[the light, the buildings, the first glimpses of green,]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Mar 10 13:53:01 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Be a &quot;Sponsor of the Day!&quot;</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/be-a-sponsor-of-the-day</link>	<pubDate>Mon Feb 15 01:04:46 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="fun"><![CDATA[fun]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="fundraising"><![CDATA[fundraising]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="help"><![CDATA[help]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/be-a-sponsor-of-the-day</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-family: arial, sans-serif; border-collapse: collapse;">We have a sponsor of the day package.<p />There are 18 full days that we'll be in the States.&nbsp; So here's the offer.<p />As sponsor of the day you get:<br /><ul><li style="margin-left: 15px;">A blog post before the trip announcing your involvement and describing what you do, how hot/cool/fancy/delicious you are, why people should buy or use your stuff.</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">A blog post on the day reminding our readers/viewers/listeners of your support and how awesome you are.</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">A video blog post of us using, consuming, looking at or talking about your product (and, naturally, it's complete awesomeness) on the day</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Credits in all content produced on the day ("This post/video/audio was created on Brand X day")</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">If you have branded t-shirts, badges or other clothing and can get it to us in time we will wear it all day long (if it's really nice, some of us may sleep in it).</li><li style="margin-left: 15px;">Attendance at a special supporters party on our return including the first screening of our documentary.</li></ul><br />We hope that you'll understand that you don't get editorial control of other content posted during the day - we're looking to work with people who know they can trust us to do the right thing.<p />All for &pound;1,250 (&pound;1,750 for the 5 days we're actually attending SXSW - 12th-16th March)<p />And you can take as many days as you like and you can choose the day that you sponsor.&nbsp; First come, first served - ie the earlier you confirm, the wider choice of days you'll have. &nbsp;The itinerary is on the wiki. &nbsp;Details of the latter part of the trip will be confirmed shortly.<br /></span></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[We have a sponsor of the day package.There are 18 full days that we'll be in the States. So here's the offer.As sponsor of the day you get:A blog post before the trip announcing your involvement and describing what you do, how hot/cool/fancy/delic...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Feb 15 01:04:46 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>Daily Story Digest #1</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/daily-story-digest-1</link>	<pubDate>Thu Jul 08 03:31:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="chunking"><![CDATA[chunking]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="dailyemail"><![CDATA[dailyemail]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="digest"><![CDATA[digest]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="remix"><![CDATA[remix]]></category>			<category domain="tag" nicename="stories"><![CDATA[stories]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/daily-story-digest-1</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I'm having a go at using a short daily e-mail to make a sort of illustrated serial out of stories from the trip.?? I'm going to publish a digest of them here every week.?? This is the first.</p><p>If you'd like to get these straight to your mailbox every weekday morning you can <a href="http://eepurl.com/GcpJ" title="mailing list sign-up" target="_blank">sign up here</a>.</p><p>Please help me improve on this - let me know in the comments what you like and what could be better - either about the daily e-mails or this digest format.</p><p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4155897066/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2486/4155897066_fe4b0dd48f_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a></p><p><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"To begin  at the beginning..."</span></p><p>"To begin at the beginning" that's  all I've got in my head, Richard  Burton's voice booming out of one of  those big wooden loudspeakers.?? But  what is the true beginning of this  tale of risk, adventure, romance and  laughter??? Mmmm... well let's just  start with a conversation between friends.?? If we have to backtrack  at  all then we will, but for now let's start with December 3rd 2009.?? We   (assorted members of the <a href="http://tuttleclub.wordpress.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Tuttle Club</a>) are at the <a href="http://www.ica.org.uk/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">ICA</a> celebrating the  completion of some fascinating work  with the British Council's  thinktank, <a href="http://www.counterpoint-online.org/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Counterpoint</a>,  applying our social artistry and consulting  skills to their complex  organisational environment and helping them find  new ways to engage  with people online.?? <p />  We're talking.?? We're tuttlers,  that's  what we do.?? And so the story emerges from a conversation.?? I  say  something like "I want to go to <a href="http://sxsw.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">SXSWi</a> again this year, but I don't  want to just flit in and out.?? Maybe we  could fly to somewhere over on  the east coast and then trek across  somehow."?? Yes! voices are raised.??  Yes! and little eyes light up.?? <a href="http://stevelawson.net/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Steve Lawson</a> talks  about his low-carbon  touring approach.?? Sara Haq reminds us of the <a href="http://www.alexiagoethegallery.com/x/exhibitions.html?exid=31&amp;atid=11" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Overland Project</a>.?? Yes!  we'd be up for something like  that.?? Yes! we could make a movie as we go  along.?? And I have the  familiar sick feeling beginning deep within that  we've started  something that will soon have irresistible momentum.??  Something a bit  scary, but exhilarating.?? A new piece of social art.<p />  Here we go  again...</p><p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4177098428/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm3.staticflickr.com/2496/4177098428_f7d441e757_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a></p><p><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Practicalities"</span></p><p>So we have an idea, a plan, a scheme.  It's exciting and we're all  up for it. Yeah!</p><p>And so to practicalities.  But first we have to  descend through a layer of fantasy practicalities - the cool ways that  someone else once did something quite similar to this but, well, "who  knows unless we try, right?"</p><p>These are not actually  practicalities at all, they're still part of imagining.  They're a  method we use to convince ourselves that we're not crazy even if we've  just had a crazy idea.  They're more justifications than practicalities.   But that's not always a bad thing and anyway they also open you up to  even more audacious possibilities, thus: "Then if we do that, it means  we could probably do this other thing too and that would *totally*  rock."</p><p>We really do need to get down to practicalities though, oh  yes.  Which basically means: "Um. How much is this going to cost?   Where might we get the money? No, really, where?  What do we actually  have that we can depend on? Hmmmmm...this may be trickier than we  thought."</p><p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/paul_clarke/4385860294/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4006/4385860294_f2edb20922_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a></p><p><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"The  Point"</span><p />Days pass, weeks pass... oh. my. goodness! we're at  the point. The point of no return.?? The point of make or break.?? The  time when we decide whether we're going to do this thing or slink off  into the February gloom and start planning for something else, something  less daring, something more boring.<p />Of course, three months down  the line, we all know that we pushed ahead, pulled ourselves up by our  bootstraps and went for it.?? But there really was a time when I didn't  know if we were going or not.?? In truth, this "point" stretched out over  a few weeks, and, at least from my own point of view, the period of  uncertainty didn't really end until I was sitting on Long Beach enjoying  the Californian spring sunshine.?? But in London, in February, Brian,  Heather and I had to decide whether to pull the plug or to embrace the  uncertainty, to set off and let the story unfold, even if that involved  spending our own money and a lot of "whistling in the dark".<p />Well  I wrote in the <a href="http://tuttleclub.wordpress.com/2009/04/09/tuttle-club-annual-report-2009/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">first Tuttle Annual Report:</a> "<em>We don't know how all of  this will turn out. We've never known, to be honest, but at times when  we had to make a decision (like moving location to the ICA for example) I  was happy to hold the uncertainty on the group's behalf and say that  while I didn't know what was going to happen next, I was sure it would  be OK and that I would do everything in my power to ensure that it was  OK. It's been important for me to establish from the start that I didn't  have all the answers.</em>"<p />And that seemed to fit here too.?? So,  y'know, we went.<p />(photo credit: <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/paul_clarke/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Paul Clarke</a>)</p><p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4379079450/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4061/4379079450_fec04568dc_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a></p><p><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"The  Kindness of Strangers"</span><p />Dealing with uncertainty was not  just about taking a deep breath and jumping in.<p />This diagram was  an attempt to draw together what we knew and didn't know before we  started the trip.?? My name and Brian's name in red, for example, means  we didn't know where we were going to stay.?? This all worked out more  beautifully than we could have imagined but that's a story for another  day.?? The blue bits are what we knew about where we would hang out - and  if we didn't know where, then who was helping.<p />So this doesn't  acknowledge the help we got from people before we started.?? People we  didn't know at all, who just popped up in our facebook and twitter  streams offering help.?? <a href="http://www.stephaniefrost.net/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Stephanie Frost</a> in Atlanta, Georgia was one of them -  organising a tweetup in a bar for us and persuading Mike at <a href="http://www.ignitionalley.com/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Ignition Alley</a> to  let us hang out there all day.?? I didn't get the importance of this at  first, though I was amazed?? and appreciative of all the work people like  Stephanie did for us, I was still wanting to be as self-reliant as  possible - I saw it as a bug, not a feature.?? Later on, I would see that  relying on the kindness of strangers, giving people the opportunity to  do something useful and pleasurable and interesting was a vital part of  keeping the flow going and the more we asked for, the more we were  given.<p />So thank you, all of you, not just for what you did, but  for helping me learn that lesson.</p><p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4401502243"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4041/4401502243_cd5098d06a_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a></p><p><span class="title" style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold; color: #000080; font-family: Trebuchet MS; line-height: 150%;">"Wanderers"</span><p />  In typical style, I've blundered into telling you the story  without introducing you to the splendid cast of characters.?? This is <a href="http://digital-citizen.co.uk/wordpress/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Brian Condon</a>.??  I met Brian at Tuttle about 18 months ago - he is typical of the  fascinating people that Tuttle has introduced me too.?? Very clever,  curious, always on the go.?? He showed me the plans for what has become  the <a href="http://creative-collaboration.org.uk/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">Centre  for Creative Collaboration</a> (#C4CC) soon after we met.?? I smiled and  nodded and told him to let me know how I could help if it ever got off  the ground.?? We then worked together on the <a href="http://tuttleclub.wordpress.com/2009/07/15/our-first-consulting-gig/" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">first Tuttle Consulting gig</a> and as a strategy consulting  old-timer, he sees how radical and powerful this approach can be.?? He  does great <a href="http://audioboo.fm/brian_condon" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">audioboos</a>.<p />  Brian and I both have migrants in our heritage.?? You can tell from  our names that we're not from round here.?? So it shouldn't be  surprising that we found ourselves rambling across a big country.<p />  Brian set out first.?? He was our scout, going off to see <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/social-art-and-healthcare-metaphors" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">interesting things in Toronto</a> to help think about #C4CC  before heading south-east into the Land of the Free.?? I first got a real  taste that we were going on a journey and we'd be writing about it,  y'know like real travel writers, when I saw <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/crossing-the-border-geographically-and-virtua" style="color: #800000; text-decoration: underline; font-weight: normal;">this post pop up</a> from Brian just after he crossed the  border from Canada.?? I was also hit with the realisation of how long our  journey was going to be and how far away it all seemed.?? <p />Sitting  in London, on a chilly February day looking at pictures from a man  surrounded by snow,?? I started to sweat.</p><p>TO BE CONTINUED...</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I'm having a go at using a short daily e-mail to make a sort of illustrated serial out of stories from the trip. I'm going to publish a digest of them here every week. This is the first. If you'd like to get these straight to your mailbox every we...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Jul 08 03:31:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name>daily-story-digest-1</wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>A little Canadian perspective</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/a-little-canadian-perspective</link>	<pubDate>Wed Jan 27 16:32:46 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/a-little-canadian-perspective</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I've always wanted to travel across the US, and to do it by train? Magic.&nbsp;I first encountered Lloyd's cultural conversations as part of Counterpoint and felt inspired by the depth and breadth of conversation. When I heard about the planned journey across the US to lead more of these conversations, I jumped at the chance to be a part of it. Not only am I facinated by the experience and the conversations that will take place, but as a filmmaker, I'm excited to be able to capture it on film.</p><p>Tonight I brainstormed with my DP, Michelle,&nbsp;about what we could do and capture as we travelled through the country. Capturing the tuttlers (us included) and the conversations are very important, yes, but being there, talking about culture, we want to experience even more.&nbsp; So if we can arrange it, we'd love to speak to a new immigrant and a multi-generational individual/ family in each city. Time allowing, we'd speak to people in their own homes or a place in the city that represents their city/ their culture in the city &ndash; whatever helps them identify themselves in the community &ndash; basically where ever they feel represents their culture, their home.</p><p>Beyond that, the most exciting part of the cultural conversations is my place in them.&nbsp; Michelle and I are both Canadians and so in these US - UK conversations, where do we belong? Growing up in Canada, we were fed daily doses of US television and ads and I've lived in England for 8 years now. Though I still sound Canadian, my language is peppered with Britishisms so no one is sure where to place me. And in some ways, neither can I.&nbsp; So maybe this journey will help me find a bit more about where I sit amongst these countries where we all speak English but our worlds often feel miles apart.</p><p>So do you know anyone in the countries we're visiting who might want to be interviewed individually? Or show us around the place they call home so we can know a bit more about their culture?&nbsp;Your thoughts would be most welcome!</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I've always wanted to travel across the US, and to do it by train? Magic. I first encountered Lloyd's cultural conversations as part of Counterpoint and felt inspired by the depth and breadth of conversation. When I heard about the planned journey...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Jan 27 16:32:46 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>mail@taylordavidson.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Wed Jan 27 18:33:42 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Wed Jan 27 18:33:42 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[What kind of questions do you want to ask?  What do you want to learn from the conversations?As I told Lloyd, let's talk about when and where and I'll help however I can, especially in DC and New Orleans.]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Feb 04 21:25:42 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Feb 04 21:25:42 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I want to find learn about how people belong to the places they call home.  Are their perceptions of the world built by their culture and how, if you are transplanted to a new culture, are you able to combine your own culture with your new culture or do you want to? Thats one part.  The other part would be about perception - what you think about a place and if, by conversing openly across cultures, can that perception change. The main focus will be between US/UK/Canadian cultures in all it's diversity.  Though we are all from countries whose official languages are English, what has led us to be so culturally different?Basically I want to interview a person born and raised in each city and a person who now lives that city who moved there later in their life. Anyone you think would be good to be interviewed, I'd love to hear!]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Mon Feb 08 05:17:10 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Mon Feb 08 05:17:10 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Hi Heather, are you still looking for people to interview? I have strong ties in all of those cities and am thinking of some who have particularly interesting (e)migration stories. Drop me a line if you're interested! kue dot rose at gmail dot com]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Mon Feb 08 17:04:08 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Mon Feb 08 17:04:08 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Thanks so much!  I've sent an email your way so let me know if you need any more info. :)]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Celebrate St Pat's the Muff-a-lotta way in NOLA!</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/celebrate-st-pats-the-muff-a-lotta-way-in-nol</link>	<pubDate>Sat Mar 13 14:14:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Condon]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/celebrate-st-pats-the-muff-a-lotta-way-in-nol</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='386' poster='http://getfile1.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/GIggdjaqpGmxEklsiFxobpoIlafusrJkxlblBtvuwicvbBqdDgnuuhHIbkHp/IMG_0071.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile9.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/GIggdjaqpGmxEklsiFxobpoIlafusrJkxlblBtvuwicvbBqdDgnuuhHIbkHp/IMG_0071.mp4'></source></video></div></p><p><div class='p_embed p_image_embed'><a href="http://getfile7.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/msHbHonDxHHdgkHefgjuCDDuFrxGveqfyqjlniDanbaogpeyCitgaewEmraw/IMG_0072.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0072" height="667" src="http://getfile8.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/msHbHonDxHHdgkHefgjuCDDuFrxGveqfyqjlniDanbaogpeyCitgaewEmraw/IMG_0072.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a><a href="http://getfile6.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/ltmizaCDDhIcxobkqwsDmnscesnzfCyFahudniAhfAffHuIvIIxjpzDgIkIG/IMG_0073.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0073" height="667" src="http://getfile4.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/ltmizaCDDhIcxobkqwsDmnscesnzfCyFahudniAhfAffHuIvIIxjpzDgIkIG/IMG_0073.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a><a href="http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/qnoChtFmmxxAidasCvqyuoHwApxDnbItgDhBzlfAGFuhlFzhjitdFrwxgeAi/IMG_0074.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0074" height="667" src="http://getfile3.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/qnoChtFmmxxAidasCvqyuoHwApxDnbItgDhBzlfAGFuhlFzhjitdFrwxgeAi/IMG_0074.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a><a href="http://getfile9.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/bjHabDlksAgcdzFxHdznyaBnnaIcsCjBnJaGjtoqgxdEvyJqaFcwkreHBvoG/IMG_0075.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0075" height="375" src="http://getfile8.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/bjHabDlksAgcdzFxHdznyaBnnaIcsCjBnJaGjtoqgxdEvyJqaFcwkreHBvoG/IMG_0075.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a><a href="http://getfile1.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/bbqcFDcwcybvCjGBgjzbczdakfaGqAmutwgykdsmuHrkjjuzCgDgeusdkrxu/IMG_0076.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0076" height="667" src="http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/bbqcFDcwcybvCjGBgjzbczdakfaGqAmutwgykdsmuHrkjjuzCgDgeusdkrxu/IMG_0076.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a><a href="http://getfile1.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/cAytqqkBkeGezHlqekpCxavJbbbxfEelHkwCrBJynljkxioebIbCCCgabolg/IMG_0077.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0077" height="667" src="http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/cAytqqkBkeGezHlqekpCxavJbbbxfEelHkwCrBJynljkxioebIbCCCgabolg/IMG_0077.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a><a href="http://getfile8.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/ayDyqyztaqffzrHmwomwEACFArgDbcgjgdIcyBDsGxIxEnkqJevCqentgwqF/IMG_0078.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0078" height="667" src="http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/ayDyqyztaqffzrHmwomwEACFArgDbcgjgdIcyBDsGxIxEnkqJevCqentgwqF/IMG_0078.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a><a href="http://getfile7.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/HwtAryuloFBafruxGvjhzvgqeyhewHxrbHwbIorfoxrmDsAdpnhucFdEcbnk/IMG_0079.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0079" height="667" src="http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/HwtAryuloFBafruxGvjhzvgqeyhewHxrbHwbIorfoxrmDsAdpnhucFdEcbnk/IMG_0079.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a><a href="http://getfile6.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/JosIIBCneFpdDaJgpExfsEamkyepCpFspiEdGJrnjtGkjCxFhgiIGarGvedC/IMG_0080.jpg.scaled1000.jpg"><img alt="Img_0080" height="667" src="http://getfile1.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/JosIIBCneFpdDaJgpExfsEamkyepCpFspiEdGJrnjtGkjCxFhgiIGarGvedC/IMG_0080.jpg.scaled500.jpg" width="500" /></a></div></p><p><span style="font-size: medium;">I also recorded a series of Audioboo - which I'm embedding here.&nbsp; </span></p><p><span style="font-size: medium;">In the first, everyone is getting ready - the Dance Troupe are tense, some nervous, all getting 'psyched-up' for the performance; concentrating on the practicalities of getting ready.&nbsp; Much laughter and joking to cover the nervousness.</span></p><p><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=A+New+Orleans+dance+troupe+gets+ready+to+celebrate+St+Pat%27s+-+Muff-a-lottas&amp;mp3Time=06.04pm+12+Mar+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F104824-a-new-orleans-dance-troupe-gets-ready-to-celebrate-st-pat-s-muff-a-lottas.mp3&amp;mp3Author=brian_condon&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F104824-a-new-orleans-dance-troupe-gets-ready-to-celebrate-st-pat-s-muff-a-lottas" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/104824-a-new-orleans-dance-troupe-gets-ready-to-celebrate-st-pat-s-muff-a-lottas.mp3">Listen!</a></object></p><p><span style="font-size: medium;">In the second, we're assembling and on the parade - I was pulling the float with Graham; we had technical problems which had to be worked on by a couple of the 'Bun Warmers' (male members of the troupe) as the float moved along at a brisk walking pace.&nbsp; The dancers' adrenaline was flowing and the energy high as they danced - you can see this in the video above.</span></p><p><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=In+the+parade+in+NOLA+with+the+Muff-a-lottas+%23tuttle2texas&amp;mp3Time=07.21pm+12+Mar+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F105168-in-the-parade-in-nola-with-the-muff-a-lottas-tuttle2texas.mp3&amp;mp3Author=brian_condon&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F105168-in-the-parade-in-nola-with-the-muff-a-lottas-tuttle2texas" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/105168-in-the-parade-in-nola-with-the-muff-a-lottas-tuttle2texas.mp3">Listen!</a></object></p><p><span style="font-size: medium;">In the third, made this morning in Houston TX, I wanted to capture how the crowd reacted to the Muff-a-lottas and how it felt to be part of it.<br /></span></p><p><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3Title=After+the+Party+-+Muffa-a-lottas+rule%21+%23tuttle2texas&amp;mp3Time=09.46am+13+Mar+2010&amp;mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F105173-after-the-party-muffa-a-lottas-rule-tuttle2texas.mp3&amp;mp3Author=brian_condon&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F105173-after-the-party-muffa-a-lottas-rule-tuttle2texas" /><a href="http://audioboo.fm/boos/105173-after-the-party-muffa-a-lottas-rule-tuttle2texas.mp3">Listen!</a></object></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I also recorded a series of Audioboo - which I'm embedding here. In the first, everyone is getting ready - the Dance Troupe are tense, some nervous, all getting 'psyched-up' for the performance; concentrating on the practicalities of getting ready...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Sat Mar 13 14:14:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item><item>	<title>My ponderings from Boston</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/my-ponderings-from-boston</link>	<pubDate>Thu Mar 04 22:11:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/my-ponderings-from-boston</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is day three of Tuttle2Texas and I&rsquo;ve already have heard enough stories to last a lifetime. I think I could have stayed in Boston for weeks and still not have enough. One of the things I&rsquo;m very glad of (though takes more time to organize) is staying with people in all of the cities we are visiting. In Boston, we stayed with John and Jay. John works in tech at Tech Superpowers and Jay is a lawyer who works with bio-tech patents. They have a beautiful daughter Maggie who is only 2 and is smarter then some adults I know (no offence to anyone out there). They also have 8 cats which worried me immensely due to my allergies but since my allergist is very sweet, I got a bunch of steroids that kept me from reacting. Yes. I&rsquo;m doing Tuttle2Texas on steroids. <p /><a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pa_DOThr8BQ" target="&amp;rdquo;_blank&amp;rdquo;">www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pa_DOThr8BQ </a><p />Last night John was making syrup out of the Sugar Maple sap he collected from the tree in the back of their new house. As we talked, he not only showed me how to make my own syrup but he gave me some insight into his values. Though he is immersed in tech and the tech world, he consciously puts aside time for the lost arts. The recipes of our grandparents, a more hands on way of doing things. A time where you can slow down and just enjoy the world. I feel the same way &ndash; though I don&rsquo;t really show that. Since getting my iPhone, it is always to hand. The moment I wake up, I&rsquo;m on it and communicating to the world. Is this a good thing or am I losing a bit of my past and my culture by becoming so entrenched in social media? <p />Not only did we get to try to the homemade maple syrup (which tasted fresh out of a tree but in a good way), but John toasted up some homemade walnut bread for Michelle and I to munch on while we talked later than we thought we&rsquo;d be able to stay up to. This all day filming is tiring. So much so, we left no energy to actually interview John and Jay which I regret &ndash; though the conversations we had were equally invaluable. <p />When we said goodbye to John last night, he gave us each a bear hug. The kind you give to an old friend. This morning we left behind new friends with a promise that we&rsquo;d come back and when we did, we can stay with them whenever we want. No matter how nice hotels are, I&rsquo;ve never got that from them. <p /><p /><object type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="129" width="400"><param name="movie" value="http://boos.audioboo.fm/swf/fullsize_player.swf" /><param name="scale" value="noscale" /><param name="salign" value="lt" /><param name="bgColor" value="#FFFFFF" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="window" /><param name="FlashVars" value="mp3=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F102519-thanks-fearboy-jay-tuttle2texas.mp3&amp;mp3Author=Propgrl&amp;mp3LinkURL=http%3A%2F%2Faudioboo.fm%2Fboos%2F102519-thanks-fearboy-jay-tuttle2texas&amp;mp3Title=Thanks+%40fearboy+%26+Jay%21+%23tuttle2texas&amp;mp3Time=02.31pm+04+Mar+2010" /></object></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[This is day three of Tuttle2Texas and I???ve already have heard enough stories to last a lifetime. I think I could have stayed in Boston for weeks and still not have enough. One of the things I???m very glad of (though takes more time to organize) is ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Mar 04 22:11:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Patrick]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Sat Mar 06 12:23:14 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Sat Mar 06 12:23:14 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[That's a rather lovely post! Just so you know...]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Starting Week 0</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/starting-week-0</link>	<pubDate>Mon Feb 22 13:05:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>				<category domain="tag" nicename="progress"><![CDATA[progress]]></category>		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/starting-week-0</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4379079450/"><img class="posterous_download_image" src="http://farm5.staticflickr.com/4061/4379079450_fec04568dc_b.jpg" border="0" width="500" /></a></p><p /><div>I love this bit of any project - I thrive on the mix of certainty and uncertainty. &nbsp;You're certain that you're really truly going to launch/ship/do that thing but still uncertain over how everything will get done and just how it will all work out. &nbsp;I always like to call it Week Zero.</div><p /><div>As I've taken my project life more and more into the realm of social art, it's just shifted a lot more into the uncertain. &nbsp;And this project is no different. &nbsp;With Tuttle, in the beginning, there was a time when I had to just say "OK, I'm going to show up here every week. &nbsp;I don't know how it's going to work. I don't know how I'm going to make any money, but I'm going to commit to a couple of hours every Friday, making sure that it happens and that people know it's here." &nbsp;I had no idea how it would turn out from there, and if I did have any ideas, what actually happened went far beyond my limited imagination.</div><p /><div>So we're committed. &nbsp;We have the things in place to get started. &nbsp;We are all flying to North America, Brian's going to get there a bit earlier. &nbsp;On March 2nd (as I'm getting used to calling it - instead of "The Second of March"),&nbsp;Heather, Michelle and I are coming in from London and we're proud to announce that Dana is coming down from St John's to join us for the Boston and NYC. &nbsp;And we have <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/were-doing-tuttle-boston-on-march-3rd">a great place to hang out in Boston</a>. &nbsp;And there are lots of other bits in place - the flow chart above shows me roughly what we know and don't know. &nbsp;</div><p /><div>There's lots of uncertainty about where Brian and I will be staying because we're middle-aged, stubborn, British men who would probably rather stay awake all night in a roach-infested $50-a-night motel than impose on the kindness and home comforts of a friendly couchsurfer. &nbsp;And we don't all have passes to SXSWi yet or train passes. &nbsp;However we've secured one &pound;3,000 package of support and are finalising one for &pound;1250, we're having our party tomorrow, we have some nice kit from Nokia and Canon and there are still open doors on other potential <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/be-a-sponsor-of-the-day">sponsors of the day</a> (please twist corporate arms where you can but not so hard that they're unable to sign-off some cash for us).</div><p /><div>We've had &pound;50 today in personal donations - that makes my heart sing even more, thank you <a href="http://twitter.com/frankie_ecap">@frankie_ecap</a>, <a href="http://twitter.com/tessybritton">@tessybritton</a>, <a href="http://twitter.com/artsmonkey1">@ArtsMonkey1</a> and <a href="http://twitter.com/fj">@fj</a>&nbsp;&nbsp;(STOP PRESS: and while I was writing this post <a href="http://twitter.com/darenBBC">@darenBBC</a> )- I will send a postcard from <a href="http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/nailing-down-the-itinerary-part-1">any of our stop-off cities</a> on the route to anyone who plops at least &pound;5 or $10 in our <a href="http://tuttle2texas.chipin.com">fund</a>.</div><p /><div>But the main thing I want to show with this, is that, just as with Tuttle (and arguably everything in life), there's no such thing as failure - it's all part of the adventure and so we will continue to collect money and raise funds right up until the end of the trip if that's what we need to do - in fact I shan't be surprised if some potential sponsors are still holding back until they can actually see how much noise we really make - which fine - I'd much people gave us money becasue of what we actually do than what forecast numbers we can come up with to satisfy the ROI crowd.</div><p /><div><a href="http://tuttle2texas.chipin.com">Chip in, my darlings</a> :)</div><p /><div><object height="250" width="250"><param name="movie" value="http://widget.chipin.com/widget/id/d38e54751b2c1a96" /><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always" /><param name="wmode" value="transparent" /><embed src="http://widget.chipin.com/widget/id/d38e54751b2c1a96" wmode="transparent" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" height="250" width="250"></embed></object><p /> </div>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I love this bit of any project - I thrive on the mix of certainty and uncertainty. You're certain that you're really truly going to launch/ship/do that thing but still uncertain over how everything will get done and just how it will all work out. ...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Mon Feb 22 13:05:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Mon Feb 22 13:12:12 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Mon Feb 22 13:12:12 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[And thanks to @DarenBBC who just donated about 30 seconds ago!  I'm so grateful for all the support.  I'm getting my postcard writing skills up to scratch as we speak!]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>New York City roundup</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/new-york-city-roundup</link>	<pubDate>Wed Mar 10 12:44:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/new-york-city-roundup</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/lloyd-davis/4422816612/" title="tuttle2texas by Lloyd Davis, on Flickr"><img src="http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4042/4422816612_b1d0768541.jpg" height="333" alt="tuttle2texas" width="500" /></a></p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;"><strong>Metrotwin</strong></p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">I facilitated a group discussion on Thursday evening in New York about <a href="http://metrotwin.com">Metrotwin</a>, British Airways online social network for people who love New York and London. For the utmost fullness of disclosure I was involved in the original conceptual development of metrotwin with Many by Many and metrotwin paid for my flights to and from the States for this trip.</p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">We had people who contribute to the site as bloggers as well as other wise digital folk. The substance of the conversation was subject to an NDA for the participants &ndash; they came up with some really interesting insights and ideas for future development &ndash; but I think it was also interesting as an example of how sites that use the power of social interactions online really need to engage in face to face social interactions too. The things I was reminded of, beyond the conversations we had about the state of the art in social networking were:</p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">&nbsp;</p><ul><li>Some people like to show off what they know and who they are &ndash; often these are the same people who write a particular kind of blog &ndash; one with a strong identity and lots of links.</li><li>Others like to sit and listen and come up with an interesting analysis or synthesis of what is being said.</li><li>People who like being on social networking sites do (generally) like other people and want to help and be useful. An obvious outcome of this meeting is to continue to get metrotwin bloggers and users together to swap stories and build the relationships.</li><li>The smallest or shortest contributions can be just as valuable as the long and rambling ones. Some people just need fewer words to express what they have to say.</li><li>Whichever people come are the right people &ndash; this is one of Harrison Owen's principles for Open Space but it's important to remember in more formal situations too &ndash; I worried at first that a couple of people I'd invited couldn't make it, even though I knew they'd make a great contribution to the conversation On this occasion, it wasn't to be, but who am I to say for sure that the conversation was poorer?</li></ul><p>&nbsp;</p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">&nbsp;</p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;"><strong>New Work City</strong></p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">On Friday afternoon, Brian, Dana and I dropped into Tony Bacigalupo's <a href="http://nwcny.com">New Work City</a> coworking space. This was my first experience of a US coworking environment. Guess what? I felt right at home :) I haven't been in any US office spaces before apart from BBH the night before, and that's well y'know, an advertising agency... lovely but not that different from the London office (apart from the stunning view of the rest of Manhattan from the 19<sup>th</sup> floor) New Work City has a suite within an office building and my first reaction was it looked like something from the FBI &ndash; characterless corridors with tightly shut doors &ndash; everything looks the same and very little signage. However we finally found the suite for NWC, said hello to Tony and his coworkers and settled in. It actually felt to me quite like being in a small University computer lab (at least like the ones I hung out in as a student) where everyone knows each other.</p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">We didn't have long and our main needs were mains power and wifi which we gratefully received but it was really nice to have somewhere else to be for a bit and I managed to knock my mailbox down to about 5 or 6 items &ndash; somehow I felt much more productive and ready to get stuff done there than I had done, sitting alone in my hotel room.</p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Metrotwin I facilitated a group discussion on Thursday evening in New York about Metrotwin, British Airways online social network for people who love New York and London. For the utmost fullness of disclosure I was involved in the original concept...]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Wed Mar 10 12:44:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>			<wp:comment>			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>			<wp:comment_author_email>andrew.scott@rummble.com</wp:comment_author_email>			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>			<wp:comment_date>Thu Mar 11 13:10:12 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Mar 11 13:10:12 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Would love to have a chat about MetroTwin - we spoke to BA last year about a white label version of Rummble for them, they were eager but then their budgets were cut...cheers!]]></wp:comment_content>			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>		</wp:comment>	</item><item>	<title>Lloyd plays in NOLA and Taylor takes us for a spin...</title>	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/lloyd-plays-in-nola</link>	<pubDate>Thu Mar 11 12:00:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Brian Condon]]></dc:creator>			<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/lloyd-plays-in-nola</guid>	<description></description>	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='386' poster='http://getfile2.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/kpvgkeGBsBgBHrrmofAuxmbmqjohifCllFwouvhHJGBAwtAosfHxyDCooruG/IMG_0069.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile1.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/kpvgkeGBsBgBHrrmofAuxmbmqjohifCllFwouvhHJGBAwtAosfHxyDCooruG/IMG_0069.mp4'></source></video></div></p>The day before, we spent a fab day with Taylor Davidson who told us about NOLAlicious (<a href="http://www.nolalicious.com">www.nolalicious.com</a>) <p><div class='p_embed p_video_embed'><video autobuffer='autobuffer' height='217' poster='http://getfile7.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/EalkCrgdBmFDlDaksjsIJbjfxmbpouBCztJFfFvuIJpFvAjydlwtiylAEqEg/IMG_0081.png' width='290'><source src='http://getfile5.posterous.com/getfile/files.posterous.com/tuttle2texas/EalkCrgdBmFDlDaksjsIJbjfxmbpouBCztJFfFvuIJpFvAjydlwtiylAEqEg/IMG_0081.mp4'></source></video></div></p>]]></content:encoded>	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[The day before, we spent a fab day with Taylor Davidson who told us about NOLAlicious (www.nolalicious.com)]]></excerpt:encoded>		<wp:post_date>Thu Mar 11 12:00:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>	</item></channel></rss>