<item>
	<title>High-level itinerary choices</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/high-level-itinerary-choices</link>
	<pubDate>Sun Jan 17 05:07:25 -0800 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/high-level-itinerary-choices</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[I spent some time this morning on the Amtrak timetable site.  I will never complain about <a href="http://nationalrail.co.uk">nationalrail.co.uk</a> again.  Well I probably will, but when I do so I will likely bear in mind the fact that things could be worse.<p /> Everyone has said to me &quot;You know they really don&#39;t have a train system like Europe&quot; and I&#39;m like &quot;Well duh!&quot; but it wasn&#39;t until I actually started putting real dates and times in that I realised what a constraint travelling by train will be.  Yipeee!  Nonetheless, I am completely committed to making this work by rail.  Loads of people do road trips across the States.  Only a bunch of nutcases from London would attempt to do it on the railroad.<p /> So there&#39;s a decision that needs to be made first of all, which is the overall shape of the trip. What is &quot;firm&quot; is that we take our time to get there, having conversations on the way, we hang out at the festival and then pull together our movie based on whatever happened in the previous week or so. At the moment I have a few alternative ways of doing this in mind:<p /> 1.  The original idea was to return the way we came and use the time we have on the train to reflect a little on our experience and turn it into an interesting narrative.<p />2.  Another suggestion was that instead of heading back east, we carry on across the desert (by train again) through Tucson and up into California, finishing our trip either in San Francisco (where we&#39;re likely to meetup with people from SXSW who flew straight back) or that place further south where we have friends in Long Beach.<p /> 3.  We stick around and finish the movie making in Austin, taking in some of the music festival which starts after interactive, and then fly straight back home from there.<p />Hmmm.... pros and cons, pros and cons]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I spent some time this morning on the Amtrak timetable site. I will never complain about nationalrail.co.uk again. Well I probably will, but when I do so I will likely bear in mind the fact that things could be worse. Everyone has said to me "You ...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Sun Jan 17 05:07:25 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[pollyrt]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Tue Jan 19 05:25:00 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Jan 19 05:25:00 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to following your travels.

You've probably seen this but www.seat61.com/UnitedStates.htm has useful summary info on routes and timings.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Tue Jan 19 05:31:19 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Tue Jan 19 05:31:19 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Yes, thank you that's where I started out and am getting most of my information from now :)]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
</item>
