<item>
	<title>Nailing down the itinerary Part 1</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/nailing-down-the-itinerary-part-1</link>
	<pubDate>Thu Jan 28 15:38:08 -0800 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>
	
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="amtrak"><![CDATA[amtrak]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="itinerary"><![CDATA[itinerary]]></category>
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/nailing-down-the-itinerary-part-1</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Right.&nbsp; Let's come at it from the other end.</p>
<p>We want to be in Austin late on 11th or early on 12th March for the opening.</p>
<p>This means leaving New Orleans on the 11th - it's an 8 or 9 hour drive (Taylor has offered a lift &amp; there may be a bus going) so leaving early on the 11th feels do-able.&nbsp; I had a lingering idea that I'd love to actually roll in to Austin station - I saw it last year and parked it as part of the idea that turned into this year's trip.&nbsp; However, New Orleans has become a solid part of the trip too and insanely enough the timetable suggests that the only way from NOLA to Austin is via (wait for it...) Chicago and if we left NOLA on Thursday 11th, we'd get to Austin on the Saturday.&nbsp; So it's all working out beautifully.&nbsp; I really want to have a full day in New Orleans so that would be the 10th and so we need to arrive on 9th.</p>
<p>So the 9th is a travel day from Atlanta to NOLA leaving Atlanta at 08:38 and arriving in the Big Easy at 19:38 yup a cool 12-hour trip.</p>
<p>Now the trip from Washington to Atlanta is a biggie too - 14 hours overnight.&nbsp; So to be able to leave on the 9th we'll have to arrive on the morning of 8th which means leaving Washington on Sunday night (7th) Train leaves Union Station at 18:30</p>
<p>Our time in Washington then would seem to be Saturday night and Sunday.&nbsp; We could leave New York on Saturday morning and get to Washington after lunch in time for an evening do and then maybe a brunch date on Sunday.</p>
<p>This means our main event will need to be on Friday evening in New York and to make the most of our time there we should arrive on the afternoon of 4th.&nbsp; Boston to NYC is 4 hours - so leaving first thing (there's an 09:40 gets in at 13:50) should get us there OK.</p>
<p>This means an evening event on 3rd in Boston and probably arriving the night before in order to give time for last minute glitches.</p>
<p>Oh, so that means leaving UK on 2nd - earlier than I expected.&nbsp; Which has implications for costs - I just added 3 nights accomodation to the budget... ah well, better to know now.&nbsp; In my head, I now have every project manager I've ever worked with looking at me over the top of their glasses, nodding and saying "I told you so"</p>
<p>so to summarize in reverse order, which is actually the right order:</p>
<p>2nd March Fly London to Boston</p>
<p>3rd March day in Boston for conversations (any Berkman Centre folk up for that?) and a Boston Tuttle in the evening.</p>
<p>4th March 09:40 to NYC arrives 13:50 evening tweetup</p>
<p>5th March day in NYC for conversations and exploration (New Work City and other coworkers?) unconfirmed sponsor event in the evening</p>
<p>6th March 10:05 to Washington, DC arrives 13:25 evening conversation space and tweetup</p>
<p>7th March Brunch conversation spaces, afternoon exploration 18:30 to Atlanta arrives 08:12 the next day</p>
<p>8th March day in Atlanta, conversations, exploration, evening tweetup<p />  9th March 08:38 to New Orleans arrive 19:38<p />  10th March day in NOLA - exploration &amp; conversations in the hands of Mr Taylor Davidson<p />  11th March drive with Taylor to Austin<p /> 12th SXSWi begins - sighs of relief all round</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Right. Let's come at it from the other end. We want to be in Austin late on 11th or early on 12th March for the opening. This means leaving New Orleans on the 11th - it's an 8 or 9 hour drive (Taylor has offered a lift & there may be a bus going) ...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Thu Jan 28 15:38:08 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 15:41:11 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 15:41:11 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Very jealous, sounds like a great trip. Looking forward to Tuttling with you in Texas.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 15:43:23 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 15:43:23 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I think that works - though am starting to think that SXXSW should be the destination.  That it's the climax to the journey though coast to coast is nice it could be a nice north to south journey and then a little fun, more discussion, more bits of having fun, talking, cowboys, then...home.
]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email>mail@taylordavidson.com</wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 16:13:53 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 16:13:53 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Right.  I'll work on a couple things for you in NOLA. Great to hear you're coming.  Remember my car probably only has space for 2, but we'll hack that out :)]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 23:17:24 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 23:17:24 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Sam, I'm trying to see how we can tie things together with other Brits during the trip.  Nonetheless, big thanks for making Tuttle in Texas happen again on the Sunday!]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 23:25:26 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 23:25:26 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Heather, I know.  I'm very drawn though to getting over to the West Coast in order to make the overall shape of the trip be Boston to LA because those are the places where we have strong Tuttle support.  

I also accept that this is a pretty big trip already... and carrying on would bump up the costs because the rail passes are for 15 days or 30 days.  It all comes down for me to how much support we can raise.  

But also remembering that we don't all have to do the same thing all the way.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Thu Jan 28 23:29:40 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Jan 28 23:29:40 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Taylor, capacity noted.  I'm not surprised that the NOLA -&gt; Austin leg is going to be the wildest and most unpredictable.  However, I'm also confident that we can build enough momentum in the next 6 weeks to get us from Louisian-i-a to Texas, no matter how many of us there are]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Fiona Cullinan]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email>fionacullinan@hotmail.com</wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Sun Feb 07 05:09:53 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Sun Feb 07 05:09:53 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Oh ello! I'm flying to Miami and routing either through Atlanta/Birmingham to New Orleans (or direct bus to New Orleans). Might be able to join up with TuttletoTexas for the last leg anyway! PS There's a train from New Orleans to San Antonio then Austin (if that helps).]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
</item>
