<item>
	<title>We're doing Tuttle Boston on March 3rd</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/were-doing-tuttle-boston-on-march-3rd</link>
	<pubDate>Thu Feb 18 00:56:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>
	
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="boston"><![CDATA[boston]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="conversations"><![CDATA[conversations]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="support"><![CDATA[support]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="techsuperpowers"><![CDATA[techsuperpowers]]></category>
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/were-doing-tuttle-boston-on-march-3rd</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/needfire/1219873714/">http://www.flickr.com/photos/needfire/1219873714/</a> <br />photo by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/needfire/" target="_blank">needfire</a></p>
<p>Big thanks to Mike Oh at Tech Superpowers in Boston for &nbsp;saying "mi case es su casa" and helping arrange an evening Tuttle tweetup at the start of our trip.</p>
<p>Mike came to Tuttle in London soon after we moved to the ICA I think and he's a regular visitor when he's in London. &nbsp;He and I talked excitedly about his concept of a Digital Lounge in his <a href="http://www.techsuperpowers.com">Mac Support Shop</a> and the idea of doing Tuttle in Boston. &nbsp;I'm really glad that he both managed to open <a href="http://www.techsuperpowers.com/digilounge">Digilounge</a> and to do several tuttle-esque events there. &nbsp;I'm looking forward to coming over and giving it a bit of London flavour.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Mike has said we can use Digilounge as Tuttle HQ for the day. &nbsp;We're also talking to a certain prestigious business school on the other side of the Charles River about running some conversation spaces so we're going to be busy.</p>
<p>And on Wednesday evening we'll be holding Tuttle Boston there for local folk to come together, get some beer (or coffee!) &amp; nibbles (also generously provided by Mr Oh and his team) and join in some great tuttle-ish conversations.</p>
<p>At the moment Heather, Michelle &amp; I are arriving in Boston at around 1.30 on Tuesday March 2nd and Brian is going to get there a little earlier, we think. &nbsp;We'll take it easy on the Tuesday night while we acclimatise to the different gravity conditions of the USA, 18th Century spelling conventions, escaping the metric system etc. &nbsp;But as we're getting the train to New York City on the Thursday morning Wednesday is the big opportunity to meet up with us, so give us a shout and help us get the trip off to a bostin' start (sorry, couldn't help it...)</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[http://www.flickr.com/photos/needfire/1219873714/ photo by needfire Big thanks to Mike Oh at Tech Superpowers in Boston for saying "mi case es su casa" and helping arrange an evening Tuttle tweetup at the start of our trip. Mike came to Tuttle in ...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Thu Feb 18 00:56:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
