<item>
	<title>Airport bound: #tuttle2texas</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/airport-bound-tuttle2texas</link>
	<pubDate>Tue Mar 02 00:45:47 -0800 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/airport-bound-tuttle2texas</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span style=""><span>So it's beginning today. In some ways it's already began, but now the bags are (over) packed and I'm on a very slow 137 on the way to the Piccadilly line.</span><br /><span></span><br /><span>People have asked me if I am excited. I'm not sure yet. It seems all surreal. And though I do have a calm vaneer about our travels I am worried as well. I think if I was just doing the journey, and leading discussions and taking too long train journeys, that wouldn't worry me as much. But shooting a documentary in 6 cities in 10 days and socially documenting it is making me more naceous than excited I think.</span><br /><span></span><br /><span>Am I ready? No. As usual, the night before travel all technical things that could go wrong did. But it's all par for the course, so I shrug and get on with it.</span><br /><span></span><br /><span>It's a bit strange - for this journey Im using the backpack that I used on my way to England, my first great adventure. I packed all of my belongings in this bag on 31 December, 2001 &amp; started a new life on New Years Day. Now I feel the same - all my favourite clothes &amp; electronics are packed (except my Zi8 which maddingly has decide to play hide &amp; seek with me, and still hasn't been found.) And I'm off on one of the greatest adventures &amp; challenges I've ever been on. There's even a maple leaf on my bag - but that's more because I couldn't get it off. Though, as this whole trip is about culture, it does become a reminder of where I came from.</span><br /><span></span><br /><div><p><img border="0" width="300" /></p></div></span>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[So it's beginning today. In some ways it's already began, but now the bags are (over) packed and I'm on a very slow 137 on the way to the Piccadilly line.People have asked me if I am excited. I'm not sure yet. It seems all surreal. And though I do...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Tue Mar 02 00:45:47 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
