<item>
	<title>Boston to NYC - our first train ride</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/boston-to-nyc-our-first-train-ride</link>
	<pubDate>Thu Mar 04 13:59:39 -0800 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/boston-to-nyc-our-first-train-ride</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">Woah, this is a shaky old train. Difficult to type because the tray is up close to me but anyway it&#39;s better than having it on my lap. The Amtrak trains are like big tin cans, they look like they&#39;re just slats of aluminium stapled together. And this ride south out of Boston feels like it too. Everything rattles and judders.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">It&#39;s snowing outside and we&#39;re getting out of the city and into more countryside space. We just stopped at a station called Route 128 – the train station is named after a road? OK it&#39;s also University Park.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">I&#39;m unreasonably excited about being on an American train. I&#39;ve lived around London and commuted for 20 years. I know what trains are like, and I&#39;m used to the experience. However, this feels weirdly different. The conductor we met was friendly and um, American, confidently in charge, rather than being officious and jobsworthy.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">I realised what it was that I was getting excited about - American rail reminds me of Casey Jones. Casey Jones was to me an exciting and exotic part of my television childhood. Plucky Alan Ladd driving a train regardless of bandits and rockfalls and anything else that might have gotten in his way He always got through. He just did. Anyway he wasn&#39;t a train driver he was an Engineer – American usage, I blame the literal German immigrants – he drives and engine so he must be an engineer. Maybe that&#39;s what we originally meant by engineer too. Maybe i&#39;m jetlagged and I&#39;m writing stuff that I ordinarily wouldn&#39;t let out of my head. And of course now I&#39;ve also got the theme to the show stuck in my head, squeezing out Chatanooga Choo Choo - “Casey Jones, steamin&#39; and a&#39; rollin&#39;”</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Woah, this is a shaky old train. Difficult to type because the tray is up close to me but anyway it's better than having it on my lap. The Amtrak trains are like big tin cans, they look like they're just slats of aluminium stapled together. And th...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Thu Mar 04 13:59:39 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[boofulls]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email> susandavis45@hotmail.com</wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Thu Mar 04 14:48:50 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Thu Mar 04 14:48:50 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[ I told you never go down to the end of town etc and there you are on a tin train wobbling about in America]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
</item>
