<item>
	<title>Asking for help, again</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/asking-for-help-again</link>
	<pubDate>Fri Mar 05 02:54:42 -0800 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/asking-for-help-again</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">In summary: We need practical offers of help and support to keep this trip (but more importantly, ourselves) going. This includes, but is not limited to, bringing in immediate funds from sponsors or other sources. </p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">People ask how the trip is going. It&#39;s going well. But that doesn&#39;t mean that it&#39;s necessarily comfortable. As with other things Tuttle, we got started, rather than waiting for the whole thing to be planned, sorted, pinned down. I think it&#39;s important to keep doing this, to keep showing that stuff can be done differently and to recognise that art, including social art, requires someone to take an audacious step into the unknown.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">I think that mostly when people ask that question, they mean have we raised enough money? And that&#39;s actually quite a difficult question to answer beyond “No”!. Like most creative entrepreneurs we are pulling ourselves up by our bootstraps. We have covered our flights to and from the US in different ways – speaking just for myself, I am being supported by Metrotwin in return for running a workshop for them in NYC and writing a blog post about what they&#39;re doing. Heather and Brian have used savings and credit, at their own risk, to pay for their rail passes and some accommodation. I&#39;ve dug into savings for accommodation for the first few nights. I have a personal rule that I don&#39;t use unsecured credit. I don&#39;t have a credit card. That makes my life much simpler in lots of ways. It also makes it more difficult. I am committed to not incurring any personal unsecured debt during this trip – I find that it makes for quite a creative if sometimes vexing constraint.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">We have agreements for support with a couple of organisations which amount to £3250 though we&#39;re still waiting for that money to come through. And I&#39;ve been thrilled daily by the influx of funds donated by friends and family who just want to help make it happen.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">In order to make the whole thing break even though, we raise at least twice as much as that again. Anything you can do to help us find more sponsors of the day is very welcome.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">Our current prominent issue is that Brian &amp; I don&#39;t know where we&#39;re going to stay in Washington DC yet and I&#39;m relying on money flowing through faster in order to pay for it. Beyond that we had to make the decision that we could not afford right now to book a room on the overnight train to Atlanta on Sunday night and will have to sleep in our seats.  </p><p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">The important thing when asking for help though is not just to present the problem but to be clear where you think others can be of use.  So suggestions of which cool hotels you stayed in in Washington are lovely but essentially an added cognitive overhead for us to deal with.  Offers of somewhere central and free to cheap to stay are much more useful as is finding us a sponsor of the day who can immediately transfer funds.  We&#39;re open to other ways of doing things and believe me we&#39;re grateful for everyone who offers an idea - we just need more in terms of practical help - people who can do things rather than throw more ideas at us. </p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">Yet again, making it up as we go along and staying flexible is an important part of the work. The project is a bit like a piece of improvisational theatre. Before we arrived it was like waiting in the wings for the moment to step on stage, knowing that there&#39;s nothing you can do yet and once you get started, apart from some simple bits of structure you have no idea what&#39;s going to happen.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">So everyday we don&#39;t know what we&#39;re going to do, who we&#39;re going to meet, what might happen at all. To me that&#39;s what makes it worth doing, but I can see that for some people, that makes it hard to understand.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">Right now I&#39;m in the low spot where we&#39;ve made some bold first moves, we&#39;ve got some laughs and the general support of the audience, but I don&#39;t know quite what to do next to keep it all together. The phrase “It&#39;s all part of the adventure” is wearing mighty thin - it&#39;s this point where confidence starts to stray - “Who&#39;s stupid idea was this? What on earth made me think I could make it work? You should have done X, you should have done Y, you should have should have, should have...” </p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">But I&#39;ve been here before believe the only answer is to keep making bold moves , keep showing up to the work and above all rely on help from your fellow actors and the audience – use whatever comes to hand. And the way we get support from the audience (whether that&#39;s the sort of support I think I need or not) is to blog about it, write about it on the internet, do what we do best, talk the thing through – certainly lying in bed at 5am jetlagged and trying to <b>think</b> a solution is only going to get me a headache.</p> <p style="margin-bottom: 0in;">So yeah. “Halp. Plz I needs it”</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[In summary: We need practical offers of help and support to keep this trip (but more importantly, ourselves) going. This includes, but is not limited to, bringing in immediate funds from sponsors or other sources. People ask how the trip is going....]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Fri Mar 05 02:54:42 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Jason Jarrett]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email>jason@thejarretts.com</wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Fri Mar 05 03:02:35 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Fri Mar 05 03:02:35 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Ok. You need help. My first parse is that you need cash and accommodation in Washington. Is there a hotel that could benefit from you staying there and talking about it. Young, hip place that might help you out? Going to try and help, not sure how, watch twitter.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Fri Mar 05 03:25:49 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Fri Mar 05 03:25:49 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Hi Lloyd... just chipped in £20 &amp; RT'd. Thanks again for running @metrotwin last night. Look forward to the outputs. Stay bold.]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Fri Mar 05 03:30:34 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Fri Mar 05 03:30:34 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Thanks Jason - we had an intro to just such a place in New York and started talking but e-mails weren't replied to :(  Always ready to try again though.  Thanks for all the tweet love!]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Ian B]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email>sachanian@aol.com</wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Fri Mar 05 08:04:20 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Fri Mar 05 08:04:20 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[Lloydy, just had a look at accn in DC.  Have you tried YHA?  Address is 1009, 11st NW, Washington DC 20001. tel 1-202-737-23333, washingtonDC@hiusa.org.  Single room $69 per night.  Don't know if that is any help at all.  Try www.hihostels.com.  I also hate the word 'should'.  My definition is &quot;inactivity with implied blame&quot;.  All the best amigo, as we used to say in The Mob, 'no plan survives first contact with the enemy'. Strap on yer helmet &amp; fight thru old friend.  cheers Ian]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
</item>
