<item>
	<title>Day 4: Our adventures in three boroughs</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/day-4-our-adventures-in-three-boroughs</link>
	<pubDate>Sun Mar 07 05:37:00 -0800 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Heather Taylor]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/day-4-our-adventures-in-three-boroughs</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>Yesterday was a blur. We started with Bagels and coffee for Michelle (yes &ndash; I am still caffeine free for the NSPCC Kick bullying campaign) &ndash; Nick went out on his scooter to go and pick them up for us.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>I had an all-dressed one with all the toppings including onion.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>The thing about these bagels that make them stand out is the salt. It&rsquo;s just a thin sprinkling of it, but it makes all the difference. And you don&rsquo;t even need to put anything on it, in fact I&rsquo;d argue it&rsquo;d sully the taste if you did.</span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>First interview of the day was in Redhook with Jen and Brian Gubicza of <a href="http://www.zooguu.com" title="Zooguu">Zooguu </a>(thanks to John DeYoung who set it all up!).<span style="">&nbsp; </span>They work out of a warehouse space with around 12 other artists making stuffed toys to be sold on Etsy, their own online shop and in craft fairs.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>The warehouse is in an area that only a few years ago was known for crime &ndash; On the Waterfront was based on that area and bodies have been known to wash up on shore. More recently, gritty crime chases are filmed there &ndash; Matt Damon was filming down the road the week before so I&rsquo;m going to keep my eye out next time I&rsquo;m watching a chase scene down by the docks. A large amount of the area was bought up by a retired cop who wanted to regenerate Redhook. So anyone wanting to rent his properties has to put in a proposal to show what they will be using it for. Which is why Jen and Brian found themselves in a warehouse over looking the water (and the statue of Liberty). </span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>They are starting to get some interest from wholesalers, which can be trickier as Brian traces and cuts all the patterns for Jen to sew by hand.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Yes, that&rsquo;s right.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>All Zooguu toys are hand-made.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Lately they have been doing more collaborations with illustrators (Brian being one of them), to make stuffed toys out of their 2D work. The results have their own Zooguu-esque quality that still keeps the aesthetic that the original illustrations have.</span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>All of the toys have a quirky appeal that makes them loved by adults and children alike. And because they are homemade, you can pick what colours you want each part to be.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Jen always knows when a kid put the order in as the colours are not ones most people would ever put together.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>But that&rsquo;s what makes these toys so personal and something you could grow up with. Though Brian teases her about it, Jen always makes sure she packs the toy so when you open it; it looks up at you like it&rsquo;s greeting you like an old friend. If you want one of your own, you can order them online and you can get one sent to you anywhere in the world. Go. Do it. I&rsquo;m going to. <a href="http://www.zooguu.com" title="Zooguu">www.zooguu.com</a></span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>After lunch in midtown with my old friend Reisha, we met with Jill of <a href="http://www.jillwrites.com" title="Jill writes">www.jillwrites.com</a>, who is born and raised in Brooklyn and lives on Staten Island. We took the ferry over to Staten Island with her and looked back across the water at Manhattan. To me this ferry is the starting point of my favourite movie: Working Girl.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>Well, one of my favourite movies. The film opens up with Carly Simon singing her heart out as Melanie Griffith makes the journey into Manhattan to work her way to the top.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>She has brains and beauty but no one takes her seriously because of where she&rsquo;s from. Honestly, the Carly Simon song went through my head the whole way there AND back.</span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin: 0in 0in 0pt;"><span>On the way to the Tweet-Up at BBH in the AT&amp;T building (<a href="http://www.32sixthave.com/location.html">32 Avenue of the Americas</a>), Michelle and I made a special stop inspired by Zooguu&rsquo;s Brian &ndash; <a href="http://www.bigwaste.com/photos/ny/ghostbusters/firehouse.shtml" title="The Ghostbusters firestation">the Ghostbusters fire station</a>! Yes, photos and video were taken.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>It was much narrower than I expected but what a beautiful little firehouse it was.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>And just around the corner from where the meet up was.<p /></span><span style="font-family: Times New Roman,serif; font-size: 12pt;">Thanks go out to Dan, who helped make the tweet-up in New York happen.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>We did a live feed as the night progressed so anyone, anywhere in the world could be a part of it. I found that by capturing it and interviewing, the two hours go by too quickly and I actually met very few people there.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>And everyone I spoke was so interesting that I wish we had more time to meet and talk with everyone there.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>But I guess that&rsquo;s how it all goes and the people you meet are the right people to meet at the time.<span style="">&nbsp; </span>And in less than 2 days, I&rsquo;ve met so many wonderful people that I would have never met under other circumstances.</span></p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Yesterday was a blur. We started with Bagels and coffee for Michelle (yes – I am still caffeine free for the NSPCC Kick bullying campaign) – Nick went out on his scooter to go and pick them up for us. I had an all-dressed one with all the toppings...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Sun Mar 07 05:37:00 -0800 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
		<wp:comment>
			<!-- <wp:comment_id>5</wp:comment_id> -->
			<wp:comment_author><![CDATA[Patrick]]></wp:comment_author>
			<wp:comment_author_email></wp:comment_author_email>
			<wp:comment_author_url></wp:comment_author_url>
			<wp:comment_date>Sun Mar 07 06:24:16 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date>
			<wp:comment_date_gmt>Sun Mar 07 06:24:16 -0800 2010</wp:comment_date_gmt>
			<wp:comment_content><![CDATA[I've been processing my photos from my trip to the States last year - I still have several hundred to go... But I have some great pictures taken from the Staten Island ferry of a storm over Manhattan: shiny skyscrapers set against black clouds.

They may even get posted to flickr by the time you return! ]]></wp:comment_content>
			<wp:comment_approved>1</wp:comment_approved>
			<wp:comment_type></wp:comment_type>
			<wp:comment_parent>0</wp:comment_parent>
		</wp:comment>
	
</item>
