<item>
	<title>Retracing our steps</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/retracing-our-steps</link>
	<pubDate>Sun Apr 04 14:28:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>
	
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="afterwards"><![CDATA[afterwards]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="review"><![CDATA[review]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="sensemaking"><![CDATA[sensemaking]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="thinking"><![CDATA[thinking]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="writing"><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/retracing-our-steps</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I got back home two weeks ago tomorrow. &nbsp;</p>
<p>One week went to jetlag. &nbsp;LAX -&gt; LHR was the furthest I've ever flown and it felt like it. &nbsp;Added to the 7 hours time difference was accumulated tiredness from the trip itself and from the period leading up to it and the fact that I'd been through enough time zone changes including a Daylight Savings Time change to ensure that my body was totally confused about what time it was. &nbsp;Towards the end of that first week a friend gave me some melatonin - it worked beautifully - next time I'm not travelling without it... &nbsp;</p>
<p>Ha ha! "Next time"! You thought there wasn't going to be a next time. &nbsp;Well. &nbsp;Don't know where, don't know when, but I got the taste for this kind of travelling, meeting new people, studying culture, thinking, writing, talking, stretching and stretching my comfort zone and I'll be definitely doing it again.</p>
<p>Anyway, during the second week (the one that's just gone) I got more and more frustrated with myself for not being able to write - not being able to write up what we'd done, not being able to type up handwritten notes, not being able to annotate or tag photos. &nbsp;Plus I don't have a powerful enough computer at the moment to edit or even really look at the video I shot. &nbsp;I feel guilty about not writing about the kit I was lent for the trip mixed with a recurrence of the old resentment that these loans are so short and the value exchange so biased. &nbsp;And I feel guilty about not being able to more swiftly tell more of the stories of the amazing people we met along the way. &nbsp;So exhaustion followed by frustration, guilt and resentment - mmmm... attractive!</p>
<p>And then I started to see light at the end of the tunnel (btw didn't go through many tunnels at all on Amtrak - there's a wee story about it that needs to be written, but it's very wee and it doesn't fit here). &nbsp;I started to see what to do next. &nbsp;</p>
<p>And of course it happened at Tuttle on Friday. &nbsp;I was talking to Fergus Bell about making sense of it all, I've become obsessed with "making sense of it all" and somehow, I don't know how, neither does he, he helped me to see that my role is not so much to make sense of it all, but to create a process of some kind, to hold the space for others to make sense of it with me. &nbsp;And I felt much better. &nbsp;And then I did a little slideshow of the 956 photographs that I took and that I've uploaded to flickr. &nbsp;And I had the chance to talk about it with a group for the first time instead of the formulaic "How was the trip?" "Amazing" "Oh really what was your favourite part" etc. interview that we fall into so easily one-to-one.</p>
<p>Now that process, in it's form, is unlikely to be very different from what I was intending to do "to make sense of it all" ie I will be writing about the trip, about what we did, where we went, what I learned, how I changed, how it changed me. &nbsp;However I've let go of the responsibility of having to make it all be manageable and understandable by me and therefore I feel liberated to start doing it. &nbsp;I'm writing again - look... it's happening... as I ummm... write.</p>
<p>So all that's a bit of a warning, I suppose that what comes next here, and on perfectpath and on the tuttle blog probably, will likely be quite messy and jump around a lot &nbsp;- it won't be a smooth chronological journey back through that month of March 2010 which turned out to be so remarkable and important to me. &nbsp;It will be (at least at the start, I think) a jumble of snippets and glimpses and ramblings and it might not make sense to any of us. &nbsp;</p>
<p>And that's OK.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I got back home two weeks ago tomorrow. One week went to jetlag. LAX -> LHR was the furthest I've ever flown and it felt like it. Added to the 7 hours time difference was accumulated tiredness from the trip itself and from the period leading up to...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Sun Apr 04 14:28:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
