<item>
	<title>Overnight to Atlanta</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/overnight-to-atlanta</link>
	<pubDate>Sun Apr 04 15:39:00 -0700 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>
	
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="amtrak"><![CDATA[amtrak]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="atlanta"><![CDATA[atlanta]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="dc"><![CDATA[dc]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="distractions"><![CDATA[distractions]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="overnight"><![CDATA[overnight]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="relationships"><![CDATA[relationships]]></category>
	
		<category domain="tag" nicename="sleep"><![CDATA[sleep]]></category>
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/overnight-to-atlanta</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>
<p>[<em>I wrote this longhand in my notebook and didn't type it up. &nbsp;Soon after I wrote it, I realised that the curry I'd had for lunch was going to give me the full Johnny Cash experience - I didn't sleep much at all...]</em></p>
<p>I'm on a midnight train to Georgia. &nbsp;Well not quite. &nbsp;It's 7.30pm and we left Washington DC an hour ago for a 14 hour overnight ride to Atlanta GA. &nbsp;So I will be on it at midnight but not sure I'll be awake by then. &nbsp;Well at least I hope I'll be asleep. &nbsp;The train horn seems to sound several times a minute, in case, I guess, wandering wildlife don't hear the rattling of the tracks as we thunder through Virginia. &nbsp;There's a little low chatter in this carriage but mostly the sound is of people sitting together in communal quietness punctuated by those laughing at th eDVDs that they're watching or the shifting of someone in their seat. &nbsp;The woman behind me was oozing into her cellphone when we left DC but she's quietened down now too. &nbsp;This ride is our longest although I don't know yet what I'm going to do after Austin. &nbsp;The 1400 mile trip to LA is no more than a desire to be at LAX on Sunday 21st. &nbsp;Of course it's more than a desire, it's a necessity and it's also still two weeks away.</p>
<p>I've found it quite difficult to get into the moment on this trip, to stop thinking about what's coming and what might have been and focus on what we're actually doing right now. &nbsp;There have been two reasons for this, I think &nbsp;First was that we didn't have money in place and I couldn't see how it was going to work and got into the frame of mind where I believed somehow that thining about it some more would help. &nbsp;Big mistake. &nbsp;What really helped was to write about it, get it out and get reassured - partly by some lovely donations from friends but uals ojust from the overall reaction that people had - everyone wanted to help out. &nbsp;There isn't anything less to worry about (objectively speaking) it's just that I realised I was worrying about things over which I have little influence and recognising those limits helpe me worry less. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The other issue is that I was spending time with someone, Dana, whom I've been getting to know well for a while and whom I care for very much. &nbsp;But she also lives in Newfoundland and I in London and so we haven't spent so much time face to face. &nbsp;We've been building a romantic relationship, using these tools, we've talked to each other practically every day by skype, phreadz (thanks Kosso!) IM and DMs and we've written letters and postcards and I sent her flowers for Valentines Day, but... but we hadn't kissed until we saw each other in Boston Airport.</p>
<p>So yeah. &nbsp;I've been distracted by that too. &nbsp;Getting to build the face to face, hand in hand, gazing into each others eyes part of our relationship. &nbsp;And while that's been lovely, it did make it hard for me to focus on the early part of the trip especially as I struggled with jetlag an dgeneral tiredness after running around getting bits of the trip together. &nbsp;So now, I've stopped worrying (at least for the time being) Dana's gone back to Newfoundland to go back to work and my mind and body are getting used to which part of the world I'm in. &nbsp;And so I feel like I'm ready for the adventurous part. &nbsp;The part where we get far away from places where they're used to hearing English accents. &nbsp;Brian and I have given in on the accomodation part and are relying on the kindness of strangers despite our embarrassment at doing so, and I'm really glad that I'm going to be able to stay with Sarah Vela in Austin and hang out with the other lovelies there. &nbsp;Plus Stephanie Frost has set up big fun for us in Atlanta and Taylor D has done a great job for us on the ground in NOLA. &nbsp;The amazing adventure is getting even amazinger!</p>
<p />
</p>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[[I wrote this longhand in my notebook and didn't type it up. Soon after I wrote it, I realised that the curry I'd had for lunch was going to give me the full Johnny Cash experience - I didn't sleep much at all...] I'm on a midnight train to Georgi...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Sun Apr 04 15:39:00 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
