<item>
	<title>Whose stupid idea (redux)</title>
	<link>http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/whose-stupid-idea-redux</link>
	<pubDate>Mon Apr 05 07:05:26 -0700 2010</pubDate>
	
	<dc:creator><![CDATA[Lloyd Davis]]></dc:creator>
	
	

	<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

	<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://tuttle2texas.posterous.com/whose-stupid-idea-redux</guid>
	<description></description>
	<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; margin-top: 8px; margin-right: 8px; margin-bottom: 8px; margin-left: 8px; background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"> <p>I&#39;m on the floor.</p><p>I&#39;m actually lying on the floor of the train carriage.  In the baggage section at the back.  I just filmed out of the back window as we left Austin and now after a couple of hours or so down to San Antonio we&#39;re on a 7 hour layover there in the sidings.  I can&#39;t sleep next to this guy that I&#39;ve just met. Is this because I&#39;m a soft English scaredy-cat or because I have justifiable reservations about falling asleeep on a train, thousands of miles from home next to a complete stranger.  Would you?  You would? Well I think you&#39;re weird.</p> <p>A crazy spanish-speaking lady is talking to a girl who got on in Austin.  The lady has a lot to say.  The girl is just smiling.  The lady isn&#39;t going to sleep in her seat she&#39;s going to sleep on the floor.  And I decide to copy her.</p> <p>Where did all this start?  Why am I doing it anyway?  Where do any ideas begin?  We don&#39;t really know, do we?  In my experience, every time we say it was this moment when it came together there&#39;s always some pre-cursor, some other thought or conversation that can legitimately lay claim to leading up to this one.</p> <p>So we just have to grab at one.  I don&#39;t think it&#39;s too much of a stretch to take this back to march last year, when I returned from my first SXSW, full of excitement and inspiration and induced enthusiasm simply from being in the presence of so many excitable American entrepreneurs.  but yes, back then I was thinking of how I could get back to Austin.  I had to borrow money in order to pay my hotel bill and that was not something I was comfortable with.  and so while I wasn&#39;t giving it much thought, I had decided that I would want to go, but needed help from some other source.  I tried first to get a panel slot.  I proposed, got support from the community and it ll seemed well received but then in each of the rounds of announcements of who was speaking I found myself understanding that it wasn&#39;t going to be me.  And so I started looking for other ways to make it happen anyway.  and of course I started to talk about it.  I started to socialise the idea, sound it out with people.  &quot;I wonder how we could do this...&quot; Which is, by the way, exactly the same process that we went through with both Tuttle itself and Tuttle Consultingl.  I don&#39;t know at what point it became a thing.  A real thing that we were trying to do.  but I think it was December 3rd when we presented all the work for Counterpoint and we were all sitting round afterwards.</p> <p>Was that Brian&#39;s birthday?  I think it was, yes.  anyhow we did talk about it then.  I confessed it, as a half-formed idea, that we should see whether we could fly to an eastern part of North America and then find our way across by train - surely that must be doable.  And lots of people, of course, said &quot;yes, yes we&#39;d like to do that&quot;  We, as a group, were full of &quot;what&#39;s next&quot; energy.  The thrill of having delivered and the excitement of seeing another project come alive.  And then, like it&#39;s elder siblings, it needed to percolate for a while.  Over Christmas I decided that it was something I wanted to do and that I wanted to pull other people in.</p> <p>So naturally, I wrote a blog post.</p> </div>]]></content:encoded>
	<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[I'm on the floor.I'm actually lying on the floor of the train carriage. In the baggage section at the back. I just filmed out of the back window as we left Austin and now after a couple of hours or so down to San Antonio we're on a 7 hour layover ...]]></excerpt:encoded>	

	<wp:post_date>Mon Apr 05 07:05:26 -0700 2010</wp:post_date>
	<wp:post_date_gmt>%= display_date %></wp:post_date_gmt>
	<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
	<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
	<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
	<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
	<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
	<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
	<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
	<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
	<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>

	
</item>
